2
00:00:01,240 --> 00:00:03,550
A royal wedding is history.

3
00:00:05,670 --> 00:00:06,960
He's choking!

4
00:00:07,140 --> 00:00:09,050
- Come with me now. - Joffrey! Joffrey!

5
00:00:09,480 --> 00:00:11,420
He poisoned my son.

6
00:00:11,420 --> 00:00:13,780
Take him. Take him!

7
00:00:15,200 --> 00:00:17,160
You're safe with me

8
00:00:18,020 --> 00:00:19,540
and sailing home.

9
00:00:20,790 --> 00:00:24,620
They say 1,000 slaves died building the Great Pyramid of Meereen.

13
00:00:32,260 --> 00:00:34,070
Mhysa! Mhysa!

14
00:00:34,620 --> 00:00:35,890
Your brother is dead.

15
00:00:35,890 --> 00:00:37,480
Do you know what that means?

16
00:00:37,480 --> 00:00:39,520
- It means I'll become king. - Yes.

17
00:00:39,520 --> 00:00:41,270
Now, as the king,

18
00:00:41,270 --> 00:00:43,170
you will have to marry.

19
00:00:44,190 --> 00:00:48,740
I demand a trial by combat.

20
00:00:51,130 --> 00:00:52,550
Tyrion Lannister,

21
00:00:52,550 --> 00:00:54,760
you are hereby sentenced to death.

22
00:00:55,260 --> 00:00:57,010
He came from the sky.

23
00:00:57,320 --> 00:00:58,400
My girl.

24
00:00:58,910 --> 00:01:00,090
My little girl.

25
00:01:06,000 --> 00:01:07,820
Myrcella is my only daughter.

26
00:01:07,820 --> 00:01:10,190
Dorne is the safest place for her.

27
00:01:11,340 --> 00:01:12,890
You're Arya Stark.

28
00:01:12,890 --> 00:01:14,370
I'll take you to safety.

29
00:01:16,890 --> 00:01:18,090
Arya!

30
00:01:18,480 --> 00:01:19,900
Arya!

31
00:01:20,050 --> 00:01:21,140
Cousin Lancel,

32
00:01:21,140 --> 00:01:23,690
Cersei must have great trust in you.

33
00:01:23,950 --> 00:01:25,150
Get back into bed.

34
00:01:26,010 --> 00:01:27,260
More wine, your grace?

35
00:01:28,770 --> 00:01:30,300
The bore got me.

36
00:01:30,300 --> 00:01:33,000
100 generations have defended this castle.

37
00:01:33,000 --> 00:01:34,430
She will not fall tonight.

38
00:01:34,430 --> 00:01:36,470
Let's kill some crows!

39
00:01:45,060 --> 00:01:46,550
- Are you attacking us? - No.

40
00:01:46,560 --> 00:01:47,800
We don't have the men.

41
00:01:48,770 --> 00:01:49,860
Stand down!

42
00:01:50,290 --> 00:01:54,100
It is customary to kneel when surrendering to a king.

43
00:01:54,410 --> 00:01:56,040
We do not kneel.

44
00:01:57,030 --> 00:01:57,930
What are you doing?

45
00:01:57,930 --> 00:01:59,260
What do you think I'm doing?

46
00:02:01,530 --> 00:02:02,510
I'm sorry.

47
00:02:04,020 --> 00:02:04,910
Tyrion.

48
00:02:05,060 --> 00:02:07,130
You're no son of mine.

49
00:02:07,130 --> 00:02:08,400
I am your son.

50
00:02:11,370 --> 00:02:12,580
What have you done?

51
00:04:21,250 --> 00:04:23,800
- We shouldn't be out here alone. - Why not?

52
00:04:23,910 --> 00:04:26,490
- If your father... - He'll never know we're gone.

53
00:04:26,920 --> 00:04:28,530
But if he finds out...

54
00:04:32,660 --> 00:04:34,950
You don't need to be afraid of my father.

55
00:05:02,240 --> 00:05:03,590
Are you sure?

56
00:05:04,870 --> 00:05:05,820
Yes.

57
00:05:06,470 --> 00:05:09,440
- We shouldn't go in. - Of course we should.

58
00:05:53,930 --> 00:05:56,720
Get out. Get out!

59
00:05:56,840 --> 00:05:58,460
- Let's go. - No.

60
00:05:59,380 --> 00:06:00,870
Listen to your friend.

61
00:06:02,310 --> 00:06:04,240
They said that you were terrifying

62
00:06:04,830 --> 00:06:07,140
with cat's teeth and three eyes.

63
00:06:07,710 --> 00:06:09,340
You're not terrifying.

64
00:06:11,460 --> 00:06:12,640
You're boring.

65
00:06:13,600 --> 00:06:15,360
You don't know what I am.

66
00:06:15,360 --> 00:06:18,820
I know you're a witch and you can see the future.

67
00:06:20,650 --> 00:06:21,920
Tell me mine.

68
00:06:21,920 --> 00:06:24,180
Everyone wants to know their future

69
00:06:24,650 --> 00:06:26,150
until they know their future.

70
00:06:26,150 --> 00:06:29,890
This is my father's land. My land.

71
00:06:29,960 --> 00:06:31,100
Tell me my future

72
00:06:31,100 --> 00:06:35,200
or I'll have your two boring eyes gouged out of your head.

73
00:06:44,520 --> 00:06:45,670
Your blood.

74
00:06:47,650 --> 00:06:48,940
Give me a taste.

75
00:07:14,350 --> 00:07:16,050
Three questions you get.

76
00:07:17,160 --> 00:07:18,880
You won't like the answers.

77
00:07:23,180 --> 00:07:25,140
I've been promised to the prince.

78
00:07:26,620 --> 00:07:28,190
When will we marry?

79
00:07:28,380 --> 00:07:30,200
You will never wed the prince.

80
00:07:30,510 --> 00:07:31,960
You will wed the king.

81
00:07:32,300 --> 00:07:33,570
But I will be queen?

82
00:07:33,570 --> 00:07:34,890
Oh, yes.

83
00:07:36,170 --> 00:07:37,480
You'll be queen.

84
00:07:38,710 --> 00:07:39,960
For a time.

85
00:07:41,430 --> 00:07:42,800
Then comes another,

86
00:07:43,950 --> 00:07:45,100
younger,

87
00:07:45,820 --> 00:07:47,230
more beautiful,

88
00:07:47,680 --> 00:07:51,190
to cast you down and take all you hold dear.

89
00:07:52,000 --> 00:07:53,970
W-will the king and I have children?

90
00:07:53,970 --> 00:07:58,170
No. The king will have 20 children

91
00:07:58,170 --> 00:07:59,530
and you will have three.

92
00:07:59,530 --> 00:08:00,440
That doesn't make sense.

93
00:08:00,440 --> 00:08:02,320
Gold will be their crowns.

94
00:08:04,000 --> 00:08:06,620
Gold their shrouds.

95
00:08:14,110 --> 00:08:15,640
Come on, we have to go.

96
00:08:17,440 --> 00:08:19,400
We have to go! Cersei!

97
00:08:23,490 --> 00:08:24,910
Bearers, put it down.

98
00:08:41,690 --> 00:08:43,520
Bearers, up.

99
00:08:44,050 --> 00:08:45,010
Away.

100
00:08:59,410 --> 00:09:01,950
Your Grace, we are honored by your presence.

101
00:09:01,950 --> 00:09:03,370
The mourners are waiting.

102
00:09:03,370 --> 00:09:04,770
They will keep waiting.

103
00:09:05,920 --> 00:09:07,500
I want a moment alone with him.

104
00:09:07,710 --> 00:09:09,890
But, Your Grace, many of these lords and ladies have travelled

105
00:09:09,900 --> 00:09:12,870
day and night to be here from all seven kingdoms.

106
00:09:12,870 --> 00:09:14,100
They will wait.

107
00:09:41,780 --> 00:09:43,970
He never wanted you to be a Kingsguard,

108
00:09:43,970 --> 00:09:46,820
but here you are, protecting his dead body.

109
00:09:49,250 --> 00:09:53,360
What he built, it's ours.

110
00:09:54,750 --> 00:09:57,440
He built it for us. He meant it for us.

111
00:09:59,600 --> 00:10:01,180
They're going to try to take it away.

112
00:10:01,180 --> 00:10:02,200
- All of it. - They?

113
00:10:02,200 --> 00:10:05,050
All of them out there, our enemies.

114
00:10:05,700 --> 00:10:07,860
They're waiting in line to make sure he's really dead.

115
00:10:07,860 --> 00:10:09,790
And as soon as they see the stones on his eyes,

116
00:10:09,790 --> 00:10:11,450
they'll set to work on tearing us apart.

117
00:10:11,450 --> 00:10:13,030
They have nothing to do with it.

118
00:10:14,160 --> 00:10:16,500
The man who murdered our father, he tore us apart.

119
00:10:16,510 --> 00:10:18,830
He's the enemy. I've been telling you for years.

120
00:10:18,830 --> 00:10:20,150
You've been defending him for years.

121
00:10:20,150 --> 00:10:21,620
This is exactly what they want.

122
00:10:21,620 --> 00:10:23,490
And now our father is dead

123
00:10:24,070 --> 00:10:27,600
and that little monster is out there somewhere drawing breath.

124
00:10:29,560 --> 00:10:30,940
Did you set him free?

125
00:10:34,540 --> 00:10:35,730
Tyrion may be a monster,

126
00:10:35,740 --> 00:10:39,070
but at least he killed our father on purpose.

127
00:10:40,060 --> 00:10:41,880
You killed him by mistake.

128
00:10:41,940 --> 00:10:43,330
With stupidity.

129
00:10:45,330 --> 00:10:46,910
You're a man of action, aren't you?

130
00:10:46,910 --> 00:10:49,420
When it occurs to you to do something, you do it.

131
00:10:49,530 --> 00:10:51,380
Never mind the consequences.

132
00:10:54,580 --> 00:10:55,680
Take a look.

133
00:10:56,920 --> 00:10:58,630
Look at the consequences.

134
00:11:01,100 --> 00:11:02,180
Here they are.

135
00:11:06,820 --> 00:11:09,490
He loved you more than anyone in this world.

136
00:12:42,520 --> 00:12:43,690
Apologies.

137
00:12:54,280 --> 00:12:57,230
I still don't see why I had to stay

138
00:12:57,230 --> 00:13:00,420
in this fucking crate once we set sail.

139
00:13:00,420 --> 00:13:01,990
I saved your life.

140
00:13:02,580 --> 00:13:04,590
If they catch you, they catch me.

141
00:13:05,210 --> 00:13:07,000
I cannot say I feel overly guilty

142
00:13:07,000 --> 00:13:09,490
about leaving you in that fucking crate.

143
00:13:09,490 --> 00:13:11,990
Do you know what it's like to stuff your shit

144
00:13:11,990 --> 00:13:13,800
through one of those airholes?

145
00:13:13,850 --> 00:13:15,670
No, I only know what it's like

146
00:13:15,670 --> 00:13:18,120
to pick up your shit and throw it overboard.

147
00:13:21,530 --> 00:13:22,740
Pentos?

148
00:13:24,140 --> 00:13:27,290
The home of my colleague Illyrio Mopatis,

149
00:13:27,460 --> 00:13:28,610
a merchant.

150
00:13:28,620 --> 00:13:30,390
He and I met many years ago

151
00:13:30,390 --> 00:13:32,230
through mutual friends.

152
00:13:32,640 --> 00:13:35,110
A group of people who saw Robert Baratheon

153
00:13:35,110 --> 00:13:37,040
for the disaster he was.

154
00:13:37,540 --> 00:13:40,020
We tried to do what was best for the realm

155
00:13:40,020 --> 00:13:42,460
by supporting a Targaryen restoration.

156
00:13:43,480 --> 00:13:45,860
And thus began the chain of mistakes

157
00:13:45,860 --> 00:13:47,690
that has led us both here.

158
00:13:48,610 --> 00:13:51,580
Things have gotten worse, not better.

159
00:13:52,130 --> 00:13:55,230
Westeros needs to be saved from itself.

160
00:14:01,010 --> 00:14:02,200
Much better.

161
00:14:02,700 --> 00:14:03,660
My lord?

162
00:14:06,200 --> 00:14:08,660
I don't think I am anymore.

163
00:14:09,600 --> 00:14:10,800
A lord.

164
00:14:19,200 --> 00:14:21,610
Are you a lord if you kill your father?

165
00:14:23,370 --> 00:14:28,190
I don't imagine they revoke your nobility for killing a whore.

166
00:14:28,680 --> 00:14:30,350
It must happen all the time.

167
00:14:30,620 --> 00:14:33,000
You already drank yourself across the Narrow Sea.

168
00:14:33,000 --> 00:14:34,990
In a box. Why stop now?

169
00:14:34,990 --> 00:14:38,140
Because we are talking about the future of our country.

170
00:14:42,210 --> 00:14:44,870
The future is shit.

171
00:14:47,020 --> 00:14:48,930
Just like the past.

177
00:17:56,430 --> 00:17:57,630
The Sons of the Harpy?

178
00:17:57,950 --> 00:18:00,270
Yes, Your Grace. They left it on the body.

179
00:18:00,270 --> 00:18:01,690
They've never killed before.

180
00:18:02,080 --> 00:18:03,810
It was only a matter of time, Your Grace.

181
00:18:04,550 --> 00:18:06,730
Conquerors always meet with resistance.

182
00:18:06,730 --> 00:18:08,930
I didn't conquer them. Their own people did.

185
00:18:17,200 --> 00:18:19,790
He did not risk his life fighting for his freedom

186
00:18:19,790 --> 00:18:21,800
so cowards in masks could take it away.

187
00:18:21,800 --> 00:18:23,820
And I did not take up residence in this pyramid

188
00:18:23,820 --> 00:18:26,990
so I could watch the city below decline into chaos.

189
00:18:28,040 --> 00:18:29,560
What was the name of the man you lost?

190
00:18:30,550 --> 00:18:32,250
White Rat, Your Grace.

191
00:18:33,100 --> 00:18:36,620
I want him buried with honor, publically

192
00:18:37,280 --> 00:18:38,780
in the Temple of the Graces.

193
00:18:39,540 --> 00:18:41,560
The Sons of the Harpy will hear that message.

194
00:18:41,560 --> 00:18:43,240
Make them very angry.

195
00:18:43,240 --> 00:18:45,050
Angry snakes lash out.

196
00:18:45,330 --> 00:18:47,710
Makes chopping off their heads that much easier.

197
00:18:48,090 --> 00:18:51,230
Find the men who did this and bring them to me.

198
00:18:55,380 --> 00:18:56,120
Your Grace.

199
00:19:10,680 --> 00:19:11,770
Torgo Nudho.

200
00:19:12,560 --> 00:19:14,110
Missandei hin Naath.

201
00:19:16,160 --> 00:19:17,810
I wanted to speak with you.

202
00:19:26,760 --> 00:19:27,920
Why do you come?

203
00:19:29,250 --> 00:19:31,500
White Rat, the Unsullied who...

204
00:19:34,190 --> 00:19:36,900
I have heard they found his body in a brothel.

205
00:19:38,690 --> 00:19:41,520
I have heard that more than one Unsullied

206
00:19:41,520 --> 00:19:44,070
has been known to visit Meereen's brothels.

207
00:19:47,040 --> 00:19:48,540
May I ask you why?

208
00:19:50,580 --> 00:19:52,750
Why would an Unsullied go to a brothel?

209
00:19:57,390 --> 00:19:58,470
I do not know.

210
00:20:01,310 --> 00:20:02,170
I must go.

211
00:20:19,020 --> 00:20:20,880
- Get your shield up. - It's too heavy.

212
00:20:20,880 --> 00:20:22,300
If it wasn't heavy, it wouldn't stop a sword.

213
00:20:22,300 --> 00:20:23,340
Now get it up.

214
00:20:36,550 --> 00:20:38,580
Come. Try it again.

215
00:20:39,160 --> 00:20:41,640
Drive at me. Keep your shield up.

216
00:20:42,130 --> 00:20:43,530
Or I'll ring your head like a bell.

217
00:20:44,620 --> 00:20:46,230
Shouldn't you be training, too?

218
00:20:47,820 --> 00:20:50,520
I'm hardly a new recruit.

219
00:20:53,120 --> 00:20:54,280
How many brothers can say

220
00:20:54,280 --> 00:20:56,300
that they've killed a white walker and a Thenn?

221
00:20:56,760 --> 00:20:58,450
I might be the first in history.

222
00:20:58,970 --> 00:21:01,100
These men need a firm hand.

223
00:21:01,690 --> 00:21:02,670
Always have.

224
00:21:02,870 --> 00:21:04,960
They're poachers and thieves.

225
00:21:07,380 --> 00:21:08,900
Not soldiers.

226
00:21:15,190 --> 00:21:16,560
That one hates me.

227
00:21:18,760 --> 00:21:21,280
If Ser Alliser is chosen as the new Lord Commander...

228
00:21:22,160 --> 00:21:23,450
He hates the wildlings.

229
00:21:25,190 --> 00:21:26,470
All the wildlings.

230
00:21:26,470 --> 00:21:28,790
- Don't let them send us away. - It's not a sure thing.

231
00:21:28,790 --> 00:21:31,980
Ser Denys Mallister has commanded the Shadow Tower for 20 years

232
00:21:31,990 --> 00:21:33,370
and people say he's a good man.

233
00:21:33,370 --> 00:21:34,600
He's running against Ser Alliser...

234
00:21:34,600 --> 00:21:37,390
Sam, don't let them send us away.

235
00:21:37,390 --> 00:21:38,520
I told you.

236
00:21:39,540 --> 00:21:41,960
Wherever you go, I go, too.

237
00:21:41,960 --> 00:21:44,090
You can't leave. They'll execute you.

238
00:21:51,930 --> 00:21:53,980
Good, good, pivot. Don't forget to pivot.

239
00:21:55,840 --> 00:21:56,680
Shield up.

240
00:21:59,330 --> 00:22:00,690
The king wants a word.

241
00:22:29,710 --> 00:22:30,880
You're not cold, my lady?

242
00:22:31,800 --> 00:22:32,550
Never.

243
00:22:34,080 --> 00:22:36,660
The Lord's fire lives within me, Jon Snow.

244
00:22:39,920 --> 00:22:40,600
Feel.

245
00:22:48,960 --> 00:22:50,070
Are you a virgin?

246
00:22:54,660 --> 00:22:55,290
No.

247
00:22:58,240 --> 00:22:58,910
Good.

248
00:23:06,790 --> 00:23:07,600
Your Grace.

249
00:23:08,690 --> 00:23:10,220
The bastard of Winterfell.

250
00:23:20,090 --> 00:23:21,860
You know who rules at Winterfell now?

251
00:23:23,480 --> 00:23:24,520
Roose Bolton.

252
00:23:25,200 --> 00:23:27,980
The traitor who plunged a dagger in Robb Stark's heart.

253
00:23:29,920 --> 00:23:31,180
Don't you want to avenge him?

254
00:23:32,820 --> 00:23:35,030
I want a great many things, Your Grace.

255
00:23:36,150 --> 00:23:38,260
But I'm a sworn brother of the Night's Watch now.

256
00:23:38,780 --> 00:23:40,750
I've been talking to your sworn brothers.

257
00:23:41,870 --> 00:23:43,610
- Many of them love you. - They're good men.

258
00:23:43,610 --> 00:23:44,470
Many don't.

259
00:23:45,600 --> 00:23:49,250
You were seen taking the body of a wildling girl north of the Wall.

260
00:23:49,850 --> 00:23:50,520
Why?

261
00:23:51,030 --> 00:23:52,190
It's where she belonged.

262
00:23:52,620 --> 00:23:54,340
Some of the Night's Watch feel you have

263
00:23:54,360 --> 00:23:56,110
too much affection for the wildlings.

264
00:23:56,110 --> 00:23:58,060
They were born on the wrong side of the Wall.

265
00:23:59,330 --> 00:24:00,830
That doesn't make them monsters.

266
00:24:01,200 --> 00:24:01,940
No matter.

267
00:24:02,340 --> 00:24:05,070
I shall take back the North from the thieves who stole it.

268
00:24:05,070 --> 00:24:07,530
Tywin Lannister is dead. He can't protect them now.

269
00:24:07,750 --> 00:24:10,840
I shall mount Roose Bolton's head on a spike.

270
00:24:11,740 --> 00:24:13,950
But if I'm to take Winterfell, I need more men.

271
00:24:14,270 --> 00:24:16,920
The men of the Night's Watch are sworn to play no part--

272
00:24:16,920 --> 00:24:18,820
I'm not talking about the damn Night's Watch.

273
00:24:18,920 --> 00:24:20,360
I'm talking about the wildlings.

274
00:24:29,620 --> 00:24:32,700
Your Grace, you want the wildlings

275
00:24:32,890 --> 00:24:34,250
to march in your army?

276
00:24:34,610 --> 00:24:36,630
If they swear to follow me, I'll pardon them.

277
00:24:36,730 --> 00:24:38,540
We'll take Winterfell. Once the North is won,

278
00:24:38,540 --> 00:24:40,480
I'll declare them citizens of the realm.

279
00:24:40,590 --> 00:24:42,030
I'll give them land to live on.

280
00:24:42,710 --> 00:24:45,450
It's a fair offer. More than fair.

281
00:24:45,850 --> 00:24:47,750
I'll offer them their lives and their freedom

282
00:24:48,100 --> 00:24:50,960
if Mance kneels before me and swears his loyalty.

283
00:24:51,410 --> 00:24:52,790
I don't think that's likely.

284
00:24:55,280 --> 00:24:56,460
You admire him, don't you?

285
00:24:56,460 --> 00:24:58,840
- I respect him. - He likes you.

286
00:24:59,200 --> 00:25:01,060
- Convince him to bend the knee... - Your Grace.

287
00:25:01,060 --> 00:25:02,230
or he burns.

288
00:25:06,450 --> 00:25:07,720
How much time do I have?

289
00:25:08,000 --> 00:25:08,990
Nightfall.

290
00:25:09,540 --> 00:25:11,640
The sun drops fast this time of year.

291
00:25:11,820 --> 00:25:13,240
Hurry, Jon Snow.

292
00:25:17,110 --> 00:25:17,860
Shield up.

293
00:25:19,280 --> 00:25:20,800
Attack, my lord!

294
00:25:21,610 --> 00:25:22,550
Attack!

295
00:25:23,700 --> 00:25:25,270
Don't cross your feet.

296
00:25:26,440 --> 00:25:28,010
My sons had swords in their hands

297
00:25:28,020 --> 00:25:29,950
from the time they could walk. This one...

298
00:25:29,950 --> 00:25:31,990
Lord Arryn will never be a great warrior.

299
00:25:32,000 --> 00:25:33,240
Great warrior?

300
00:25:33,920 --> 00:25:36,580
He swings a sword like a girl with palsy.

301
00:25:36,580 --> 00:25:37,430
My lord.

302
00:25:39,830 --> 00:25:41,420
Sword up, my lord!

303
00:25:49,130 --> 00:25:50,990
Some boys develop more slowly.

304
00:25:52,070 --> 00:25:53,180
He's still young.

305
00:25:53,180 --> 00:25:56,180
He's 13. Boys go to war at 13.

306
00:25:56,180 --> 00:25:58,090
- He has other gifts. - Does he?

307
00:25:58,770 --> 00:26:00,310
The gift of a great name.

308
00:26:01,120 --> 00:26:04,510
Sometimes that's all one needs.

309
00:26:09,860 --> 00:26:12,450
Good-bye, Lord Royce, and thank you for all you've done for me.

310
00:26:12,450 --> 00:26:14,860
I have done nothing more than my duty, my lady.

311
00:26:14,940 --> 00:26:16,380
I have no doubt that on my return,

312
00:26:16,380 --> 00:26:18,990
Robin's skills will have improved immeasurably.

313
00:26:19,710 --> 00:26:21,080
He'll be safe here.

314
00:26:22,090 --> 00:26:23,840
As for his skills,

315
00:26:24,420 --> 00:26:26,160
I make no promises.

316
00:26:39,600 --> 00:26:41,160
Will we head north at some point?

317
00:26:42,800 --> 00:26:45,430
He said Sansa had a brother at Castle Black.

318
00:26:46,310 --> 00:26:48,300
We're a few days' ride from the Kingsroad.

319
00:26:48,620 --> 00:26:50,620
- But that will take us-- - Us?

320
00:26:52,790 --> 00:26:55,180
The only reason you're here is because Jaime Lannister

321
00:26:55,180 --> 00:26:57,330
told me you weren't safe in the capital.

322
00:26:59,330 --> 00:27:01,420
You're hundreds of miles from King's Landing.

323
00:27:02,210 --> 00:27:03,820
No one knows what you look like.

324
00:27:04,180 --> 00:27:07,230
No one cares. You're safe.

325
00:27:07,300 --> 00:27:09,870
- But I'm your squire. - Do you even know what a squire is?

326
00:27:12,280 --> 00:27:13,480
An attendant to a knight.

327
00:27:13,480 --> 00:27:14,590
I'm not a knight.

328
00:27:15,070 --> 00:27:16,590
That means you're not a squire.

329
00:27:17,620 --> 00:27:18,570
Well, where would I go?

330
00:27:18,570 --> 00:27:20,690
I don't care. I'm not your mother.

331
00:27:30,110 --> 00:27:32,090
You swore to find the Stark girls.

332
00:27:32,090 --> 00:27:34,930
I found Arya. She didn't want my protection.

333
00:27:34,930 --> 00:27:37,150
- Sansa still might. - Will you shut your mouth?

334
00:27:38,180 --> 00:27:39,810
I didn't ask for your advice.

335
00:27:42,450 --> 00:27:44,350
I don't want anyone following me.

336
00:27:44,890 --> 00:27:46,010
I'm not a leader.

337
00:27:46,850 --> 00:27:49,390
All I ever wanted was to fight for a lord I believed in.

338
00:27:50,080 --> 00:27:52,380
The good lords are dead and the rest are monsters.

339
00:28:03,270 --> 00:28:05,790
You told Lord Royce we were going to the Fingers.

340
00:28:05,790 --> 00:28:06,650
I did.

341
00:28:08,210 --> 00:28:10,930
- But we're heading west. - We are.

342
00:28:11,320 --> 00:28:13,490
If he wanted to betray us, he already would have.

343
00:28:15,340 --> 00:28:18,120
Lord Royce might be as honorable as he thinks he is,

344
00:28:18,420 --> 00:28:20,090
but he's not alone in that castle.

345
00:28:20,730 --> 00:28:22,820
Do you trust all those knights and ladies,

346
00:28:22,820 --> 00:28:24,950
stable boys and serving girls?

347
00:28:24,950 --> 00:28:28,290
No, do you trust the carriage driver or the knights escorting us?

348
00:28:28,290 --> 00:28:29,190
No.

349
00:28:30,560 --> 00:28:31,810
But I pay them well

350
00:28:32,040 --> 00:28:34,340
and they've seen what happens to men who disappoint me.

351
00:28:34,340 --> 00:28:35,850
So where are we going?

352
00:28:36,770 --> 00:28:38,730
To a land where you trust everyone?

353
00:28:39,190 --> 00:28:41,570
To a land so far from here,

354
00:28:41,930 --> 00:28:44,500
even Cersei Lannister can't get her hands on you.

355
00:28:52,540 --> 00:28:55,930
It was such a deep, deep shock to us all.

356
00:28:59,550 --> 00:29:00,660
Your father was a--

357
00:29:01,440 --> 00:29:03,350
a force to be reckoned with.

358
00:29:03,740 --> 00:29:04,720
He truly was.

359
00:29:05,940 --> 00:29:09,470
I wouldn't presume to claim to have known him as such, but--

360
00:29:10,290 --> 00:29:13,130
but just being in his presence was enough to make it so clear

361
00:29:13,660 --> 00:29:16,760
just how formidable a person you were dealing with.

362
00:29:16,950 --> 00:29:20,490
What a-- what a force to be reckoned with.

363
00:29:21,850 --> 00:29:24,100
Thank you so much for your kind words.

364
00:29:29,240 --> 00:29:31,300
Deepest condolences, Your Grace.

365
00:29:31,300 --> 00:29:34,220
This tragedy... I never trusted Varys.

366
00:29:34,220 --> 00:29:35,480
I often warned...

367
00:29:40,690 --> 00:29:41,510
Your Grace.

368
00:29:44,100 --> 00:29:46,690
Cousin Lancel. I hardly recognized you.

369
00:29:46,690 --> 00:29:47,980
My deepest sympathies.

370
00:29:49,440 --> 00:29:51,940
I apologize for my son's appearance.

371
00:29:52,150 --> 00:29:53,670
Uncle, that's quite all right.

372
00:29:56,630 --> 00:29:58,600
They call themselves sparrows.

373
00:29:59,410 --> 00:30:00,870
Bloody fanatics.

374
00:30:01,250 --> 00:30:03,410
Religion has its place, of course,

375
00:30:03,410 --> 00:30:04,750
but at a certain point...

376
00:30:06,160 --> 00:30:08,950
They never would have come to the capital when Tywin was alive.

377
00:30:08,950 --> 00:30:10,740
I'm sure he'll grow out of it,

378
00:30:10,940 --> 00:30:11,970
whatever it is.

379
00:30:13,150 --> 00:30:14,840
- Excuse me. - Of course.

380
00:30:33,750 --> 00:30:36,330
Your wounds from the Blackwater seem to have healed.

381
00:30:37,390 --> 00:30:39,630
It wasn't my wounds that needed healing.

382
00:30:42,520 --> 00:30:43,690
What can I do for you?

383
00:30:45,800 --> 00:30:46,920
You can forgive me.

384
00:30:47,790 --> 00:30:50,620
What could you possibly have done to warrant my forgiveness?

385
00:30:50,930 --> 00:30:53,080
I led you into the darkness.

386
00:30:53,190 --> 00:30:55,070
I doubt you've ever led anyone anywhere.

387
00:30:55,720 --> 00:30:57,450
I tempted you into our...

388
00:30:58,530 --> 00:31:00,440
unnatural relations.

389
00:31:02,150 --> 00:31:05,320
And, of course, there was the king...

390
00:31:07,490 --> 00:31:08,680
his boar hunt.

391
00:31:11,390 --> 00:31:12,230
His wine.

392
00:31:16,160 --> 00:31:17,550
I don't know what you're talking about.

393
00:31:19,210 --> 00:31:20,820
I'm a different person now.

394
00:31:22,820 --> 00:31:25,770
I've found peace in the light of the Seven.

395
00:31:26,010 --> 00:31:27,080
You can, too.

396
00:31:27,160 --> 00:31:28,610
They watch over all of us,

397
00:31:28,850 --> 00:31:30,540
ready to dole out mercy

398
00:31:31,920 --> 00:31:32,950
or justice.

399
00:31:36,650 --> 00:31:38,470
Their world is at hand.

400
00:31:41,480 --> 00:31:43,270
I will pray for your father's soul.

401
00:31:45,830 --> 00:31:49,050
The day Tywin Lannister's soul needs your help...

402
00:31:57,840 --> 00:32:00,740
- It looks like Dorne. - It doesn't.

403
00:32:01,570 --> 00:32:02,440
It does.

404
00:32:03,540 --> 00:32:07,490
That's the-- that's the Sunspear bit right there.

405
00:32:08,550 --> 00:32:10,590
And that's where the mountains are.

406
00:32:11,370 --> 00:32:12,800
And over here is--

407
00:32:14,160 --> 00:32:16,520
is Sunsnake?

408
00:32:16,980 --> 00:32:18,020
Stonespear?

409
00:32:18,030 --> 00:32:19,070
Sandstone.

410
00:32:19,880 --> 00:32:20,580
Yes.

411
00:32:21,360 --> 00:32:23,090
Yes, Sandstone.

412
00:32:25,260 --> 00:32:26,220
Just there.

413
00:32:27,050 --> 00:32:27,840
Fine.

414
00:32:31,360 --> 00:32:32,230
It's Dorne.

415
00:32:34,230 --> 00:32:35,200
We should go there.

416
00:32:36,400 --> 00:32:39,240
I think we would have a lovely time,

417
00:32:39,540 --> 00:32:41,590
judging by my experience.

418
00:32:41,930 --> 00:32:45,060
That would be wonderful. Dorne, Highgarden.

419
00:32:46,120 --> 00:32:47,270
Anywhere but here.

420
00:32:56,840 --> 00:32:58,620
We're late for dinner as it is.

421
00:32:59,830 --> 00:33:00,830
You're very respectful.

422
00:33:00,830 --> 00:33:02,060
I'm very hungry.

423
00:33:19,700 --> 00:33:20,780
What's your name?

424
00:33:22,270 --> 00:33:23,560
Olyvar, my lady.

425
00:33:24,050 --> 00:33:28,970
I'm afraid my brother is keeping the king waiting, Olyvar.

426
00:33:38,520 --> 00:33:39,200
My lady.

427
00:33:53,460 --> 00:33:56,790
Perhaps you might consider being a bit more discreet?

428
00:33:57,330 --> 00:33:57,950
Why?

429
00:33:58,880 --> 00:34:00,460
They all know about me anyway.

430
00:34:01,270 --> 00:34:03,610
Everybody knows everything about everyone.

431
00:34:04,360 --> 00:34:06,460
What's the point in trying to keep a secret in a place like this?

432
00:34:06,460 --> 00:34:10,050
In any event, you shouldn't keep your intended waiting.

433
00:34:11,390 --> 00:34:13,520
My intended? Please.

434
00:34:13,520 --> 00:34:14,510
Tywin's dead.

435
00:34:14,850 --> 00:34:17,000
That means no one can force Cersei to marry me.

436
00:34:17,000 --> 00:34:18,900
- Lucky you. - Unlucky you.

437
00:34:18,900 --> 00:34:21,250
You think I want that woman married to my brother?

438
00:34:21,250 --> 00:34:24,510
If she doesn't marry me, she doesn't go to Highgarden.

439
00:34:24,980 --> 00:34:26,950
Which means she stays in King's Landing.

440
00:34:27,300 --> 00:34:28,580
Which means you're trapped here

441
00:34:28,580 --> 00:34:31,070
with Cersei Lannister as your mother by law.

442
00:34:31,720 --> 00:34:32,510
Perhaps.

443
00:34:34,040 --> 00:34:34,840
Perhaps?

444
00:34:36,210 --> 00:34:37,000
Perhaps.

445
00:34:51,300 --> 00:34:55,550
Eunuch, the Spider, the Master of Whisperers.

446
00:34:55,550 --> 00:34:57,360
Imp, Half-man.

447
00:35:00,280 --> 00:35:02,220
There are faster ways to kill yourself.

448
00:35:02,220 --> 00:35:03,420
Not for a coward.

449
00:35:04,150 --> 00:35:05,890
You are many things, my friend,

450
00:35:05,890 --> 00:35:07,290
but not a coward.

451
00:35:11,810 --> 00:35:13,870
You never told me why you set me free.

452
00:35:14,360 --> 00:35:15,790
Your brother asked me to.

453
00:35:17,390 --> 00:35:18,370
Could have said no.

454
00:35:19,020 --> 00:35:21,380
Refuse the Kingslayer? A dangerous proposition.

455
00:35:21,380 --> 00:35:23,410
Not as dangerous as releasing me.

456
00:35:23,860 --> 00:35:26,350
You risked your life, your position, everything.

457
00:35:26,350 --> 00:35:28,800
Why? You're not family. You owe me nothing.

458
00:35:29,340 --> 00:35:30,900
I didn't do it for you.

459
00:35:31,700 --> 00:35:33,730
I did it for the Seven Kingdoms.

460
00:35:33,780 --> 00:35:37,230
A drunken dwarf will never be the savior of the Seven Kingdoms.

461
00:35:37,230 --> 00:35:38,980
I don't believe in saviors.

462
00:35:39,210 --> 00:35:42,980
I believe men of talent have a part to play in the war to come.

463
00:35:44,240 --> 00:35:46,270
You're going to have to find another soldier.

464
00:35:47,320 --> 00:35:50,470
I'm done with Westeros and Westeros is done with me.

465
00:35:50,840 --> 00:35:53,240
You have many admirable qualities,

466
00:35:53,240 --> 00:35:54,990
self-pity is not one of them.

467
00:35:55,640 --> 00:35:57,130
Any fool with a bit of luck

468
00:35:57,130 --> 00:35:59,870
can find himself born into power.

469
00:36:00,480 --> 00:36:04,350
But earning it for yourself, that takes work.

470
00:36:05,090 --> 00:36:06,610
I'm not well-suited for work.

471
00:36:06,610 --> 00:36:07,620
I think you are.

472
00:36:07,990 --> 00:36:10,790
You have your father's instincts for politics.

473
00:36:10,810 --> 00:36:12,090
And you have compassion.

474
00:36:12,090 --> 00:36:14,000
Compassion? Yes.

475
00:36:15,420 --> 00:36:18,580
I killed my lover with my bare hands.

476
00:36:18,790 --> 00:36:22,010
I shot my own father with a crossbow.

477
00:36:22,010 --> 00:36:23,910
I never said you were perfect.

478
00:36:24,690 --> 00:36:27,490
What is it you want exactly?

479
00:36:27,950 --> 00:36:29,100
Peace.

480
00:36:30,100 --> 00:36:31,500
Prosperity.

481
00:36:31,950 --> 00:36:35,360
A land where the powerful do not prey on the powerless.

482
00:36:35,360 --> 00:36:37,470
Where the castles are made of gingerbread

483
00:36:37,480 --> 00:36:40,460
and the moats are filled with blackberry wine.

484
00:36:40,460 --> 00:36:42,700
The powerful have always preyed on the powerless.

485
00:36:42,700 --> 00:36:45,130
That's how they became powerful in the first place.

486
00:36:45,130 --> 00:36:46,340
Perhaps.

487
00:36:46,930 --> 00:36:50,140
And perhaps we've grown so used to horror,

488
00:36:50,310 --> 00:36:52,490
we assume there's no other way.

489
00:36:53,580 --> 00:36:55,770
If you sat on the Iron Throne,

490
00:36:55,780 --> 00:36:58,130
would you spread misery throughout the land?

491
00:36:58,130 --> 00:37:00,580
I will never sit on the Iron Throne.

492
00:37:00,860 --> 00:37:02,410
No, you won't.

493
00:37:02,740 --> 00:37:05,300
But you could help another climb those steps

494
00:37:05,300 --> 00:37:07,170
and take that seat.

495
00:37:07,990 --> 00:37:10,980
The Seven Kingdoms need someone stronger than Tommen,

496
00:37:10,980 --> 00:37:12,980
but gentler than Stannis.

497
00:37:13,190 --> 00:37:14,790
A monarch who can intimidate

498
00:37:14,790 --> 00:37:17,100
the high lords and inspire the people.

499
00:37:17,100 --> 00:37:19,860
A ruler loved by millions with a powerful army

500
00:37:19,860 --> 00:37:22,040
and the right family name.

501
00:37:22,040 --> 00:37:23,940
Good luck finding him.

502
00:37:25,030 --> 00:37:27,240
Who said anything about "Him"?

503
00:37:31,320 --> 00:37:33,330
You have a choice, my friend.

504
00:37:33,360 --> 00:37:35,860
You can stay here at Illyrio's palace

505
00:37:35,860 --> 00:37:37,820
and drink yourself to death,

506
00:37:38,180 --> 00:37:40,360
or you can ride with me to Meereen,

507
00:37:40,360 --> 00:37:41,780
meet Daenerys Targaryen,

508
00:37:41,780 --> 00:37:44,860
and decide if the world is worth fighting for.

509
00:37:47,050 --> 00:37:50,780
Can I drink myself to death on the road to Meereen?

510
00:38:01,270 --> 00:38:04,140
When did the Unsullied start patrolling the streets of Meereen?

511
00:38:04,150 --> 00:38:07,030
Looks like your friends haven't been behaving themselves.

512
00:38:09,930 --> 00:38:12,980
Our mission to Yunkai was a resounding success.

513
00:38:12,980 --> 00:38:15,380
The Wise Masters of Yunkai have agreed to cede power

514
00:38:15,380 --> 00:38:17,160
to a council of elders made up of

515
00:38:17,160 --> 00:38:19,820
both the freed men and the former slaveholders.

516
00:38:19,820 --> 00:38:22,890
All matters of consequence will be brought to you for review.

517
00:38:23,070 --> 00:38:24,200
Good.

518
00:38:24,730 --> 00:38:26,850
They did ask for some concessions.

519
00:38:27,380 --> 00:38:28,780
Concessions?

520
00:38:28,910 --> 00:38:31,110
Politics is the art of compromise, Your Grace.

521
00:38:31,110 --> 00:38:32,700
I'm not a politician.

522
00:38:32,700 --> 00:38:33,960
I'm a queen.

523
00:38:34,540 --> 00:38:35,610
Forgive me.

524
00:38:35,870 --> 00:38:37,240
You're right, of course.

525
00:38:37,240 --> 00:38:41,650
Still, it's easier to rule happy subjects than angry ones.

526
00:38:41,650 --> 00:38:43,890
I don't expect the Wise Masters to be happy.

527
00:38:43,890 --> 00:38:45,580
Slavery made them rich.

528
00:38:45,750 --> 00:38:47,080
I ended slavery.

529
00:38:47,080 --> 00:38:49,570
They do not ask for the return of slavery.

530
00:38:50,010 --> 00:38:52,990
They ask for the reopening of the fighting pits.

531
00:38:53,980 --> 00:38:55,430
The fighting pits?

532
00:38:55,480 --> 00:38:57,950
Where slaves fought slaves to the death?

533
00:38:57,950 --> 00:38:59,970
In the new world that you've brought to us,

534
00:38:59,970 --> 00:39:02,220
free men would fight free men.

535
00:39:03,680 --> 00:39:05,080
The pit fighters you liberated

536
00:39:05,080 --> 00:39:07,000
plead for this opportunity.

537
00:39:07,600 --> 00:39:09,550
Bring some here and ask them yourself.

538
00:39:09,550 --> 00:39:11,010
No fighting pits.

539
00:39:11,010 --> 00:39:12,550
Opening them would show the people of

540
00:39:12,550 --> 00:39:15,100
Yunkai and Meereen that you respect their traditions.

541
00:39:15,100 --> 00:39:18,020
I do not respect the tradition of human cockfighting.

542
00:39:18,020 --> 00:39:19,750
- If you-- - How many times must I say no

543
00:39:19,750 --> 00:39:21,480
before you understand?

544
00:39:23,490 --> 00:39:26,010
Whatever he wants from me, he's not going to get it.

545
00:39:26,320 --> 00:39:28,890
If he really believes I'm going to reopen the fighting pits...

546
00:39:28,890 --> 00:39:30,850
You should reopen the fighting pits.

547
00:39:32,550 --> 00:39:33,630
What?

548
00:39:34,280 --> 00:39:36,810
My mother was a whore. I told you that.

549
00:39:38,840 --> 00:39:40,880
She liked to drink pear brandy.

550
00:39:41,170 --> 00:39:42,540
The older she got,

551
00:39:42,820 --> 00:39:44,330
the less she made selling her body,

552
00:39:44,330 --> 00:39:46,000
the more she wanted to drink.

553
00:39:46,960 --> 00:39:49,960
So one day when I was 12, she sold me to a slaver

554
00:39:49,970 --> 00:39:51,900
she fucked the night before.

555
00:39:53,300 --> 00:39:54,490
I'm sorry.

556
00:39:54,990 --> 00:39:58,050
Why? I was a bad child.

557
00:39:58,060 --> 00:40:01,460
I wasn't big, but I was quick.

558
00:40:01,520 --> 00:40:02,910
And I loved to fight.

559
00:40:02,910 --> 00:40:04,800
So they sold me to a man in Tolos

560
00:40:04,800 --> 00:40:06,900
who trained fighters for the pits.

561
00:40:07,270 --> 00:40:09,830
I had my first match when I was 16.

562
00:40:09,930 --> 00:40:11,440
You were sold into slavery,

563
00:40:11,440 --> 00:40:12,750
forced to fight to the death

564
00:40:12,750 --> 00:40:14,160
for the amusement of the masters,

565
00:40:14,170 --> 00:40:16,090
and you're defending the fighting pits?

566
00:40:17,290 --> 00:40:20,200
I'm only here because of those pits.

567
00:40:20,200 --> 00:40:22,670
I learned to fight like a Dothraki screamer,

568
00:40:22,670 --> 00:40:25,260
a Norvoshi priest, a Westerosi knight.

569
00:40:25,260 --> 00:40:26,870
Soon I was famous.

570
00:40:26,870 --> 00:40:29,120
10,000 men and women screamed my name

571
00:40:29,120 --> 00:40:30,780
when I stepped into the pit.

572
00:40:30,790 --> 00:40:32,800
I made so much money for my master,

573
00:40:32,820 --> 00:40:35,070
he set me free when he died.

574
00:40:35,340 --> 00:40:37,440
I joined the Second Sons.

575
00:40:37,640 --> 00:40:39,000
And then I met you.

576
00:40:45,210 --> 00:40:46,600
You're the queen.

577
00:40:47,190 --> 00:40:49,780
Everyone's too afraid of you to speak truth.

578
00:40:50,040 --> 00:40:51,650
Everyone but me.

579
00:40:52,770 --> 00:40:56,350
You've made thousands of enemies all across the world.

580
00:40:56,350 --> 00:40:59,070
As soon as they see weakness,

581
00:40:59,080 --> 00:41:00,540
they'll attack.

582
00:41:01,210 --> 00:41:04,970
Show your strength here, now.

583
00:41:04,970 --> 00:41:07,570
That's why I have the Unsullied patrolling the streets.

584
00:41:09,650 --> 00:41:11,270
Anyone with a chest full of gold

585
00:41:11,280 --> 00:41:13,360
can buy an army of Unsullied.

586
00:41:13,360 --> 00:41:15,840
You're not the Mother of Unsullied.

587
00:41:16,910 --> 00:41:18,830
You're the Mother of Dragons.

588
00:41:25,720 --> 00:41:29,120
I don't want another child's bones dropped at my feet.

589
00:41:30,550 --> 00:41:32,670
No one's seen Drogon in weeks.

590
00:41:33,280 --> 00:41:35,900
For all I know, he's flown halfway across the world.

591
00:41:40,820 --> 00:41:42,480
I can't control them anymore.

592
00:41:44,510 --> 00:41:46,850
A dragon queen with no dragons

593
00:41:48,160 --> 00:41:49,420
is not a queen.

594
00:42:55,750 --> 00:42:57,000
Viserion?

595
00:42:59,940 --> 00:43:01,130
Rhaegal?

596
00:43:13,600 --> 00:43:15,470
Easy. Easy.

597
00:43:15,480 --> 00:43:16,550
Easy.

598
00:43:56,950 --> 00:43:58,320
So here we are.

599
00:43:59,050 --> 00:44:00,170
Here we are.

600
00:44:03,270 --> 00:44:05,780
When we first met, you were my prisoner.

601
00:44:06,790 --> 00:44:09,640
And now, for our last meeting...

602
00:44:12,140 --> 00:44:14,490
This doesn't have to be our last meeting.

603
00:44:14,490 --> 00:44:17,120
No, but it will be.

604
00:44:19,430 --> 00:44:21,130
You know what Stannis wants?

605
00:44:21,890 --> 00:44:23,770
He wants me to bend the knee.

606
00:44:24,510 --> 00:44:26,870
And he wants the free folk to fight for him.

607
00:44:27,950 --> 00:44:29,680
I'll give him this much,

608
00:44:29,760 --> 00:44:31,020
he's bold.

609
00:44:31,210 --> 00:44:33,010
Shouldn't a king be bold?

610
00:44:33,130 --> 00:44:34,390
Oh, aye.

611
00:44:35,340 --> 00:44:36,910
I respect him.

612
00:44:38,060 --> 00:44:39,550
If he gets what he wants,

613
00:44:39,550 --> 00:44:41,240
I expect he'll be a better ruler than

614
00:44:41,240 --> 00:44:44,680
the fools sitting on the Iron Throne the last hundred years.

615
00:44:44,890 --> 00:44:47,160
But I'll never serve him.

616
00:44:49,160 --> 00:44:50,660
You told me you weren't here to conquer.

617
00:44:50,660 --> 00:44:51,990
You told me your people have bled enough.

618
00:44:51,990 --> 00:44:53,020
That's right.

619
00:44:54,170 --> 00:44:56,750
I don't want them bleeding for Stannis Baratheon either.

620
00:44:56,750 --> 00:45:00,090
You spent your life convincing 90 clans to come together

621
00:45:00,090 --> 00:45:02,080
for the first time in history.

622
00:45:02,500 --> 00:45:04,340
Thenns and Hornfoots,

623
00:45:04,610 --> 00:45:07,150
the ice-river clans, even the giants.

624
00:45:07,770 --> 00:45:09,670
A life's work uniting them.

625
00:45:09,670 --> 00:45:11,210
You didn't do it for power.

626
00:45:11,710 --> 00:45:13,310
You didn't do it for glory.

627
00:45:14,240 --> 00:45:16,250
You brought them together to save them

628
00:45:16,260 --> 00:45:17,970
because none of them will survive the winter,

629
00:45:17,970 --> 00:45:19,570
not if they're north of the Wall.

630
00:45:19,570 --> 00:45:22,220
Isn't their survival more important than your pride?

631
00:45:22,220 --> 00:45:23,400
Pride?

632
00:45:25,980 --> 00:45:27,910
Fuck my pride.

633
00:45:30,380 --> 00:45:32,130
This isn't about that.

634
00:45:34,230 --> 00:45:38,070
Then bend the knee and save your people.

635
00:45:39,690 --> 00:45:43,070
They followed me because they respected me.

636
00:45:43,120 --> 00:45:44,860
Because they believed in me.

637
00:45:44,860 --> 00:45:47,230
The moment I kneel for a southern king, that's all gone.

638
00:45:47,230 --> 00:45:50,180
And how many tens of thousands are out there right now?

639
00:45:50,580 --> 00:45:53,430
How many women? How many children?

640
00:45:53,760 --> 00:45:56,380
And you won't go out and rescue them because why?

641
00:45:57,230 --> 00:45:59,450
You're afraid of looking afraid.

642
00:45:59,460 --> 00:46:02,390
Oh, I am afraid.

643
00:46:03,510 --> 00:46:05,240
No shame in that.

644
00:46:14,500 --> 00:46:15,790
How will they do it?

645
00:46:16,200 --> 00:46:17,340
Beheading?

646
00:46:18,470 --> 00:46:19,560
Hanging?

647
00:46:23,760 --> 00:46:25,380
They'll burn you alive.

648
00:46:30,200 --> 00:46:31,570
Bad way to go.

649
00:46:35,860 --> 00:46:37,300
I'll be honest with you.

650
00:46:37,660 --> 00:46:39,460
I don't want to die.

651
00:46:39,970 --> 00:46:41,360
And burnt to death,

652
00:46:41,470 --> 00:46:43,840
I don't want people to remember me like that,

653
00:46:43,840 --> 00:46:46,020
scorched and screaming.

654
00:46:46,810 --> 00:46:50,130
But it's better than betraying everything I believe.

655
00:46:50,780 --> 00:46:52,640
And what happens to your people?

656
00:46:53,110 --> 00:46:56,000
You preserve your dignity and die standing

657
00:46:56,480 --> 00:46:58,430
and they'll sing songs about you.

658
00:46:59,040 --> 00:47:01,110
You'd rather burn than kneel.

659
00:47:01,270 --> 00:47:02,720
The great hero.

660
00:47:04,250 --> 00:47:05,640
Until winter comes

661
00:47:05,980 --> 00:47:07,650
and the white walkers come for us all

662
00:47:07,660 --> 00:47:09,750
and there's no one left to sing.

663
00:47:13,090 --> 00:47:14,730
You're a good lad.

664
00:47:15,290 --> 00:47:17,320
Truly you are.

665
00:47:18,270 --> 00:47:20,070
But if you can't understand

666
00:47:20,070 --> 00:47:22,480
why I won't enlist my people

667
00:47:22,490 --> 00:47:24,190
in a foreigner's war,

668
00:47:25,320 --> 00:47:27,270
there's no point explaining.

669
00:47:43,770 --> 00:47:46,250
I think you're making a terrible mistake.

670
00:47:47,530 --> 00:47:50,060
The freedom to make my own mistakes

671
00:47:50,060 --> 00:47:51,860
was all I ever wanted.

672
00:49:01,680 --> 00:49:05,030
Mance Rayder, you've been called the King-beyond-the-Wall.

673
00:49:05,030 --> 00:49:07,090
Westeros only has one king.

674
00:49:08,240 --> 00:49:10,370
Bend the knee, I promise you mercy.

675
00:49:24,060 --> 00:49:25,430
Kneel and live.

676
00:49:33,590 --> 00:49:37,000
This was my home for many years.

677
00:49:39,140 --> 00:49:41,250
I wish you good fortune

678
00:49:41,430 --> 00:49:43,060
in the wars to come.

679
00:50:25,530 --> 00:50:27,320
We all must choose.

680
00:50:28,550 --> 00:50:29,960
Man or woman, 

681
00:50:30,230 --> 00:50:31,910
young or old,

682
00:50:32,010 --> 00:50:33,300
lord or peasant,

683
00:50:33,300 --> 00:50:35,220
our choices are the same.

684
00:50:35,390 --> 00:50:38,800
We choose light or we choose darkness.

685
00:50:39,180 --> 00:50:42,180
We choose good or we choose evil.

686
00:50:42,430 --> 00:50:46,990
We choose the true god or the false.

687
00:50:57,910 --> 00:50:59,250
Free folk,

688
00:51:00,160 --> 00:51:02,430
there is only one true king

689
00:51:02,540 --> 00:51:05,100
and his name is Stannis.

690
00:51:05,110 --> 00:51:07,500
Here stands your king of lies.

691
00:51:07,500 --> 00:51:10,830
Behold the fate of those who choose the darkness.

