2
00:00:02,660 --> 00:00:04,160
You have a choice, my friend.

3
00:00:04,160 --> 00:00:06,530
You can stay here at Illyrio's palace

4
00:00:06,530 --> 00:00:07,980
and drink yourself to death,

5
00:00:07,980 --> 00:00:10,050
or you can ride with me to Meereen,

6
00:00:10,050 --> 00:00:11,290
meet Daenerys Targaryen,

7
00:00:11,290 --> 00:00:14,410
and decide if the world is worth fighting for.

8
00:00:14,440 --> 00:00:16,280
You swore to find the Stark girls.

9
00:00:16,280 --> 00:00:19,430
I found Arya. She didn't want my protection.

10
00:00:20,440 --> 00:00:21,940
So where are we going?

11
00:00:21,950 --> 00:00:23,650
To a land so far from here,

12
00:00:23,650 --> 00:00:26,530
even Cersei Lannister can't get her hands on you.

13
00:00:28,870 --> 00:00:30,710
Myrcella is my only daughter.

14
00:00:30,710 --> 00:00:33,420
Do you really think I'll let you sell her like a common whore?

15
00:00:33,420 --> 00:00:35,310
Dorne is the safest place for her.

16
00:00:35,310 --> 00:00:36,620
She'll be a hostage.

17
00:00:36,620 --> 00:00:38,950
she was swimming in the Water Gardens.

18
00:00:38,950 --> 00:00:41,100
We don't hurt little girls in Dorne.

19
00:00:41,100 --> 00:00:43,350
Her mother misses her very much.

20
00:00:43,350 --> 00:00:45,890
I am the brother of Elia Martell.

21
00:00:45,890 --> 00:00:46,950
You raped my sister.

22
00:00:46,960 --> 00:00:47,880
You murdered her.

23
00:00:47,890 --> 00:00:50,640
You killed her children.

24
00:00:56,060 --> 00:00:57,290
The Sons of the Harpy?

25
00:00:57,290 --> 00:00:58,770
They've never killed before.

26
00:00:58,910 --> 00:01:00,320
It was only a matter of time, Your Grace.

27
00:01:00,320 --> 00:01:02,240
And I did not take up residence in this pyramid

28
00:01:02,240 --> 00:01:05,120
so I could watch the city below decline into chaos.

29
00:01:05,120 --> 00:01:08,360
Find the men who did this and bring them to me.

30
00:01:08,980 --> 00:01:10,220
You know what Stannis wants?

31
00:01:10,220 --> 00:01:11,600
He wants me to bend the knee.

32
00:01:11,600 --> 00:01:13,300
And he wants the free folk to fight for him.

33
00:01:13,300 --> 00:01:15,200
But I'll never serve him.

34
00:01:22,890 --> 00:01:25,170
If the day comes when you must find me again,

35
00:01:25,170 --> 00:01:27,080
just give that coin to any man from Braavos

36
00:01:27,080 --> 00:01:28,230
and say these words to him,

37
00:01:28,230 --> 00:01:29,700
Valar Morghulis.

38
00:01:29,700 --> 00:01:31,240
Valar dohaeris.

39
00:01:31,240 --> 00:01:32,280
I'm going home.

40
00:01:32,280 --> 00:01:34,200
- Where's home? - Braavos.

41
00:03:36,980 --> 00:03:39,880
In the old times,  whenever Braavos stood in danger,

42
00:03:40,920 --> 00:03:44,750
the Titan would step with fire in his eyes.

43
00:03:44,750 --> 00:03:47,840
He'd wade into the sea and smash the enemies.

44
00:03:49,200 --> 00:03:50,740
He's a statue.

45
00:03:55,890 --> 00:03:59,500
Don't be afraid. He's announcing our arrival.

46
00:04:01,780 --> 00:04:03,040
I'm not afraid.

47
00:05:11,920 --> 00:05:13,570
The House of Black and White.

48
00:05:14,380 --> 00:05:17,220
This is where you'll find the man you seek.

49
00:05:22,840 --> 00:05:24,590
Here I leave you.

50
00:05:32,610 --> 00:05:33,880
Thank you for bringing me.

51
00:05:34,380 --> 00:05:36,480
Any man of Braavos would have done the same.

52
00:05:39,180 --> 00:05:41,940
- Valar morghulis. - Valar dohaeris.

53
00:06:17,790 --> 00:06:18,740
Hello.

54
00:06:22,650 --> 00:06:24,200
Valar morghulis.

55
00:06:35,120 --> 00:06:36,960
Jaqen H'ghar gave me this.

56
00:06:41,070 --> 00:06:44,640
- No one here by that name. - Please!

57
00:06:45,620 --> 00:06:48,730
I've crossed the narrow sea. I have nowhere else to go.

58
00:06:48,730 --> 00:06:52,140
- You have everywhere else to go. - But wait!

59
00:07:12,800 --> 00:07:13,810
Cersei...

60
00:07:15,040 --> 00:07:16,130
Walder Frey...

61
00:07:17,690 --> 00:07:18,860
The Mountain...

62
00:07:20,520 --> 00:07:21,870
Meryn Trant.

63
00:07:23,620 --> 00:07:24,770
Cersei...

64
00:07:26,710 --> 00:07:27,990
Walder Frey...

65
00:07:29,540 --> 00:07:30,790
The Mountain...

66
00:07:32,860 --> 00:07:34,140
Meryn Trant.

67
00:07:34,520 --> 00:07:35,420
Cersei...

68
00:07:35,800 --> 00:07:36,890
Walder Frey...

69
00:07:37,360 --> 00:07:38,370
The Mountain...

70
00:07:39,820 --> 00:07:40,890
Meryn Trant.

71
00:07:42,930 --> 00:07:43,940
Cersei...

72
00:07:44,700 --> 00:07:45,770
Walder Frey...

73
00:07:46,370 --> 00:07:47,450
The Mountain...

74
00:07:48,130 --> 00:07:49,250
Meryn Trant.

75
00:07:50,380 --> 00:07:51,450
Cersei...

76
00:07:53,010 --> 00:07:54,100
Walder Frey...

77
00:07:55,970 --> 00:07:57,050
The Mountain...

78
00:07:59,110 --> 00:08:00,290
Meryn Trant...

79
00:08:31,800 --> 00:08:33,660
Must be good food if it's crowded.

80
00:08:38,950 --> 00:08:39,860
Ale?

81
00:08:47,670 --> 00:08:48,620
Ale?

82
00:08:57,100 --> 00:09:00,190
Before we left, a maester gave you a raven's scroll.

83
00:09:02,840 --> 00:09:05,280
You are becoming an observant young lady.

84
00:09:05,280 --> 00:09:07,980
My mother used to say "dark wings, dark words".

85
00:09:07,980 --> 00:09:11,590
An old saying. Inaccurate in this case.

86
00:09:14,670 --> 00:09:16,050
So it's good news.

87
00:09:16,280 --> 00:09:18,820
My marriage proposal has been accepted.

88
00:09:18,830 --> 00:09:21,750
I thought you still mourned the death of my beloved Aunt Lysa.

89
00:09:21,750 --> 00:09:24,500
- Ale? - I'll have some.

90
00:09:28,800 --> 00:09:29,770
My Lady...

91
00:09:31,130 --> 00:09:34,040
- What is it? - Sansa Stark. Don't look!

92
00:09:35,560 --> 00:09:36,490
You sure?

93
00:09:36,490 --> 00:09:38,010
She's dyed her hair, but it's her.

94
00:09:38,010 --> 00:09:39,700
She's sitting with Petyr Baelish.

95
00:09:39,710 --> 00:09:40,840
Littlefinger?

96
00:09:40,840 --> 00:09:42,520
A bunch of knights with them.

97
00:09:42,520 --> 00:09:44,560
A bunch? What's a bunch, Podrick? Six? Twenty?

98
00:09:44,560 --> 00:09:46,450
Ten, I think. Too many.

99
00:09:46,840 --> 00:09:47,950
My Lady, I don't think this is the right...

100
00:09:47,950 --> 00:09:49,570
Ready the horses!

101
00:09:49,570 --> 00:09:51,170
We only have one horse.

102
00:09:51,170 --> 00:09:52,790
Find more!

103
00:09:58,890 --> 00:10:00,170
Do you like the taste?

104
00:10:00,780 --> 00:10:02,680
Don't see what all the fuss is about.

105
00:10:03,460 --> 00:10:05,930
Why do men love it so much?

106
00:10:05,930 --> 00:10:08,090
It gives some men courage.

107
00:10:08,090 --> 00:10:09,800
Does it give you courage?

108
00:10:12,940 --> 00:10:14,080
That's far enough.

109
00:10:15,870 --> 00:10:17,170
Lord Baelish.

110
00:10:17,670 --> 00:10:18,820
Lady Sansa.

111
00:10:19,290 --> 00:10:21,230
My name is Brienne of Tarth.

112
00:10:21,230 --> 00:10:23,750
We've met with Renly Baratheon.

113
00:10:24,580 --> 00:10:26,180
What did he say about you?

114
00:10:26,840 --> 00:10:27,730
He said,

115
00:10:28,950 --> 00:10:31,830
your loyalty came free of charge.

116
00:10:32,980 --> 00:10:35,800
Someone appears to have paid quite a bit for it since then.

117
00:10:49,360 --> 00:10:50,660
Lady Sansa,

118
00:10:52,130 --> 00:10:54,010
before your mother's death,

119
00:10:54,010 --> 00:10:55,860
I was her sworn sword.

120
00:10:56,540 --> 00:10:59,860
I gave my word I will find you and protect you.

121
00:10:59,860 --> 00:11:02,720
I will shield your back and keep your counsel,

122
00:11:02,720 --> 00:11:05,100
and give my life for yours if need be.

123
00:11:05,560 --> 00:11:08,830
I swear it by the Old Gods and the New.

124
00:11:09,860 --> 00:11:11,890
Please, lady Brienne.

125
00:11:11,890 --> 00:11:13,570
No need for such formality.

126
00:11:14,170 --> 00:11:16,380
You were Catelyn Stark's sworn sword.

127
00:11:16,380 --> 00:11:18,580
- I was. - Strange.

128
00:11:18,580 --> 00:11:19,890
I knew Cat from the time we were children.

129
00:11:19,890 --> 00:11:21,170
She never mentioned you.

130
00:11:21,990 --> 00:11:23,840
It was after Renly's murder.

131
00:11:23,840 --> 00:11:25,300
Ah, yes.

132
00:11:25,300 --> 00:11:27,090
You were accused of killing him.

133
00:11:27,090 --> 00:11:28,510
I tried to save him.

134
00:11:28,510 --> 00:11:31,810
- But you were accused. - By men who did not see what happened.

135
00:11:31,820 --> 00:11:33,320
And what did happen?

136
00:11:38,070 --> 00:11:39,810
He was murdered by a shadow.

137
00:11:40,360 --> 00:11:43,440
A shadow with the face of Stannis Baratheon.

138
00:11:43,440 --> 00:11:44,670
A shadow?

139
00:11:46,760 --> 00:11:48,060
With the face...

140
00:11:50,760 --> 00:11:53,300
This woman swore to protect Renly,

141
00:11:53,300 --> 00:11:54,490
she failed.

142
00:11:54,490 --> 00:11:56,360
She swore to protect your mother,

143
00:11:56,780 --> 00:11:58,310
she failed.

144
00:11:58,310 --> 00:12:01,830
Why would I want somebody with your history of failure guarding Lady Sansa?

145
00:12:01,830 --> 00:12:03,900
Why should you have any say in her affairs?

146
00:12:03,900 --> 00:12:05,670
Because I am her uncle.

147
00:12:05,670 --> 00:12:09,440
I married her Aunt Lysa shortly before my beloved's untimely death.

148
00:12:09,440 --> 00:12:12,220
We're family now  and you are an outsider.

149
00:12:12,220 --> 00:12:13,370
Forgive me, Lady Brienne.

150
00:12:13,370 --> 00:12:16,570
But experience has made me wary of outsiders.

151
00:12:16,570 --> 00:12:18,030
Lady Sansa...

152
00:12:18,030 --> 00:12:20,160
- if we can have a word alone... - No.

153
00:12:20,640 --> 00:12:21,910
Please, my Lady, if I I could explain...

154
00:12:21,910 --> 00:12:23,810
I saw you at Joffrey's wedding...

155
00:12:23,810 --> 00:12:25,300
bowing to the king.

156
00:12:25,310 --> 00:12:27,220
Neither of us wanted to be there.

157
00:12:28,770 --> 00:12:31,860
- Sometimes we don't have a choice. - And sometimes we do.

158
00:12:33,730 --> 00:12:35,100
You should leave.

159
00:12:36,620 --> 00:12:39,220
We don't want our new friend wandering the countryside alone.

160
00:12:39,220 --> 00:12:41,670
The roads in these parts aren't safe.

161
00:12:41,680 --> 00:12:42,890
Why don't you stay?

162
00:12:52,120 --> 00:12:54,180
The man asked you to stay--

163
00:13:41,730 --> 00:13:43,920
- Stop! Stop! - After him!

164
00:13:45,350 --> 00:13:46,430
Podrick!

165
00:13:47,980 --> 00:13:49,030
Hold on to her.

166
00:14:24,160 --> 00:14:27,090
Stop, stop, stop, stop! Stop!

167
00:14:30,550 --> 00:14:32,310
That's a good boy. Come on.

168
00:14:32,310 --> 00:14:33,260
Come on!

169
00:14:35,690 --> 00:14:37,090
No, no, no, stop!

170
00:14:57,560 --> 00:14:59,190
Guess that means you're unarmed.

171
00:15:00,430 --> 00:15:01,920
Down! Podrick down!

172
00:15:21,670 --> 00:15:22,660
Podrick?

173
00:15:23,480 --> 00:15:24,590
Yes, my Lady?

174
00:15:25,200 --> 00:15:26,440
You can stand now.

175
00:15:27,240 --> 00:15:28,300
Yes, my Lady.

176
00:15:32,520 --> 00:15:33,670
Sansa Stark?

177
00:15:34,930 --> 00:15:37,040
Wary of strangers, as she should be.

178
00:15:37,330 --> 00:15:40,060
I saw her riding on the east road with Littlefinger.

179
00:15:40,060 --> 00:15:42,070
- We'll follow them. - My Lady...

180
00:15:42,510 --> 00:15:44,960
if both Stark girls refused your service,

181
00:15:45,620 --> 00:15:47,580
maybe you're released from your vow.

182
00:15:47,580 --> 00:15:49,420
I swore to their mother I would protect those girls.

183
00:15:49,420 --> 00:15:50,680
But if they don't want your protection.

184
00:15:50,680 --> 00:15:52,580
Do you think she's safe with Littlefinger?

185
00:15:55,560 --> 00:15:56,570
No, my Lady.

186
00:15:57,140 --> 00:15:58,260
Get your horse.

187
00:16:08,260 --> 00:16:09,650
A summons from the Queen.

188
00:16:28,370 --> 00:16:30,620
There are only two like it in the world.

189
00:16:31,520 --> 00:16:33,920
The one I'm wearing,  the one I gave to Myrcella.

190
00:16:34,330 --> 00:16:35,530
It's a threat.

191
00:16:35,540 --> 00:16:37,130
Of course it's a threat.

192
00:16:37,730 --> 00:16:39,400
Our daughter is alone in Dorne

193
00:16:39,400 --> 00:16:42,180
surrounded by people who hate our family.

194
00:16:43,080 --> 00:16:44,340
It's a threat.

195
00:16:46,950 --> 00:16:47,780
No note?

196
00:16:47,780 --> 00:16:51,100
They blame us for the death of Oberyn and his sister,

197
00:16:51,100 --> 00:16:54,150
and every other tragedy that's befallen their cursed country.

198
00:16:54,150 --> 00:16:56,920
I will burn their cities to the ground if they touch her.

199
00:16:56,920 --> 00:16:58,770
- Softer. - What?

200
00:16:58,770 --> 00:16:59,710
Not so loud.

201
00:16:59,710 --> 00:17:00,690
Our daughter is in danger

202
00:17:00,690 --> 00:17:02,620
and you're worried I am speaking too loudly?

203
00:17:02,620 --> 00:17:05,220
The world can't know she's our daughter.

204
00:17:06,420 --> 00:17:08,800
Then don't call her your daughter.

205
00:17:08,800 --> 00:17:10,060
You've never been a father to her.

206
00:17:10,060 --> 00:17:11,900
If I was a father to any of my children,

207
00:17:11,900 --> 00:17:13,110
they'd be stoned in the street.

208
00:17:13,120 --> 00:17:14,760
And what has your caution brought?

209
00:17:16,540 --> 00:17:19,150
Our eldest child murdered at his own wedding,

210
00:17:19,620 --> 00:17:21,990
our only daughter shipped off to Dorne,

211
00:17:23,250 --> 00:17:27,370
our baby boy set to marry that smirking whore from Highgarden!

212
00:17:36,650 --> 00:17:37,920
I'm going to make things better.

213
00:17:37,920 --> 00:17:39,290
You've never made anything better.

214
00:17:39,290 --> 00:17:40,430
I'm going to Dorne.

215
00:17:40,990 --> 00:17:42,650
And I'm bringing our daughter home.

216
00:17:43,940 --> 00:17:47,320
You can't just ask Prince Doran to give her back.

217
00:17:47,810 --> 00:17:49,670
She's promised to his son.

218
00:17:49,670 --> 00:17:51,680
I'm not going to ask him anything.

219
00:17:52,290 --> 00:17:54,350
You go down there with an army, it's an act of war.

220
00:17:54,350 --> 00:17:55,330
No army.

221
00:17:56,240 --> 00:17:57,730
Do you know where they're keeping her?

222
00:18:01,400 --> 00:18:03,600
Oberyn mentioned the Water Gardens.

223
00:18:03,600 --> 00:18:04,640
I'll find her.

224
00:18:07,900 --> 00:18:09,370
Is there anything else, Your Grace?

225
00:18:13,040 --> 00:18:14,290
You're going to Dorne.

226
00:18:15,780 --> 00:18:17,240
A one-handed man,

227
00:18:18,300 --> 00:18:19,180
alone?

228
00:18:20,490 --> 00:18:22,030
Never said I was going alone.

229
00:18:30,420 --> 00:18:33,080
No sunfloweres. I don't like yellow.

230
00:18:33,080 --> 00:18:35,360
Roses are very nice, definitely roses.

231
00:18:35,370 --> 00:18:37,010
And music. I adore music.

232
00:18:37,010 --> 00:18:38,330
But no flutes.

233
00:18:38,330 --> 00:18:39,310
I hate flutes.

234
00:18:39,310 --> 00:18:41,300
We can have a harp, if you like, but no flutes.

235
00:18:41,300 --> 00:18:42,230
Then there's the food.

236
00:18:42,230 --> 00:18:44,430
The food is the most important thing, don't you agree?

237
00:18:44,430 --> 00:18:46,340
We're going to need pigeon pies.

238
00:18:46,340 --> 00:18:48,890
That's what they eat in the capital, don't they?

239
00:18:50,130 --> 00:18:51,140
Don't they?

240
00:18:53,090 --> 00:18:54,140
Don't who?

241
00:18:54,140 --> 00:18:57,140
People eat pigeon pie in the capital.

242
00:18:58,290 --> 00:19:00,110
They certainly do, my dear.

243
00:19:00,110 --> 00:19:01,290
They certainly do.

244
00:19:02,650 --> 00:19:04,410
It's a fine place, isn't it?

245
00:19:05,120 --> 00:19:06,680
A fine place.

246
00:19:07,170 --> 00:19:10,790
I never thought I'd end up settling down in a place like this.

247
00:19:11,470 --> 00:19:12,680
You won't.

248
00:19:14,130 --> 00:19:14,970
Pardon?

249
00:19:14,970 --> 00:19:16,880
We won't get to live at Stokeworth.

250
00:19:16,880 --> 00:19:20,390
When mother dies, my sister gets the castle because she's older.

251
00:19:20,390 --> 00:19:21,870
She hates me.

252
00:19:21,870 --> 00:19:23,580
She calls me mean names and sometimes

253
00:19:23,580 --> 00:19:26,550
even still she pulls my hair when mother's not looking.

254
00:19:28,580 --> 00:19:29,810
You know what I think?

255
00:19:30,670 --> 00:19:32,860
I think you're a good person.

256
00:19:32,870 --> 00:19:35,170
And your sister is a mean person.

257
00:19:35,170 --> 00:19:36,160
She is.

258
00:19:38,730 --> 00:19:40,340
I've been all over the world,

259
00:19:40,340 --> 00:19:42,480
and if there's one thing I've learned,

260
00:19:42,480 --> 00:19:44,480
it's that meanness comes around.

261
00:19:45,710 --> 00:19:47,080
People like your sister,

262
00:19:47,780 --> 00:19:50,240
they always get what's coming to them eventually.

263
00:19:51,330 --> 00:19:52,710
One way or another.

264
00:19:56,400 --> 00:19:57,630
Who's that?

265
00:20:00,840 --> 00:20:02,660
Jaime fucking Lannister.

266
00:20:04,720 --> 00:20:05,800
Ser Jaime?

267
00:20:05,800 --> 00:20:07,260
Ser Bronn of the Blackwater.

268
00:20:08,790 --> 00:20:11,460
I was very sorry to hear about your father.

269
00:20:11,460 --> 00:20:12,390
Thank you.

270
00:20:13,210 --> 00:20:15,780
This is my betrothed Lollys.

271
00:20:17,510 --> 00:20:18,540
A pleasure.

272
00:20:21,550 --> 00:20:22,760
Run along, love.

273
00:20:29,490 --> 00:20:31,500
Beautiful young bride you've chosen.

274
00:20:32,230 --> 00:20:33,840
When were you planning on getting married?

275
00:20:33,840 --> 00:20:35,130
Just get on with it.

276
00:20:35,260 --> 00:20:36,280
On with what?

277
00:20:36,280 --> 00:20:37,600
What you're here for.

278
00:20:37,920 --> 00:20:39,040
There's no way this little visit

279
00:20:39,040 --> 00:20:41,050
could possibly mean anything good for me.

280
00:20:41,050 --> 00:20:42,500
It's very good for you.

281
00:20:55,000 --> 00:20:57,790
Lollys will be marrying Ser Willis Bracken.

282
00:20:59,070 --> 00:21:01,100
We've made a deal, your sister and I.

283
00:21:01,930 --> 00:21:03,580
I would have advised against that.

284
00:21:03,580 --> 00:21:04,630
How is this good for me?

285
00:21:04,630 --> 00:21:05,610
Because you're going to come with me

286
00:21:05,620 --> 00:21:07,600
and help me with something important.

287
00:21:07,830 --> 00:21:09,200
And when we return,

288
00:21:09,210 --> 00:21:13,170
I'm going to give you a much better girl and a much better castle.

289
00:21:15,860 --> 00:21:17,430
Return from where?

290
00:21:18,120 --> 00:21:20,530
As far south as south goes.

291
00:21:44,880 --> 00:21:46,860
You are my queen.

292
00:21:55,650 --> 00:21:58,050
The prince does not wish to be disturbed.

293
00:21:58,160 --> 00:21:59,550
Remove yourself from my path

294
00:21:59,550 --> 00:22:01,650
or I'll take that long axe and I'll shove it up your...

295
00:22:01,650 --> 00:22:02,740
Captain.

296
00:22:04,660 --> 00:22:06,050
let her pass.

297
00:22:10,370 --> 00:22:12,050
Your brother was murdered

298
00:22:12,680 --> 00:22:14,990
and you sit here in the Water Gardens

299
00:22:14,990 --> 00:22:17,240
staring at the sky and doing nothing.

300
00:22:17,240 --> 00:22:20,260
Oberyn was slain during a trial by combat.

301
00:22:20,260 --> 00:22:21,440
By law, that is no murder.

302
00:22:21,440 --> 00:22:24,070
- Your brother... - You don't have to remind me.

303
00:22:24,070 --> 00:22:27,360
He was my brother long before he was anything to you.

304
00:22:27,640 --> 00:22:28,890
What will you do about his death?

305
00:22:28,890 --> 00:22:31,730
I will bury him. I will mourn for him.

306
00:22:31,730 --> 00:22:32,710
And then?

307
00:22:32,710 --> 00:22:34,080
You would have me go to war.

308
00:22:34,080 --> 00:22:35,630
The whole country would have you go to war.

309
00:22:35,630 --> 00:22:38,840
Then we are lucky the whole country does not decide.

310
00:22:41,060 --> 00:22:42,690
The Sand Snakes are with me.

311
00:22:42,830 --> 00:22:44,490
They have the love of their people.

312
00:22:44,530 --> 00:22:45,760
They will avenge their father

313
00:22:45,770 --> 00:22:49,940
while you sit here in your chair doing nothing.

314
00:22:54,210 --> 00:22:55,700
Oberyn is dead.

315
00:22:56,660 --> 00:22:59,660
And this Lannister girl skips about the Water Gardens

316
00:22:59,660 --> 00:23:02,910
eating our food, breathing our air.

317
00:23:03,870 --> 00:23:05,510
How many of your brothers and sisters

318
00:23:05,520 --> 00:23:06,960
do they have to kill?

319
00:23:08,200 --> 00:23:09,430
Let me have her.

320
00:23:11,520 --> 00:23:15,660
Let me send her to Cersei one finger at a time.

321
00:23:16,860 --> 00:23:18,450
I loved my brother.

322
00:23:19,040 --> 00:23:21,470
And you made him very happy.

323
00:23:21,480 --> 00:23:24,260
For that, you will always have a place in my heart.

324
00:23:25,490 --> 00:23:29,520
But we do not mutilate little girls for vengeance.

325
00:23:29,890 --> 00:23:31,020
Not here.

326
00:23:31,650 --> 00:23:33,160
Not while I rule.

327
00:23:34,590 --> 00:23:36,330
And how long will that be?

328
00:23:52,750 --> 00:23:54,860
The Unsullied are too conspicuous.

329
00:23:55,280 --> 00:23:57,590
Anyone can see them coming from a mile off.

330
00:23:58,100 --> 00:24:00,380
'Course you haven't found any Sons of the Harpy.

331
00:24:00,810 --> 00:24:02,100
You haven't, have you?

332
00:24:04,430 --> 00:24:06,700
My Second Sons, on the other hand,

333
00:24:07,300 --> 00:24:11,630
they drink, they whore, fight in the streets,

334
00:24:12,140 --> 00:24:13,530
they blend in.

335
00:24:13,560 --> 00:24:15,690
They overhear things in taverns.

336
00:24:16,010 --> 00:24:19,400
Follow people from the taverns to nice, quiet alleys.

337
00:24:19,840 --> 00:24:23,900
Break a few fingers, overhear a few more things.

338
00:24:25,170 --> 00:24:26,490
Before you know it...

339
00:24:46,420 --> 00:24:47,700
No one here.

340
00:24:48,670 --> 00:24:49,850
We go.

341
00:24:50,140 --> 00:24:51,290
In a hurry?

342
00:24:51,710 --> 00:24:52,690
You're afraid?

343
00:24:52,700 --> 00:24:54,890
Unsullied fear nothing.

344
00:24:55,980 --> 00:24:57,110
Right.

345
00:24:57,550 --> 00:24:58,900
That's your problem.

346
00:24:59,130 --> 00:25:01,530
You understood fear once, long ago,

347
00:25:01,530 --> 00:25:03,070
but you've forgotten what it means.

348
00:25:04,080 --> 00:25:05,930
Someone who has forgotten fear

349
00:25:06,690 --> 00:25:08,330
has forgotten how to hide.

350
00:25:17,380 --> 00:25:19,230
Fear is useful that way.

351
00:25:43,950 --> 00:25:45,360
Sons of the Harpy...

352
00:25:45,360 --> 00:25:47,560
they want to put a collar back on my neck.

353
00:25:47,820 --> 00:25:50,000
On all of our necks. Please, Your Grace...

354
00:25:50,000 --> 00:25:52,400
- you must kill him. - It would send a message.

355
00:25:52,470 --> 00:25:54,640
I think you should exercise restraint...

356
00:25:54,640 --> 00:25:55,730
- Your Grace. - Why?

357
00:25:55,730 --> 00:25:57,910
Well, for one thing, he may have valuable information.

358
00:25:57,910 --> 00:26:01,050
Well, the Son of the Harpy has no more valuable information.

359
00:26:01,050 --> 00:26:02,190
How do you know that?

360
00:26:02,190 --> 00:26:03,940
Because I questioned him.

361
00:26:04,650 --> 00:26:07,070
And the information you did get... he is young and poor

362
00:26:07,070 --> 00:26:08,100
He is born free.

363
00:26:08,100 --> 00:26:09,340
Why should he want to bring back slavery?

364
00:26:09,340 --> 00:26:10,390
What did it do for him?

365
00:26:10,390 --> 00:26:11,850
Perhaps the only thing that gave him pride

366
00:26:11,850 --> 00:26:13,760
was knowing that there was someone lower than he was.

367
00:26:13,760 --> 00:26:15,070
They pay him.

368
00:26:15,140 --> 00:26:17,380
Great families, afraid to do a thing.

369
00:26:17,380 --> 00:26:18,680
They pay poor men to do it for them.

370
00:26:18,680 --> 00:26:19,770
And how do you know this?

371
00:26:19,770 --> 00:26:21,560
- Everyone know this. - I don't know it.

372
00:26:21,560 --> 00:26:22,820
And I'm the head of a great family.

373
00:26:22,820 --> 00:26:25,310
We do not know what this man did or didn't do.

374
00:26:25,310 --> 00:26:27,440
Give him a trial at least.

375
00:26:27,450 --> 00:26:28,820
A fair trial.

376
00:26:29,630 --> 00:26:31,170
Show all the citizens of Meereen

377
00:26:31,170 --> 00:26:33,630
that you are better than those who would depose you.

378
00:26:33,740 --> 00:26:34,970
Teach them a better way.

379
00:26:34,970 --> 00:26:37,600
I do not know the place from where old ser comes.

380
00:26:37,600 --> 00:26:40,330
Things maybe are different there, I hope.

381
00:26:40,900 --> 00:26:42,840
But here in Meereen,

382
00:26:42,840 --> 00:26:44,220
before Daenerys Stormborn

383
00:26:44,220 --> 00:26:45,520
they own us.

384
00:26:45,960 --> 00:26:48,010
So we learn much about them...

385
00:26:48,300 --> 00:26:49,840
or we do not live long.

386
00:26:50,450 --> 00:26:52,470
They teach me what they are.

387
00:26:52,930 --> 00:26:55,210
Mercy, fair trial...

388
00:26:55,210 --> 00:26:57,030
these mean nothing to them.

389
00:26:57,030 --> 00:26:59,170
All they understand is blood.

390
00:27:04,510 --> 00:27:06,080
Thank you all for your counsel.

391
00:27:15,120 --> 00:27:16,170
Your Grace...

392
00:27:16,170 --> 00:27:17,680
a word, please, I beg you.

393
00:27:17,680 --> 00:27:18,700
About what?

394
00:27:18,700 --> 00:27:20,080
About your father.

395
00:27:20,350 --> 00:27:22,380
- About the Mad King. - The Mad King?

396
00:27:22,380 --> 00:27:24,220
You're here to remind me of my enemies' lies?

397
00:27:24,220 --> 00:27:25,350
Consider me reminded.

398
00:27:25,350 --> 00:27:26,490
Your Grace...

399
00:27:27,360 --> 00:27:29,100
I served in his Kingsguard.

400
00:27:29,850 --> 00:27:31,860
I was at his side from the first.

401
00:27:31,860 --> 00:27:33,460
Your enemies did not lie.

402
00:27:35,730 --> 00:27:36,840
Go on.

403
00:27:38,930 --> 00:27:41,450
When the people rose in revolt against him,

404
00:27:41,790 --> 00:27:44,300
your father set their towns and castles aflame.

405
00:27:45,340 --> 00:27:47,860
He murdered sons in front of their fathers.

406
00:27:48,760 --> 00:27:51,100
He burned men alive with wildfire

407
00:27:51,100 --> 00:27:52,890
and laughed as they screamed,

408
00:27:54,030 --> 00:27:56,410
and his efforts to stamp out dissent

409
00:27:57,490 --> 00:28:00,250
led to a rebellion that killed every Targaryen...

410
00:28:00,660 --> 00:28:01,960
except two.

411
00:28:03,120 --> 00:28:04,460
I'm not my father.

412
00:28:04,690 --> 00:28:07,240
No, Your Grace, thank the gods.

413
00:28:08,240 --> 00:28:12,170
But the Mad King gave his enemies the justice he thought they deserved.

414
00:28:12,350 --> 00:28:15,060
And each time, it made him feel powerful

415
00:28:15,200 --> 00:28:16,420
and right.

416
00:28:17,480 --> 00:28:18,930
until the very end.

417
00:28:23,910 --> 00:28:25,950
I will not have the Son of the Harpy executed

418
00:28:25,950 --> 00:28:27,350
without a fair trial.

419
00:28:31,420 --> 00:28:32,530
Your Grace.

420
00:28:42,640 --> 00:28:43,810
There's a bug.

421
00:28:43,920 --> 00:28:45,460
Yes, best be careful.

422
00:28:45,460 --> 00:28:48,270
You might accidentally consume some solid food.

423
00:28:48,300 --> 00:28:50,250
When I agreed to come with you,

424
00:28:50,260 --> 00:28:53,080
did I misrepresent my intentions?

425
00:28:57,330 --> 00:28:58,350
Besides,

426
00:28:59,030 --> 00:29:02,460
what else is there for me to do inside this fucking box?

427
00:29:02,460 --> 00:29:04,600
- You don't like it? - I want to take a walk.

428
00:29:04,600 --> 00:29:05,650
You can't.

429
00:29:05,650 --> 00:29:08,950
Cersei has offered a lordship to the man who brings her your head.

430
00:29:08,950 --> 00:29:10,890
She ought to offer her cunt.

431
00:29:11,360 --> 00:29:13,740
Best part of her for the best part of me.

432
00:29:14,400 --> 00:29:17,760
Well, I suppose a box is as good a place for me as anywhere.

433
00:29:18,380 --> 00:29:21,090
Are we really going to spend the entire road to Volantis

434
00:29:21,090 --> 00:29:23,220
talking about the futility of everything.

435
00:29:23,220 --> 00:29:24,980
You're right, there's no point.

436
00:29:25,490 --> 00:29:27,400
The road to Volantis?

437
00:29:27,490 --> 00:29:30,410
You said we were going to Meereen. What's in Volantis?

438
00:29:30,410 --> 00:29:31,960
The road to Meereen.

439
00:29:31,960 --> 00:29:35,650
And what do you hope to find at the end on the road to Meereen?

440
00:29:35,660 --> 00:29:37,740
I told you. A ruler.

441
00:29:37,740 --> 00:29:39,620
We've already got a ruler.

442
00:29:39,940 --> 00:29:42,360
Everywhere has already got a ruler.

443
00:29:42,660 --> 00:29:45,380
Every pile of shit on the side of every road

444
00:29:45,380 --> 00:29:47,350
has someone's banner hanging from it.

445
00:29:47,350 --> 00:29:49,070
You were quite good, you know,

446
00:29:49,700 --> 00:29:50,960
at ruling.

447
00:29:51,650 --> 00:29:53,910
During your brief tenure as Hand.

448
00:29:54,380 --> 00:29:56,070
I didn't rule, I was a servant.

449
00:29:56,070 --> 00:29:58,560
Still, a man of talent.

450
00:29:58,560 --> 00:30:00,060
Managed to kill a lot of people?

451
00:30:00,060 --> 00:30:04,150
Yes, but you showed great promise in other areas as well.

452
00:30:07,380 --> 00:30:09,590
She wanted me to leave King's Landing.

453
00:30:10,610 --> 00:30:11,940
She begged me.

454
00:30:12,460 --> 00:30:13,750
I wouldn't go.

455
00:30:14,060 --> 00:30:15,100
Why?

456
00:30:15,100 --> 00:30:16,580
'Cause I liked it.

457
00:30:17,850 --> 00:30:19,030
power...

458
00:30:19,690 --> 00:30:21,110
even as a servant.

459
00:30:21,710 --> 00:30:23,400
People follow leaders

460
00:30:24,800 --> 00:30:26,500
and they will never follow us.

461
00:30:26,500 --> 00:30:28,350
They find us repulsive.

462
00:30:28,350 --> 00:30:29,830
I find us repulsive.

463
00:30:29,830 --> 00:30:31,820
And we find them repulsive,

464
00:30:31,820 --> 00:30:35,210
which is why we surround ourselves with large comfortable boxes

465
00:30:35,220 --> 00:30:36,590
to keep them away.

466
00:30:37,350 --> 00:30:38,440
And yet...

467
00:30:39,380 --> 00:30:41,060
no matter what we do...

468
00:30:41,630 --> 00:30:46,040
people like you and me are never really satisfied inside the box.

469
00:30:46,110 --> 00:30:47,300
Not for long.

470
00:30:48,980 --> 00:30:50,160
You're right.

471
00:30:50,800 --> 00:30:53,140
- Let's go for a walk. - No.

472
00:30:53,170 --> 00:30:55,650
How many dwarves are there in the world?

473
00:30:56,470 --> 00:30:58,550
Is Cersei going to kill them all?

474
00:31:03,120 --> 00:31:04,470
Not him.

475
00:31:04,840 --> 00:31:06,900
Are you trying to deceive your queen?

476
00:31:07,210 --> 00:31:09,170
Shall I throw them in a cell, Your Grace?

477
00:31:09,450 --> 00:31:11,040
That won't be necessary, Ser Meryn.

478
00:31:11,040 --> 00:31:13,480
I don't want to dissuade the other hunters.

479
00:31:14,010 --> 00:31:15,500
Mistakes will be made.

480
00:31:15,500 --> 00:31:16,390
- Thank you, Your Grace. - Thanks.

481
00:31:16,400 --> 00:31:17,450
- Thank you, Your Grace. - Thank you.

482
00:31:17,450 --> 00:31:18,330
Take the head.

483
00:31:18,330 --> 00:31:19,150
Pardon me,  your Grace.

484
00:31:19,150 --> 00:31:21,320
I would take it if you don't mind.

485
00:31:21,330 --> 00:31:23,420
It could prove useful for my work.

486
00:31:24,670 --> 00:31:25,860
Very good.

487
00:31:28,920 --> 00:31:30,380
Over there will be fine.

488
00:31:32,000 --> 00:31:34,110
You heard the man, over there.

489
00:32:02,200 --> 00:32:03,640
You're the hand of the King.

490
00:32:03,640 --> 00:32:04,940
No, uncle.

491
00:32:05,170 --> 00:32:08,660
Clearly it would not be appropriate for a woman to assume that role.

492
00:32:08,940 --> 00:32:10,360
I'm merely advising my son until

493
00:32:10,360 --> 00:32:13,070
he comes of age and chooses a Hand for himself.

494
00:32:13,380 --> 00:32:15,120
Your Grace, I would be willing

495
00:32:15,120 --> 00:32:17,240
to serve provisionally as the King's Hand

496
00:32:17,240 --> 00:32:18,650
until he becomes old enough.

497
00:32:18,650 --> 00:32:19,990
You're a good man, Lord Tyrell,

498
00:32:19,990 --> 00:32:21,810
but I don't imagine you'll have the time.

499
00:32:22,160 --> 00:32:24,410
In addition to be Master of Ships,

500
00:32:24,420 --> 00:32:26,940
the King has appointed you Master of Coin.

501
00:32:28,670 --> 00:32:29,690
Oh, Your Grace.

502
00:32:29,690 --> 00:32:33,750
He called your experience and wisdom in financial matters unparalleled.

503
00:32:34,040 --> 00:32:35,730
He said he would be honored

504
00:32:35,730 --> 00:32:38,410
to have you represent the Crown's interest in the same.

505
00:32:38,410 --> 00:32:40,080
The honor is all mine, Your Grace.

506
00:32:40,470 --> 00:32:43,450
Y-Y-Your Grace, in the past, on several occasions,

507
00:32:43,450 --> 00:32:46,140
a Grand Maester has served as the King's Hand.

508
00:32:46,140 --> 00:32:50,770
The King has named Qyburn the new Master of Whispers.

509
00:32:52,690 --> 00:32:53,640
Your Grace, 

510
00:32:53,640 --> 00:32:58,590
him? This-this man? Th-This embarrassment to the Citadel?

511
00:32:58,980 --> 00:33:00,090
Your Grace,

512
00:33:00,630 --> 00:33:04,020
what qualifications can he possibly have for this post?

513
00:33:04,020 --> 00:33:06,700
The qualification of loyalty, Grand Maester.

514
00:33:06,700 --> 00:33:08,970
That's far more than the eunuch ever had.

515
00:33:09,340 --> 00:33:11,540
Far more than many ever have.

516
00:33:12,290 --> 00:33:14,080
I must say... I cannot see how...

517
00:33:14,080 --> 00:33:15,280
Uncle Kevan,

518
00:33:15,280 --> 00:33:18,550
in light of your position as Commander of the Lannister Armies,

519
00:33:18,610 --> 00:33:21,910
it would please the King if you would serve as his Master of War.

520
00:33:22,230 --> 00:33:24,950
No man living better deserves the title.

521
00:33:25,480 --> 00:33:27,140
That is kind of you to say.

522
00:33:27,670 --> 00:33:30,090
I would like to hear it from the King himself.

523
00:33:30,090 --> 00:33:31,570
Well, the King is very busy at this moment.

524
00:33:31,570 --> 00:33:34,120
He should be here learning what it means to rule.

525
00:33:34,120 --> 00:33:35,360
He is learning.

526
00:33:35,570 --> 00:33:37,840
On this occasion, in his capacity as ruler,

527
00:33:37,840 --> 00:33:39,830
he's asked me to speak on his behalf.

528
00:33:40,340 --> 00:33:43,760
I returned to the capital to pay my respects to my brother,

529
00:33:44,130 --> 00:33:45,260
and to you,

530
00:33:45,260 --> 00:33:46,710
and to serve the King.

531
00:33:47,070 --> 00:33:50,660
I did not return to the capital to serve as your puppet.

532
00:33:50,660 --> 00:33:54,290
To watch you stack the Small Council with sycophants.

533
00:33:55,210 --> 00:33:56,840
Sending your own brother away so he won't be present.

534
00:33:56,840 --> 00:33:58,400
My brother has left the capital

535
00:33:58,400 --> 00:34:00,720
to lead a sensitive diplomatic mission.

536
00:34:00,720 --> 00:34:01,780
What mission?

537
00:34:01,780 --> 00:34:04,150
That is not your concern as Master of War.

538
00:34:06,300 --> 00:34:08,840
I do not recognize your authority to dictate

539
00:34:08,840 --> 00:34:11,300
what is and is not my concern.

540
00:34:11,840 --> 00:34:13,250
You are the Queen Mother.

541
00:34:14,310 --> 00:34:15,640
Nothing more.

542
00:34:18,820 --> 00:34:21,540
You would abandon your king and his time of need?

543
00:34:21,560 --> 00:34:24,390
If he wants to send for me, I will be waiting for him

544
00:34:24,930 --> 00:34:26,520
at Casterly Rock.

545
00:34:34,440 --> 00:34:36,600
Come on, you know this one.

546
00:34:38,490 --> 00:34:39,900
It looks like an animal.

547
00:34:43,040 --> 00:34:44,180
Snake.

548
00:34:44,760 --> 00:34:47,180
S-S-Sn... "S".

549
00:34:47,180 --> 00:34:49,760
- It's an "S". - Right, very good.

550
00:34:51,690 --> 00:34:54,160
Did you know that the youngest Lord Commander in history,

551
00:34:54,160 --> 00:34:56,690
Osric Stark, was elected at the age of 10?

552
00:34:58,650 --> 00:35:00,300
I know "S".

553
00:35:00,500 --> 00:35:02,010
You'll learn, I promise.

554
00:35:02,270 --> 00:35:03,050
I taught Ser Davos,

555
00:35:03,050 --> 00:35:05,240
and old people are terrible at learning new things.

556
00:35:05,240 --> 00:35:07,400
Well, you are a wonderful teacher.

557
00:35:08,950 --> 00:35:10,170
Very patient.

558
00:35:10,170 --> 00:35:13,220
I only said that the more time that you spend practicing,

559
00:35:13,220 --> 00:35:14,310
the faster you will be able to read.

560
00:35:14,320 --> 00:35:15,500
That's all right.

561
00:35:15,970 --> 00:35:17,330
We're doing just fine.

562
00:35:17,330 --> 00:35:21,660
I'm sure you and Ostrich Stark have a lot to talk about.

563
00:35:24,760 --> 00:35:27,080
How old were you when you learned how to read?

564
00:35:27,100 --> 00:35:28,700
- Three. - Three?

565
00:35:28,780 --> 00:35:30,330
Who taught you, your mother?

566
00:35:30,980 --> 00:35:32,020
No,

567
00:35:32,020 --> 00:35:33,580
old Maester Cressen did.

568
00:35:33,990 --> 00:35:35,420
I had a lot of time to practice.

569
00:35:35,420 --> 00:35:37,430
My mother kept me inside because...

570
00:35:40,230 --> 00:35:44,010
What do you call it in the south? What happened to your face.

571
00:35:44,250 --> 00:35:45,460
Grayscale.

572
00:35:46,290 --> 00:35:48,050
What would you call it in the north of the Wall?

573
00:35:48,850 --> 00:35:50,120
I don't know.

574
00:35:51,050 --> 00:35:54,170
But two of my sisters had it. They both died.

575
00:35:54,600 --> 00:35:56,150
How did they cure you?

576
00:35:56,150 --> 00:35:58,730
I don't remember. I was a baby.

577
00:35:58,950 --> 00:36:01,190
A lot of people came and tried, I think.

578
00:36:01,380 --> 00:36:03,190
Whatever they did, it went away.

579
00:36:05,310 --> 00:36:06,940
What happened to your sisters?

580
00:36:09,230 --> 00:36:13,310
My father made them move out of the keep into the huts outside. 

581
00:36:14,060 --> 00:36:15,990
None of us were allowed to go near them.

582
00:36:16,280 --> 00:36:19,810
But we heard them, especially at night.

583
00:36:20,880 --> 00:36:25,130
They started to sound not like themselves.

584
00:36:25,780 --> 00:36:27,260
Did you ever see them?

585
00:36:28,340 --> 00:36:29,930
Only once at the end.

586
00:36:31,950 --> 00:36:33,330
They were covered with it...

587
00:36:34,620 --> 00:36:37,200
their faces, their arms.

588
00:36:38,250 --> 00:36:39,870
They acted like animals.

589
00:36:41,080 --> 00:36:44,100
My father had to drag them out to the woods on a rope.

590
00:36:44,940 --> 00:36:46,850
What did he do with them in the woods?

591
00:36:52,530 --> 00:36:53,770
Mother.

592
00:36:54,110 --> 00:36:55,200
Leave us.

593
00:36:58,720 --> 00:36:59,910
Your Grace.

594
00:37:01,530 --> 00:37:03,110
You need to stay away from that girl.

595
00:37:03,110 --> 00:37:04,650
- Why? - She's a wildling.

596
00:37:04,650 --> 00:37:05,950
Her name is Gilly.

597
00:37:06,040 --> 00:37:07,850
She's nice. I'm teaching her to read.

598
00:37:07,850 --> 00:37:11,080
She's a wildling. Your father defeated her people.

599
00:37:11,080 --> 00:37:13,750
He executed their king for treason.

600
00:37:14,090 --> 00:37:16,980
They could strike at him by striking at you.

601
00:37:17,090 --> 00:37:18,540
Gilly wouldn't do that.

602
00:37:20,330 --> 00:37:22,510
You have no idea what people will do.

603
00:37:23,500 --> 00:37:25,750
All your books and you still don't know.

604
00:37:31,920 --> 00:37:34,150
I ordered Mance Rayder burned at the stake.

605
00:37:34,550 --> 00:37:36,850
You prevented that order from being carried out.

606
00:37:36,900 --> 00:37:39,180
You showed mercy to Mance Rayder.

607
00:37:39,640 --> 00:37:41,200
A King's word is law.

608
00:37:42,090 --> 00:37:43,090
Perhaps you should ask Ser Davos

609
00:37:43,090 --> 00:37:45,940
how much mercy I show to lawbreakers.

610
00:37:49,600 --> 00:37:51,770
Show too much kindness, people won't fear you.

611
00:37:51,770 --> 00:37:53,540
If they don't fear you, they don't follow you.

612
00:37:54,570 --> 00:37:56,970
With respect, Your Grace, the free folk will never follow you

613
00:37:56,970 --> 00:37:58,260
no matter what you do.

614
00:37:59,560 --> 00:38:01,590
You're the man who burned their king alive.

615
00:38:02,090 --> 00:38:03,270
Who, then?

616
00:38:05,360 --> 00:38:06,540
You?

617
00:38:06,810 --> 00:38:09,930
No. Only one of their own.

618
00:38:12,180 --> 00:38:13,700
Do you know this wretched girl?

619
00:38:15,340 --> 00:38:17,880
- Lyanna Mormont. - The Lord Commander's niece.

620
00:38:18,290 --> 00:38:19,820
Lady of Bear Island

621
00:38:20,260 --> 00:38:21,680
and a child of ten.

622
00:38:23,210 --> 00:38:26,150
I asked her to commit her house to my cause. That's her response.

623
00:38:26,390 --> 00:38:29,530
"Bear Island knows no king but the King in the North,

624
00:38:29,550 --> 00:38:31,340
whose name is Stark."

625
00:38:31,870 --> 00:38:33,270
That amuses you.

626
00:38:35,510 --> 00:38:36,960
I apologize, Your Grace.

627
00:38:38,110 --> 00:38:41,760
Northerners can be a bit like the free folk.

628
00:38:42,670 --> 00:38:44,030
Loyal to their own.

629
00:38:44,750 --> 00:38:45,650
I know.

630
00:38:45,650 --> 00:38:47,270
My brother Robert went on often

631
00:38:47,270 --> 00:38:50,180
and loudly about how difficult it was to control them.

632
00:38:52,510 --> 00:38:54,300
Even with your father's help.

633
00:38:57,250 --> 00:39:00,480
Tonight, the Night's Watch elect a new Lord Commander.

634
00:39:01,350 --> 00:39:03,040
Ser Alliser Thorne is going to win.

635
00:39:03,040 --> 00:39:05,070
- Most likely. - One pleasant man.

636
00:39:05,620 --> 00:39:07,080
He thinks you're a traitor.

637
00:39:08,320 --> 00:39:09,860
What's your life gonna be like here at the Wall

638
00:39:09,860 --> 00:39:11,280
with Thorne in command?

639
00:39:11,280 --> 00:39:12,640
Unpleasant, I expect.

640
00:39:12,650 --> 00:39:14,460
Your bravery made him look weak.

641
00:39:15,980 --> 00:39:17,440
He'll punish you for it.

642
00:39:17,690 --> 00:39:19,660
I don't punish men for bravery.

643
00:39:19,660 --> 00:39:20,940
I reward them.

644
00:39:21,500 --> 00:39:23,200
I don't doubt it, Your Grace.

645
00:39:24,450 --> 00:39:26,340
But I'm a brother of the Night's Watch.

646
00:39:26,630 --> 00:39:29,130
I pledged them my life, my honor, my sword.

647
00:39:29,510 --> 00:39:31,520
I don't know what I have left to give you.

648
00:39:31,520 --> 00:39:33,330
You can give me the North.

649
00:39:34,710 --> 00:39:36,640
I can't.

650
00:39:37,420 --> 00:39:39,880
Even if I wanted to, I'm a bastard.

651
00:39:40,120 --> 00:39:41,210
A Snow.

652
00:39:41,640 --> 00:39:44,350
Kneel before me. Lay your sword at my feet.

653
00:39:44,350 --> 00:39:47,280
Pledge me your service and you'll rise again as Jon Stark,

654
00:39:47,280 --> 00:39:48,760
Lord of Winterfell.

655
00:39:54,630 --> 00:39:57,160
He'll make you a Stark with the stroke of a pen.

656
00:39:57,380 --> 00:39:59,820
It's the first thing I ever remember wanting.

657
00:40:01,140 --> 00:40:03,800
I daydreamed that my father would ask the king

658
00:40:03,850 --> 00:40:06,330
and just like that, I would never be the Bastard of Winterfell again.

659
00:40:06,340 --> 00:40:09,310
No, you deserve that. You do.

660
00:40:09,310 --> 00:40:11,530
I-I couldn't be happier for you.

661
00:40:12,500 --> 00:40:14,090
I'm gonna refuse him.

662
00:40:16,070 --> 00:40:17,050
But...

663
00:40:17,250 --> 00:40:19,340
you'd be Lord of Winterfell.

664
00:40:20,010 --> 00:40:22,380
I swore a vow to the Night's Watch.

665
00:40:22,380 --> 00:40:23,910
If I don't take my own word seriously,

666
00:40:23,910 --> 00:40:26,160
what sort of Lord of Winterfell would I be?

667
00:40:31,320 --> 00:40:34,940
Crowded, You'd think we were serving venison stew.

668
00:40:41,550 --> 00:40:45,950
Does anyone wish to speak for candidates...

669
00:40:46,400 --> 00:40:48,860
before we cast our tokens...

670
00:40:49,150 --> 00:40:53,620
for the 998th Lord Commander

671
00:40:53,620 --> 00:40:55,450
of the Night's Watch?

672
00:40:57,690 --> 00:40:59,430
Ser Alliser Thorne is not just a knight,

673
00:40:59,440 --> 00:41:01,300
he's a man of true nobility.

674
00:41:01,300 --> 00:41:04,260
He was Acting Commander when the Wall came under attack

675
00:41:04,260 --> 00:41:06,150
and led us to victory against the wildlings.

676
00:41:06,150 --> 00:41:07,080
Hear. Hear.

677
00:41:07,080 --> 00:41:08,610
He's a veteran of 100 battles

678
00:41:08,610 --> 00:41:11,960
and has been a defender of the Watch and the Wall almost all of his life.

679
00:41:13,740 --> 00:41:15,620
- He's the only true choice. - Hear.

680
00:41:15,620 --> 00:41:17,380
Hear.

681
00:41:19,940 --> 00:41:22,610
Ser Denys Mallister joined the Watch as a boy

682
00:41:22,610 --> 00:41:26,230
and has served loyally longer than any of the Ranger.

683
00:41:26,520 --> 00:41:28,360
- That's right. - Through 10 winters he served.

684
00:41:28,360 --> 00:41:30,420
As Commander of the Shadow Tower...

685
00:41:30,420 --> 00:41:32,390
he kept the wildlings away.

686
00:41:32,690 --> 00:41:34,210
We could do no better.

687
00:41:38,250 --> 00:41:40,280
If there's no one else...

688
00:41:40,280 --> 00:41:42,260
we will begin the voting.

689
00:41:42,260 --> 00:41:47,190
The triangular tokens count for Ser Alliser Thorne.

690
00:41:47,480 --> 00:41:51,580
The square tokens for Ser Denys Mallister. Each brother...

691
00:41:51,960 --> 00:41:53,300
Maester Aemon...

692
00:41:55,720 --> 00:41:58,430
Samwell Tarly, go on.

693
00:41:59,600 --> 00:42:01,240
Sam the Slayer.

694
00:42:02,670 --> 00:42:05,760
Another wildling lover just like his friend Jon Snow.

695
00:42:05,860 --> 00:42:07,730
How's your lady love, Slayer?

696
00:42:08,500 --> 00:42:10,050
Her name is Gilly.

697
00:42:10,570 --> 00:42:12,450
Brother Slynt knows her quite well.

698
00:42:12,480 --> 00:42:13,440
They cowered together in

699
00:42:13,440 --> 00:42:15,620
the larder during the battle for the Wall.

700
00:42:16,280 --> 00:42:17,470
Lies!

701
00:42:17,530 --> 00:42:20,090
A wildling girl, a baby,

702
00:42:20,650 --> 00:42:22,320
and Lord Janos.

703
00:42:22,730 --> 00:42:24,680
I found him there after the battle was over.

704
00:42:24,680 --> 00:42:26,440
In a puddle of his own making.

705
00:42:30,480 --> 00:42:35,110
Whilst Lord Janos was hiding with the women and children

706
00:42:35,450 --> 00:42:37,210
Jon Snow was leading.

707
00:42:38,140 --> 00:42:40,370
Ser Alliser fought bravely, it is true,

708
00:42:40,370 --> 00:42:42,570
but when he was wounded, it was Jon who saved us.

709
00:42:42,570 --> 00:42:45,370
He took charge of the Wall's defense,

710
00:42:45,380 --> 00:42:47,680
he killed the Magnar of the Thenns,

711
00:42:47,920 --> 00:42:50,190
he went North to deal with Mance Rayder.

712
00:42:50,190 --> 00:42:52,990
Knowing it almost certainly meant his own death.

713
00:42:56,620 --> 00:42:57,890
Before that,

714
00:42:59,200 --> 00:43:02,370
he lead the mission to avenge the Lord Commander Mormont.

715
00:43:04,100 --> 00:43:06,930
Mormont himself chose Jon to be his steward.

716
00:43:06,930 --> 00:43:08,570
He saw something in Jon

717
00:43:08,570 --> 00:43:10,710
and now we've all seen it, too.

718
00:43:11,280 --> 00:43:12,580
He may be young,

719
00:43:13,780 --> 00:43:15,890
but he's the commander we turned to

720
00:43:15,890 --> 00:43:17,760
when the night was darkest.

721
00:43:17,760 --> 00:43:19,110
Hear.

722
00:43:25,340 --> 00:43:26,360
Aye.

723
00:43:26,880 --> 00:43:28,810
Can't argue with any of that.

724
00:43:29,930 --> 00:43:32,460
But who does Jon Snow want to command?

725
00:43:32,780 --> 00:43:34,250
The Night's Watch

726
00:43:35,810 --> 00:43:37,750
or the wildlings?

727
00:43:37,970 --> 00:43:41,230
Everyone knows he loved a wildling girl.

728
00:43:41,230 --> 00:43:43,260
Spoke with Mance Rayder many times.

729
00:43:43,260 --> 00:43:43,910
What would have happened

730
00:43:43,920 --> 00:43:47,010
in that tent between those two old friends

731
00:43:47,010 --> 00:43:49,400
if Stannis's army hadn't come along?

732
00:43:49,470 --> 00:43:54,290
We all saw him put the King-Beyond-the-Wall out of his misery.

733
00:43:54,320 --> 00:43:58,130
Do you want to choose a man who has fought the wildlings all his life

734
00:43:58,430 --> 00:44:00,260
or a man who makes love to them?

735
00:44:08,330 --> 00:44:09,710
It is time!

736
00:44:56,590 --> 00:44:58,700
It appears to be a tie, maester.

737
00:45:19,140 --> 00:45:20,810
Jon Snow! Jon Snow!

738
00:45:20,810 --> 00:45:22,370
Snow! Snow!

739
00:45:22,370 --> 00:45:24,260
Snow! Snow!

740
00:45:53,880 --> 00:45:56,450
You! You!

741
00:46:00,020 --> 00:46:01,230
What have you got there?

742
00:46:04,220 --> 00:46:07,060
- I said... - Turn around and go!

743
00:46:09,480 --> 00:46:10,700
Turn around...

744
00:46:11,370 --> 00:46:13,730
- and go! - That's a nice little sword.

745
00:46:13,980 --> 00:46:16,230
Worth a hundred pieces, a sword like that.

746
00:46:18,550 --> 00:46:20,640
Nothing's worth anything to dead men.

747
00:46:24,760 --> 00:46:26,270
Quickly, go! Go!

748
00:46:39,720 --> 00:46:40,990
Who are you?

749
00:46:41,830 --> 00:46:43,570
Why were they scared of you?

750
00:46:43,930 --> 00:46:45,330
You lost this.

751
00:46:56,650 --> 00:46:58,940
You said there was no Jaqen H'ghar here.

752
00:46:59,170 --> 00:47:00,310
There isn't.

753
00:47:00,630 --> 00:47:02,780
A man is not Jaqen H'ghar.

754
00:47:05,250 --> 00:47:06,580
Who are you, then?

755
00:47:08,160 --> 00:47:09,220
No one.

756
00:47:09,710 --> 00:47:11,830
And that is who a girl must become.

761
00:48:23,850 --> 00:48:25,780
Why?

785
00:50:25,750 --> 00:50:26,710
Mhysa!

786
00:50:26,710 --> 00:50:27,800
Mhysa!

787
00:50:28,080 --> 00:50:29,210
Mhysa!

788
00:50:29,440 --> 00:50:32,000
Mhysa! Mhysa!

789
00:50:35,190 --> 00:50:36,350
She should have cut the traitor's

790
00:50:36,350 --> 00:50:38,700
head in the Great Pyramid and be done with it.

791
00:50:38,700 --> 00:50:40,860
Which is what I keep telling her to do to you.

792
00:50:45,110 --> 00:50:46,320
Mhysa!

802
00:52:05,790 --> 00:52:07,030
Mhysa!

803
00:52:42,870 --> 00:52:44,550
Mhysa!

804
00:53:47,950 --> 00:53:50,470
I'll stand guard outside your door tonight, Your Grace.

805
00:53:50,480 --> 00:53:52,240
We all guard tonight.

806
00:53:53,670 --> 00:53:54,770
Leave me.

807
00:54:47,840 --> 00:54:49,060
Drogon.

