1
00:03:11,590 --> 00:03:13,300
Is that Estermont?

2
00:03:14,020 --> 00:03:15,800
Tarth, Ser Jaime.

3
00:03:18,300 --> 00:03:19,820
The Sapphire Isle.

4
00:03:24,350 --> 00:03:26,150
Why are we on a merchant ship?

5
00:03:26,230 --> 00:03:28,190
Why no Lannister sails?

6
00:03:30,850 --> 00:03:32,640
This ship's sailing to Oldtown.

7
00:03:32,640 --> 00:03:35,110
We'll get off earlier, not far from Sunspear.

8
00:03:35,340 --> 00:03:37,700
Row ourselves to the Dornish shores in the night.

9
00:03:39,390 --> 00:03:40,820
You ever been to Dorne?

10
00:03:41,200 --> 00:03:42,750
- No. - I have.

11
00:03:42,980 --> 00:03:44,570
The Dornish are crazy.

12
00:03:44,570 --> 00:03:47,320
All they want to do is fight and fuck, fuck and fight.

13
00:03:47,320 --> 00:03:49,150
You should be happy to go back.

14
00:03:51,200 --> 00:03:52,590
There's nothing like a good fight

15
00:03:52,600 --> 00:03:54,530
to get you in the mood for fucking.

16
00:03:54,720 --> 00:03:56,980
And there's nothing like a fuck-mad Dornish girl

17
00:03:57,060 --> 00:03:59,340
to clear your head for the next fight.

18
00:03:59,560 --> 00:04:01,410
It's how the two work together.

19
00:04:01,450 --> 00:04:03,800
Now we're gonna be doing a lot of fighting, I am sure.

20
00:04:03,890 --> 00:04:05,210
Well, I am.

21
00:04:05,250 --> 00:04:08,270
But I don't imagine we'll get to stick around for the rest.

22
00:04:08,300 --> 00:04:10,070
Not after we've kidnapped their princess.

23
00:04:10,070 --> 00:04:12,190
We are not kidnapping their princess.

24
00:04:12,190 --> 00:04:15,230
We are rescuing my niece, bringing her back to her family,

25
00:04:15,720 --> 00:04:16,860
Your niece?

26
00:04:24,990 --> 00:04:27,140
I've been doing this sort of thing a long time.

27
00:04:27,290 --> 00:04:28,400
I'm good at it.

28
00:04:28,400 --> 00:04:30,220
- That's why you're here. - I know.

29
00:04:30,370 --> 00:04:31,460
Why are you here?

30
00:04:31,460 --> 00:04:34,190
Why not send 40 of me? Or an army?

31
00:04:34,190 --> 00:04:36,380
Unlike most folks, you've actually got one.

32
00:04:36,380 --> 00:04:38,420
Because I don't want to start a war.

33
00:04:40,120 --> 00:04:42,730
That still doesn't explain what you're doing here.

34
00:04:45,510 --> 00:04:46,760
It has to be me.

35
00:04:50,020 --> 00:04:52,160
If I'm putting something like this together,

36
00:04:52,460 --> 00:04:53,700
a one-handed man

37
00:04:53,700 --> 00:04:54,510
who happens to be

38
00:04:54,510 --> 00:04:57,230
one of the most recognizable faces in Westeros is not...

39
00:04:57,230 --> 00:04:58,740
It has to be me.

40
00:05:04,600 --> 00:05:06,580
You set your brother free, didn't you?

41
00:05:08,650 --> 00:05:10,520
I'll bet your sister didn't like that.

42
00:05:12,570 --> 00:05:14,400
Varys set him free.

43
00:05:18,650 --> 00:05:19,630
Well...

44
00:05:21,600 --> 00:05:25,390
if you ever see the wee fucker, give him my regards.

45
00:05:29,190 --> 00:05:31,300
He murdered my father.

46
00:05:34,150 --> 00:05:36,870
If I ever see him, I'll split him in two.

47
00:05:38,310 --> 00:05:40,330
And then I'll give him your regards.

48
00:05:46,780 --> 00:05:51,200
The Iron Bank has called in one tenth of the Crown's debts.

49
00:05:51,530 --> 00:05:53,840
Given the expense of rebuilding the royal fleet...

50
00:05:53,840 --> 00:05:55,690
How much can the Crown afford?

51
00:05:55,840 --> 00:05:59,060
With winter coming, half what they ask.

52
00:05:59,640 --> 00:06:02,340
- Less? - You're the Master of Coin.

53
00:06:02,730 --> 00:06:03,610
How do we pay them?

54
00:06:03,620 --> 00:06:06,350
House Tyrell could front the gold and the...

55
00:06:06,350 --> 00:06:08,160
the Crown would pay us back in time,

56
00:06:08,170 --> 00:06:10,640
or I'd have words with my daughter.

57
00:06:16,310 --> 00:06:18,310
You've already given us too much.

58
00:06:19,760 --> 00:06:22,820
No, we must arrange better terms with the Iron Bank.

59
00:06:22,910 --> 00:06:24,950
- Absolutely. - In person.

60
00:06:27,250 --> 00:06:28,050
Me?

61
00:06:28,050 --> 00:06:29,990
We must send an envoy to the Iron Bank,

62
00:06:29,990 --> 00:06:33,680
someone of importance to show these bankers our respect.

63
00:06:33,680 --> 00:06:34,900
As the King's Master of Coin,

64
00:06:34,910 --> 00:06:36,760
I can think of no one more qualified.

65
00:06:36,760 --> 00:06:38,480
I would be honored, Your Grace.

66
00:06:38,480 --> 00:06:39,770
The King has expressed concern

67
00:06:39,770 --> 00:06:42,580
about his father-in-law's safety on this voyage.

68
00:06:46,020 --> 00:06:50,050
He's ordered Ser Meryn to personally lead your escort.

69
00:06:52,140 --> 00:06:54,050
My very own Kingsguard?

70
00:06:54,310 --> 00:06:56,410
- Please express my... - Safe travels, Lord Tyrell.

71
00:06:56,960 --> 00:06:58,590
Of course, of course,

72
00:06:58,800 --> 00:07:02,120
I'll give your regards to the Titan of Braavos.

73
00:07:11,170 --> 00:07:14,340
The Small Council grows smaller and smaller.

74
00:07:14,340 --> 00:07:16,090
Not small enough.

75
00:07:26,820 --> 00:07:29,270
May I offer you some wine, Your Holiness?

76
00:07:30,140 --> 00:07:31,110
No.

77
00:07:35,450 --> 00:07:37,740
The old High Septon would have asked the vintage.

78
00:07:37,740 --> 00:07:41,120
I could say that our minds are temples to the Seven

79
00:07:41,130 --> 00:07:42,990
and should be kept pure.

80
00:07:43,590 --> 00:07:45,110
But the truth is

81
00:07:45,360 --> 00:07:47,360
I don't like the taste.

82
00:07:50,060 --> 00:07:51,510
How may I serve?

83
00:07:52,630 --> 00:07:55,990
All over Westeros we hear of septs being burned,

84
00:07:56,250 --> 00:07:58,570
silent sisters raped,

85
00:07:59,550 --> 00:08:01,970
bodies of holy men piled in the streets.

86
00:08:01,970 --> 00:08:04,550
Wars teach people to obey the sword,

87
00:08:04,560 --> 00:08:05,620
not the Gods.

88
00:08:05,620 --> 00:08:08,060
Perhaps the Gods need a sword of their own.

89
00:08:08,940 --> 00:08:10,540
In the days before the Targaryens,

90
00:08:10,540 --> 00:08:14,020
the Faith Militant dispensed the justice of the Seven.

91
00:08:14,150 --> 00:08:18,080
Well, the Faith Militant was disarmed more than two centuries ago.

92
00:08:18,710 --> 00:08:21,880
If I explain their holy purpose to my son the king,

93
00:08:22,490 --> 00:08:23,780
I have no doubt he will sign

94
00:08:23,790 --> 00:08:26,890
a decree arming the believers you find worthy.

95
00:08:27,130 --> 00:08:31,040
An army that defends the bodies and souls of the common people.

96
00:08:31,040 --> 00:08:34,060
An army and service to the Gods themselves.

97
00:08:34,060 --> 00:08:35,750
And to you, of course.

98
00:08:36,370 --> 00:08:38,330
As the chosen representative of the Seven.

99
00:08:38,330 --> 00:08:40,690
An honor I've never expected.

100
00:08:41,170 --> 00:08:43,010
Or, indeed, ever wished for.

101
00:08:43,010 --> 00:08:44,790
Which is why you were chosen.

102
00:08:46,860 --> 00:08:49,270
You and I both know how the world works.

103
00:08:49,420 --> 00:08:51,440
Too often the wicked are the wealthiest,

104
00:08:51,440 --> 00:08:53,190
beyond the reach of justice.

105
00:08:53,190 --> 00:08:56,960
The king himself cannot always punish those who deserve it most.

106
00:08:57,170 --> 00:08:59,750
All sinners are equal before the Gods.

107
00:09:04,440 --> 00:09:08,800
What would you say if I told you of a great sinner in our very midst?

108
00:09:08,980 --> 00:09:11,660
Shielded by gold and privilege.

109
00:09:13,960 --> 00:09:16,170
May the Father judge him justly.

110
00:09:55,200 --> 00:09:57,160
Help me! Help me!

111
00:10:27,720 --> 00:10:30,460
This is Lord Petyr Baelish's establishment.

112
00:10:41,230 --> 00:10:42,830
Cocksucker!

113
00:10:44,180 --> 00:10:45,990
Boy fucker!

114
00:10:46,540 --> 00:10:48,830
You buggering filth!

115
00:10:49,430 --> 00:10:52,920
There's a special place in the Seven Hells for your kind.

116
00:10:52,920 --> 00:10:55,840
Please, please, I'll pay!

117
00:10:56,210 --> 00:10:57,570
I'll pay all of you.

118
00:10:58,320 --> 00:10:59,760
Yes, you will!

119
00:11:35,470 --> 00:11:36,470
Seize him.

120
00:11:38,860 --> 00:11:39,530
Get your hands off me.

121
00:11:39,530 --> 00:11:41,320
Ser Loras of House Tyrell,

122
00:11:41,330 --> 00:11:43,480
you have broken the laws of Gods and men.

123
00:11:44,980 --> 00:11:46,040
Who do you think you are?

124
00:11:47,500 --> 00:11:48,740
Justice.

125
00:11:55,520 --> 00:11:57,230
Why is my brother in a cell?

126
00:11:57,980 --> 00:11:59,360
I--I don't know.

127
00:12:00,470 --> 00:12:02,110
I--I didn't order it.

128
00:12:02,220 --> 00:12:03,780
We both know who did.

129
00:12:04,870 --> 00:12:07,610
You told me she was returning to Casterly Rock.

130
00:12:09,080 --> 00:12:10,850
Are you saying my mother is behind this?

131
00:12:10,920 --> 00:12:13,320
She's jealous you're not hers anymore.

132
00:12:13,320 --> 00:12:16,340
Arresting my brother is her revenge.

133
00:12:16,430 --> 00:12:18,120
Aren't you and mother getting along?

134
00:12:24,170 --> 00:12:27,930
Oh, my sweet, sweet King.

135
00:12:29,780 --> 00:12:32,740
Do you have any affection for me at all?

136
00:12:34,400 --> 00:12:36,130
Of course I do.

137
00:12:36,820 --> 00:12:38,230
You're my Queen.

138
00:12:38,310 --> 00:12:43,090
I can't bear to think of my brother locked away in some grimy cell.

139
00:12:45,650 --> 00:12:47,160
I'll set him free for you.

140
00:12:47,870 --> 00:12:49,020
Do you promise?

141
00:12:56,340 --> 00:12:59,200
I demand that Ser Loras be freed now!

142
00:12:59,240 --> 00:13:00,540
Did I arrest him?

143
00:13:02,570 --> 00:13:03,670
Well, no...

144
00:13:04,610 --> 00:13:06,880
But you armed the Faith Militant.

145
00:13:06,880 --> 00:13:09,400
You gave the High Sparrow an army.

146
00:13:10,190 --> 00:13:11,080
I did.

147
00:13:12,980 --> 00:13:15,610
And your wife has every right to criticize.

148
00:13:17,180 --> 00:13:19,580
We can't allow fanatics to arrest the Queen's brother

149
00:13:19,580 --> 00:13:21,670
no matter his perversions.

150
00:13:22,680 --> 00:13:23,790
Then...

151
00:13:25,950 --> 00:13:28,180
can I tell Margaery you'll have Ser Loras released?

152
00:13:28,180 --> 00:13:30,590
I told you, I am not holding Ser Loras.

153
00:13:31,680 --> 00:13:32,900
You're the King.

154
00:13:32,900 --> 00:13:34,630
I'm sure if you speak to the High Sparrow,

155
00:13:34,630 --> 00:13:36,330
he'll release the poor boy.

156
00:13:42,140 --> 00:13:43,150
Halt!

157
00:14:06,940 --> 00:14:10,100
His Holiness is praying. He will not be disturbed.

158
00:14:11,680 --> 00:14:14,670
Give the order and we'll clear out this rabble.

159
00:14:16,580 --> 00:14:20,850
You mean, kill them? Here, in the sept?

160
00:14:20,990 --> 00:14:23,570
You'd be sending them to meet the Gods that they love.

161
00:14:27,480 --> 00:14:28,910
Bastard!

162
00:14:30,180 --> 00:14:31,830
You're an abomination!

163
00:14:36,900 --> 00:14:38,460
Born of sin!

164
00:14:39,610 --> 00:14:41,310
Filthy bastard!

165
00:14:46,140 --> 00:14:47,490
We'll find another way.

166
00:14:50,110 --> 00:14:51,810
Abomination!

167
00:14:57,650 --> 00:14:58,640
My Queen?

168
00:15:04,630 --> 00:15:07,420
There was no way to free Ser Loras without violence.

169
00:15:10,460 --> 00:15:12,190
You're the King of the Andals,

170
00:15:13,000 --> 00:15:16,380
the Lord of the Seven Kingdoms, the Protector of the Realm.

171
00:15:16,860 --> 00:15:19,920
And you let a band of fanatics imprison your brother by law.

172
00:15:21,730 --> 00:15:24,570
- I'm going to speak with the High Sparrow. - Are you? When?

173
00:15:26,880 --> 00:15:28,670
- I--I don't know. - You don't know?

174
00:15:29,360 --> 00:15:31,470
He was praying just now.

175
00:15:34,920 --> 00:15:36,730
I have to send word to Grandmother.

176
00:15:37,780 --> 00:15:39,310
Will you come back later?

177
00:15:41,780 --> 00:15:44,130
I need to be with my family, Your Grace.

178
00:15:45,810 --> 00:15:47,000
Of course.

179
00:15:50,150 --> 00:15:51,840
You think highly of this boy?

180
00:15:52,740 --> 00:15:53,400
Good.

181
00:15:53,400 --> 00:15:55,310
Lord Commander of the Night's Watch.

182
00:15:55,320 --> 00:15:57,930
And a bastard by some tavern slut.

183
00:15:57,940 --> 00:16:00,800
Perhaps, but that wasn't Ned Stark's way.

184
00:16:05,170 --> 00:16:06,670
I should have given you a son.

185
00:16:08,930 --> 00:16:11,260
- Not your fault. - Whose, then?

186
00:16:12,690 --> 00:16:14,920
I gave you nothing but weakness

187
00:16:18,060 --> 00:16:19,560
and deformity.

188
00:16:20,550 --> 00:16:23,460
Those scars mean nothing to the Lord of Light.

189
00:16:23,470 --> 00:16:24,530
My Lady.

190
00:16:25,600 --> 00:16:27,620
Her father is the Lord's chosen King,

191
00:16:27,980 --> 00:16:30,360
and her father's blood runs through her veins.

192
00:16:40,060 --> 00:16:42,030
You march on Winterfell soon?

193
00:16:42,170 --> 00:16:43,290
We must

194
00:16:43,950 --> 00:16:45,570
to beat the snows.

195
00:16:46,850 --> 00:16:50,830
Once before, you put your faith in Ser Davos and left me behind.

196
00:16:53,870 --> 00:16:55,910
I hope you won't make that mistake again.

197
00:16:55,910 --> 00:16:56,920
I won't.

198
00:17:00,480 --> 00:17:01,760
I need you.

199
00:17:01,890 --> 00:17:04,100
You only need faith, my King.

200
00:17:09,050 --> 00:17:10,950
And you, my Lady, what do you need?

201
00:17:12,750 --> 00:17:14,270
To serve my Lord.

202
00:17:19,320 --> 00:17:20,640
Lord Ashford.

203
00:17:26,860 --> 00:17:28,460
Lady Caulfield.

204
00:17:31,370 --> 00:17:32,930
Lord Smallwood.

205
00:17:33,730 --> 00:17:35,110
I've never even heard of these people.

206
00:17:35,110 --> 00:17:37,120
They haven't heard of you, either.

207
00:17:37,710 --> 00:17:39,930
But we need men and they have some.

208
00:17:42,580 --> 00:17:45,580
How many men does this Lord Mayzen have to send us?

209
00:17:45,650 --> 00:17:47,590
More than Lord Wibberley.

210
00:18:01,240 --> 00:18:02,890
- Not him. - I know.

211
00:18:02,890 --> 00:18:05,850
I'm sorry, but we need men and supplies

212
00:18:05,850 --> 00:18:07,400
and Roose Bolton is the Warden of...

213
00:18:07,410 --> 00:18:08,630
He murdered my brother.

214
00:18:08,630 --> 00:18:11,490
We swore to be the Watchers on the Wall.

215
00:18:12,260 --> 00:18:14,570
We can't watch the Wall with 50 men.

216
00:18:15,940 --> 00:18:17,350
And we can't get more men

217
00:18:17,360 --> 00:18:19,870
without help from the Warden of the North.

218
00:18:42,850 --> 00:18:44,320
Apologies, my Lady.

219
00:18:56,900 --> 00:18:58,260
Lord Commander.

220
00:18:59,110 --> 00:19:00,350
How can I help you?

221
00:19:01,090 --> 00:19:03,140
Come with us when we ride south.

222
00:19:03,500 --> 00:19:05,820
None of us know the castle as well as you do.

223
00:19:06,390 --> 00:19:09,930
Its hidden tunnels, its weaknesses, its people.

224
00:19:11,460 --> 00:19:13,680
Winterfell was your home once.

225
00:19:15,200 --> 00:19:17,760
Don't you want to chase the rats out of it?

226
00:19:20,380 --> 00:19:22,620
Castle Black is my home now.

227
00:19:23,350 --> 00:19:26,520
The Night's Watch take no part in the wars of the Seven Kingdoms.

228
00:19:26,520 --> 00:19:28,020
There's only one war.

229
00:19:28,770 --> 00:19:30,830
Life against death.

230
00:19:32,720 --> 00:19:33,810
Come.

231
00:19:34,030 --> 00:19:35,980
Let me show what you're fighting for.

232
00:19:35,980 --> 00:19:38,040
You're gonna show me some vision in the fire.

233
00:19:38,870 --> 00:19:40,290
Forgive me, my Lady,

234
00:19:40,510 --> 00:19:42,240
I don't trust in visions.

235
00:19:43,600 --> 00:19:44,890
No visions.

236
00:19:45,190 --> 00:19:46,580
No magic.

237
00:19:47,460 --> 00:19:48,780
Just life.

238
00:20:09,220 --> 00:20:11,050
Do you feel my heart beating?

239
00:20:14,010 --> 00:20:15,650
There's power in you.

240
00:20:16,050 --> 00:20:20,000
You resist it, and that's your mistake. Embrace it.

241
00:20:31,000 --> 00:20:33,930
The Lord of Light made us male and female.

242
00:20:34,660 --> 00:20:36,870
Two parts of a greater whole.

243
00:20:38,110 --> 00:20:40,760
In our joining, there's power.

244
00:20:42,160 --> 00:20:43,990
Power to make life,

245
00:20:44,510 --> 00:20:46,380
power to make light,

246
00:20:47,200 --> 00:20:49,470
and power to cast shadows.

247
00:20:50,100 --> 00:20:53,120
I don't think Stannis would like that very much.

248
00:20:53,990 --> 00:20:55,490
Then we shouldn't tell him.

249
00:20:56,970 --> 00:20:58,300
I can't.

250
00:20:58,850 --> 00:21:00,040
Why?

251
00:21:00,710 --> 00:21:02,240
I swore a vow.

252
00:21:04,690 --> 00:21:06,020
I loved another.

253
00:21:06,860 --> 00:21:08,880
The dead don't need lovers.

254
00:21:09,270 --> 00:21:10,640
Only the living.

255
00:21:15,920 --> 00:21:17,140
I know.

256
00:21:18,840 --> 00:21:20,270
But I still love her.

257
00:21:35,560 --> 00:21:37,490
You know nothing, Jon Snow.

258
00:22:15,270 --> 00:22:16,620
Are you lonely?

259
00:22:18,460 --> 00:22:19,460
Just bored.

260
00:22:19,460 --> 00:22:20,610
My father used to tell me

261
00:22:20,610 --> 00:22:23,260
that boredom indicates a lack of inner resources.

262
00:22:23,390 --> 00:22:24,940
Were you bored a lot, too?

263
00:22:25,950 --> 00:22:28,620
I know Castle Black is no place for a child, but...

264
00:22:28,620 --> 00:22:29,790
I like it.

265
00:22:29,870 --> 00:22:31,470
I thought I'd be left at home.

266
00:22:32,400 --> 00:22:34,270
I know mother didn't want to bring me.

267
00:22:35,290 --> 00:22:36,530
Why do you say that?

268
00:22:38,630 --> 00:22:40,570
She told me, "I don't want to bring you."

269
00:22:42,750 --> 00:22:44,220
She shouldn't have said that.

270
00:22:54,520 --> 00:22:56,240
Are you ashamed of me, father?

271
00:23:07,780 --> 00:23:09,240
When you were an infant,

272
00:23:10,400 --> 00:23:12,790
a Dornish trader landed on Dragonstone.

273
00:23:13,920 --> 00:23:17,210
His goods were junk except for one wooden doll.

274
00:23:18,600 --> 00:23:21,720
He had even sewn a dress on it in the colors of our House.

275
00:23:23,920 --> 00:23:25,940
No doubt he had heard of your birth

276
00:23:26,480 --> 00:23:29,340
and assumed new fathers were easy targets.

277
00:23:33,060 --> 00:23:36,310
I still remember how you smiled when I put that doll in your cradle.

278
00:23:37,860 --> 00:23:39,570
How you pressed it to your cheek.

279
00:23:47,300 --> 00:23:49,770
By the time we burnt the doll, it was too late.

280
00:23:52,700 --> 00:23:54,290
I was told you would die.

281
00:23:55,350 --> 00:23:56,600
Or worse.

282
00:23:58,040 --> 00:23:59,900
The greyscale would go slow.

283
00:24:00,420 --> 00:24:02,860
Let you grow just enough to know the world

284
00:24:02,860 --> 00:24:04,500
before taking it away from you.

285
00:24:05,080 --> 00:24:07,660
Everyone advised me to send you to the ruins of Valyria

286
00:24:07,660 --> 00:24:10,010
to live out your short life with the Stone men,

287
00:24:10,010 --> 00:24:12,350
before the sickness spread to the castle.

288
00:24:14,510 --> 00:24:16,320
I told them all to go to hell.

289
00:24:18,510 --> 00:24:21,350
I called in every maester on this side of the world.

290
00:24:21,350 --> 00:24:24,430
Every healer, every apothecary.

291
00:24:26,460 --> 00:24:28,840
They stopped the disease and saved your life.

292
00:24:30,130 --> 00:24:31,040
Because you did not belong

293
00:24:31,050 --> 00:24:33,190
across the world with the bloody Stone men.

294
00:24:35,040 --> 00:24:37,510
You are the Princess Shireen of House Baratheon.

295
00:24:40,120 --> 00:24:41,610
And you are my daughter.

296
00:25:43,670 --> 00:25:45,310
I thought I might find you here.

297
00:25:48,530 --> 00:25:49,900
Your Aunt Lyanna.

298
00:25:51,110 --> 00:25:52,980
Father never talked about her.

299
00:25:54,630 --> 00:25:57,630
Sometimes I'd find him down here lighting the candles.

300
00:25:59,310 --> 00:26:00,860
They say she was beautiful.

301
00:26:01,640 --> 00:26:03,080
I saw her once.

302
00:26:03,180 --> 00:26:05,530
I was a boy living with your mother's family.

303
00:26:06,460 --> 00:26:09,110
Lord Whent held a great tourney at Harrenhal.

304
00:26:10,430 --> 00:26:11,860
Everyone was there.

305
00:26:12,250 --> 00:26:13,610
The Mad King,

306
00:26:13,970 --> 00:26:15,250
your father,

307
00:26:15,560 --> 00:26:17,000
Robert Baratheon,

308
00:26:17,990 --> 00:26:21,420
and Lyanna. She was already promised to Robert.

309
00:26:22,300 --> 00:26:25,090
You can imagine what it was like for me, a boy from nowhere

310
00:26:25,380 --> 00:26:26,790
with nothing to his name,

311
00:26:27,510 --> 00:26:31,080
watching these legendary men tilting at the lists.

312
00:26:32,290 --> 00:26:33,950
The last two riders were

313
00:26:33,950 --> 00:26:36,730
Barristan Selmy and Rhaegar Targaryen.

314
00:26:37,070 --> 00:26:40,270
When Rhaegar won, everyone cheered for their prince.

315
00:26:40,970 --> 00:26:41,890
I remember the girls laughing

316
00:26:41,890 --> 00:26:44,590
when he took off his helmet and they saw that silver hair.

317
00:26:45,050 --> 00:26:46,510
How handsome he was.

318
00:26:47,430 --> 00:26:51,690
Until he rode right past his wife, Elia Martell,

319
00:26:52,200 --> 00:26:53,910
and all the smiles died.

320
00:26:55,410 --> 00:26:57,700
I've never seen so many people so quiet.

321
00:26:59,000 --> 00:27:00,640
He rode past his wife

322
00:27:02,510 --> 00:27:05,590
and he lay a crown of winter roses in Lyanna's lap.

323
00:27:06,080 --> 00:27:07,700
Blue as frost.

324
00:27:11,840 --> 00:27:13,180
How many tens of thousands

325
00:27:13,180 --> 00:27:15,660
had to die because Rhaegar chose your aunt?

326
00:27:18,450 --> 00:27:20,270
Yes, he chose her.

327
00:27:21,320 --> 00:27:23,840
And then he kidnapped her and raped her.

328
00:27:32,010 --> 00:27:33,220
Come.

329
00:27:33,930 --> 00:27:36,260
Let's speak somewhere the dead can't hear us.

330
00:27:41,760 --> 00:27:44,060
- You're dressed for riding. - I am.

331
00:27:46,020 --> 00:27:47,330
Where are you going?

332
00:27:47,700 --> 00:27:49,020
King's Landing.

333
00:27:49,780 --> 00:27:51,100
King's Landing?

334
00:27:51,570 --> 00:27:53,040
Cersei sent for me.

335
00:27:53,680 --> 00:27:55,690
We must't let her sniff out any trouble.

336
00:27:56,380 --> 00:27:58,160
You can't leave me here.

337
00:27:58,160 --> 00:28:01,130
I know how hard it is to live with people you despise. Believe me.

338
00:28:02,160 --> 00:28:03,640
But it won't be for long.

339
00:28:04,220 --> 00:28:05,430
How do you know?

340
00:28:07,010 --> 00:28:09,780
Stannis Baratheon garrisons at Castle Black.

341
00:28:10,690 --> 00:28:12,450
He'll march south to King's Landing

342
00:28:12,450 --> 00:28:14,610
before the winter snows block his way.

343
00:28:14,610 --> 00:28:17,080
But first he has to take Winterfell.

344
00:28:18,000 --> 00:28:19,950
- You don't know that. - I do.

345
00:28:21,370 --> 00:28:23,490
Once he liberates these lands from the Boltons,

346
00:28:23,490 --> 00:28:25,820
he'll rally your father's bannermen to his cause.

347
00:28:26,000 --> 00:28:27,510
With the North behind him,

348
00:28:27,960 --> 00:28:30,200
Stannis can finally take the Iron Throne.

349
00:28:30,760 --> 00:28:32,680
You think he'll defeat the Boltons?

350
00:28:33,580 --> 00:28:35,030
He has a larger army.

351
00:28:35,160 --> 00:28:37,760
He's the finest military commander in Westeros.

352
00:28:37,830 --> 00:28:41,050
A betting man would put his money on Stannis.

353
00:28:41,640 --> 00:28:43,730
As it happens, I am a betting man.

354
00:28:45,380 --> 00:28:46,790
And if you're right?

355
00:28:47,140 --> 00:28:48,740
Stannis takes Winterfell,

356
00:28:49,260 --> 00:28:52,210
he rescues you from the most despised family in the North.

357
00:28:52,520 --> 00:28:55,510
Grateful for your late father's courageous support for his claim,

358
00:28:55,560 --> 00:28:57,910
he names you Wardeness of the North.

359
00:28:58,970 --> 00:29:01,430
But I-i wouldn't-

360
00:29:02,170 --> 00:29:03,510
wardeness of the North?

361
00:29:03,510 --> 00:29:05,690
You are the last surviving Stark.

362
00:29:06,480 --> 00:29:07,770
He needs you.

363
00:29:08,600 --> 00:29:09,370
And what if you're wrong?

364
00:29:09,370 --> 00:29:11,340
What if Stannis never attacks Winterfell?

365
00:29:11,340 --> 00:29:13,750
Or he does and the Boltons defeat him?

366
00:29:14,190 --> 00:29:16,280
Then you will take this Bolton boy, Ramsay,

367
00:29:16,290 --> 00:29:17,520
and make him yours.

368
00:29:18,470 --> 00:29:20,930
- I don't know how to do that. - Of course you do.

369
00:29:21,630 --> 00:29:23,350
He's already fallen for you.

370
00:29:24,110 --> 00:29:26,470
- His father frightens me. - He should.

371
00:29:26,470 --> 00:29:28,100
He's a dangerous man.

372
00:29:29,220 --> 00:29:32,140
But even the most dangerous men can be outmaneuvered.

373
00:29:33,070 --> 00:29:35,630
And you've learned to maneuver from the very best.

374
00:29:37,980 --> 00:29:39,780
I'll return before too long.

375
00:29:40,250 --> 00:29:42,130
You'll be strong without me.

376
00:29:51,170 --> 00:29:52,710
The North will be yours.

377
00:29:54,460 --> 00:29:55,730
Do you believe me?

378
00:29:58,650 --> 00:30:01,650
I expect I'll be a married woman by the time you return.

379
00:31:05,760 --> 00:31:06,970
Breakfast.

380
00:31:11,440 --> 00:31:13,210
That would have been a shit way to die.

381
00:31:13,260 --> 00:31:15,900
As far as I've seen, they're all shit ways to die.

382
00:31:16,480 --> 00:31:19,730
Aye, but your lot have to give the singers a good ending.

383
00:31:19,730 --> 00:31:22,040
I don't care what's sung about me when I'm dead.

384
00:31:22,630 --> 00:31:23,780
No?

385
00:31:24,460 --> 00:31:27,170
Two knights off to rescue a princess.

386
00:31:27,460 --> 00:31:30,760
- Sounds like a good song to me. - Sounds like all the rest.

387
00:31:34,240 --> 00:31:38,250
What about you? What shit way would you choose?

388
00:31:39,680 --> 00:31:42,500
In my own keep drinking my own wine

389
00:31:42,810 --> 00:31:45,180
watching my sons grovel for my fortune.

390
00:31:46,360 --> 00:31:47,830
How disappointing.

391
00:31:48,820 --> 00:31:51,010
I thought you'd have something more exciting planned.

392
00:31:52,200 --> 00:31:55,910
I've had an exciting life. I want my death to be boring.

393
00:31:58,080 --> 00:32:01,850
- How do you want to go? - In the arms of the woman I love.

394
00:32:05,770 --> 00:32:07,100
She want the same thing?

395
00:32:13,230 --> 00:32:14,300
Let's go.

396
00:32:24,740 --> 00:32:26,150
The captain to that ship...

397
00:32:26,730 --> 00:32:29,220
- what was he, Braavosi? - Pentoshi.

398
00:32:30,040 --> 00:32:31,560
And he's headed to Oldtown?

399
00:32:31,560 --> 00:32:32,790
As I said.

400
00:32:32,880 --> 00:32:34,070
Why?

401
00:32:34,350 --> 00:32:36,430
What's to stop him from docking down the coast

402
00:32:36,430 --> 00:32:39,170
and telling the locals that Jaime Lannister's in Dorne?

403
00:32:39,170 --> 00:32:40,510
A bag of gold.

404
00:32:41,510 --> 00:32:42,920
I'm not sure you understand

405
00:32:42,920 --> 00:32:45,700
how much people hate your family in this part of the world.

406
00:32:45,760 --> 00:32:47,120
It was a heavy bag.

407
00:32:47,600 --> 00:32:50,290
And I bet he swore all kinds of oaths to get it.

408
00:32:50,510 --> 00:32:52,760
But you won't be around if he breaks 'em.

409
00:33:02,430 --> 00:33:03,710
How many you count?

410
00:33:03,740 --> 00:33:04,860
Four.

411
00:33:05,080 --> 00:33:06,660
How many do you think you can take?

412
00:33:06,790 --> 00:33:08,770
One if he's slow.

413
00:33:12,550 --> 00:33:13,710
Halt!

414
00:33:14,380 --> 00:33:15,710
Over the hill.

415
00:33:18,420 --> 00:33:19,870
Fucked in the ass.

416
00:33:30,400 --> 00:33:31,570
Morning, lads.

417
00:33:33,020 --> 00:33:34,250
Glad we found you.

418
00:33:35,270 --> 00:33:36,470
Who are you?

419
00:33:36,800 --> 00:33:37,940
Cooper.

420
00:33:38,320 --> 00:33:39,650
This is Darnell.

421
00:33:39,980 --> 00:33:41,580
You're from King's Landing.

422
00:33:41,610 --> 00:33:42,980
Accent gave me away?

423
00:33:44,800 --> 00:33:45,870
Flea Bottom,

424
00:33:45,870 --> 00:33:47,100
whelped and whipped.

425
00:33:47,610 --> 00:33:48,700
Why are you here?

426
00:33:48,700 --> 00:33:50,520
Our ship capsized in the night.

427
00:33:50,520 --> 00:33:52,050
We managed to swim ashore.

428
00:33:52,860 --> 00:33:54,270
It was a near thing, really.

429
00:33:55,120 --> 00:33:56,910
I thought the sharks would get us.

430
00:33:58,240 --> 00:34:00,350
There are no sharks in Dorne.

431
00:34:01,880 --> 00:34:04,010
I could have sworn those were shark fins.

432
00:34:05,480 --> 00:34:06,810
Dolphins, maybe.

433
00:34:08,500 --> 00:34:10,110
Throw your swords in the sand.

434
00:34:10,570 --> 00:34:12,820
Boys, there's no need for this.

435
00:34:12,820 --> 00:34:15,520
Just point us in the right direction,

436
00:34:15,560 --> 00:34:17,130
we'll find our way home.

437
00:34:17,220 --> 00:34:18,720
Swords in the sand

438
00:34:18,820 --> 00:34:19,940
now!

439
00:34:47,340 --> 00:34:48,850
That one should be slow enough.

440
00:35:43,020 --> 00:35:44,130
Nice move!

441
00:35:46,430 --> 00:35:47,520
Luck.

442
00:35:48,440 --> 00:35:50,000
You had a wonderful teacher.

443
00:36:04,110 --> 00:36:06,080
Always wanted a Dornish stallion.

444
00:36:07,190 --> 00:36:10,100
Beasts can run a day and night without tiring.

445
00:36:10,840 --> 00:36:13,920
We'll ride to the Water Gardens with a nice breeze in our face.

446
00:36:13,920 --> 00:36:15,890
But first we need to bury these bodies.

447
00:36:16,720 --> 00:36:18,130
Birds have to eat, too.

448
00:36:18,140 --> 00:36:20,420
Corpses raise questions. Questions raise armies.

449
00:36:20,430 --> 00:36:22,040
We're not here to start a war.

450
00:36:22,990 --> 00:36:25,630
Do you know how long it will take us to dig all those holes?

451
00:36:26,390 --> 00:36:28,790
I can't dig very well with one hand.

452
00:36:29,370 --> 00:36:30,800
Not at all, really.

453
00:37:01,870 --> 00:37:03,050
Mama...

454
00:37:09,570 --> 00:37:12,330
- Nym, Obara. - Will it be war?

455
00:37:12,530 --> 00:37:15,570
Prince Doran will weep for your father, but nothing else.

456
00:37:15,590 --> 00:37:17,760
We must avenge Oberyn ourselves.

457
00:37:18,130 --> 00:37:21,440
Without Doran, we have no army to march against the Lannisters.

458
00:37:22,150 --> 00:37:24,560
We don't need an army to start a war.

459
00:37:25,020 --> 00:37:28,230
Queen Cersei loves her children.

460
00:37:28,560 --> 00:37:30,080
And we have one of them.

461
00:37:30,080 --> 00:37:31,750
You may have a problem.

462
00:37:38,110 --> 00:37:40,230
A ship's captain who found me in Planky Town,

463
00:37:40,230 --> 00:37:42,420
claiming he had information to sell.

464
00:37:42,720 --> 00:37:46,060
He told me he smuggled Jaime Lannister into Dorne.

465
00:37:47,570 --> 00:37:49,090
He's come for Myrcella.

466
00:37:50,450 --> 00:37:52,240
If he gets to her before we do,

467
00:37:52,240 --> 00:37:54,610
we lose our only chance for revenge.

468
00:37:55,400 --> 00:37:57,040
You must choose.

469
00:37:58,170 --> 00:38:00,370
Doran's way and peace,

470
00:38:00,380 --> 00:38:01,520
or my way

471
00:38:02,020 --> 00:38:03,160
and war.

472
00:38:05,910 --> 00:38:07,960
I'm with you always.

473
00:38:08,860 --> 00:38:09,750
Nym?

474
00:38:14,850 --> 00:38:15,970
Obara?

475
00:38:17,460 --> 00:38:20,670
When I was a child, Oberyn came to take me to court.

476
00:38:21,280 --> 00:38:23,240
I had never seen this man, and yet

477
00:38:23,240 --> 00:38:25,380
he called himself my father.

478
00:38:25,780 --> 00:38:29,860
My mother wept, said I was too young and a girl.

479
00:38:32,640 --> 00:38:35,620
Oberyn tossed his spear at my feet and said

480
00:38:35,620 --> 00:38:38,570
"Girl or boy, we fight our battles,

481
00:38:38,570 --> 00:38:41,340
"but the gods let us choose our weapons."

482
00:38:41,900 --> 00:38:44,520
My father pointed to the spear

483
00:38:44,520 --> 00:38:46,820
and then to my mother's tears.

484
00:38:54,080 --> 00:38:55,970
I made my choice long ago.

485
00:38:59,310 --> 00:39:00,830
Will you untie me?

486
00:39:02,310 --> 00:39:04,330
Will you please untie me?

487
00:39:05,310 --> 00:39:06,630
Will you please?

488
00:39:30,210 --> 00:39:31,230
Thank you.

489
00:39:40,080 --> 00:39:41,230
Who are you?

490
00:39:41,830 --> 00:39:43,010
Your captor.

491
00:39:45,730 --> 00:39:46,940
Do you have wine?

492
00:39:47,210 --> 00:39:48,120
No.

493
00:39:49,450 --> 00:39:51,090
Can't sleep without wine.

494
00:39:51,090 --> 00:39:52,410
Then stay awake.

495
00:39:59,010 --> 00:40:00,270
You're going the wrong way.

496
00:40:02,060 --> 00:40:04,510
My sister is in Westeros.

497
00:40:04,510 --> 00:40:07,120
Westeros is west!

498
00:40:07,120 --> 00:40:08,440
We're heading east.

499
00:40:09,050 --> 00:40:10,870
I'm not taking you to your sister.

500
00:40:12,690 --> 00:40:14,850
You said you were taking me to the queen.

501
00:40:14,850 --> 00:40:15,850
I am.

502
00:40:16,130 --> 00:40:18,340
Queen Daenerys Targaryen.

503
00:40:18,340 --> 00:40:20,090
She's the queen I serve.

504
00:40:26,760 --> 00:40:28,880
What a waste of a good kidnapping.

505
00:40:30,090 --> 00:40:32,480
It so happens I was heading there myself.

506
00:40:32,480 --> 00:40:34,660
What business would you have with the queen?

507
00:40:34,660 --> 00:40:36,340
Gold and glory.

508
00:40:36,340 --> 00:40:37,610
Oh, and hate.

509
00:40:38,510 --> 00:40:40,850
If you'd ever met my sister, you'd understand.

510
00:40:42,040 --> 00:40:45,620
So, now that it's clear we're on the same side.

511
00:40:55,690 --> 00:40:58,570
A high born knight from the North of Westeros

512
00:40:58,570 --> 00:41:00,770
down on his luck in Essos.

513
00:41:01,530 --> 00:41:02,890
Dragon epaulets,

514
00:41:03,260 --> 00:41:05,300
bear sigil breast plate.

515
00:41:06,380 --> 00:41:08,080
You're Jorah Mormont.

516
00:41:09,810 --> 00:41:11,100
I have to ask.

517
00:41:11,500 --> 00:41:14,610
How exactly were you serving your queen in a whorehouse

518
00:41:14,610 --> 00:41:16,040
half a world away?

519
00:41:16,770 --> 00:41:19,240
Is it possible that you were running?

520
00:41:20,300 --> 00:41:22,070
Why would you be running?

521
00:41:22,070 --> 00:41:24,090
And why would she have sent you away?

522
00:41:25,010 --> 00:41:26,350
Oh, wait.

523
00:41:27,440 --> 00:41:29,830
You were spying on her, weren't you?

524
00:41:30,800 --> 00:41:32,490
It's all coming back to me.

525
00:41:32,490 --> 00:41:34,430
I was drunk through most of the small council meetings,

526
00:41:34,430 --> 00:41:36,200
but it's all coming back.

527
00:41:36,430 --> 00:41:39,530
You passed notes to Varys's little birds.

528
00:41:41,360 --> 00:41:43,160
She found out, didn't she?

529
00:41:43,800 --> 00:41:45,950
Found out and exiled you.

530
00:41:47,390 --> 00:41:50,640
Now you hope to win back her favor with a gift.

531
00:41:52,140 --> 00:41:53,460
Risky scheme.

532
00:41:54,500 --> 00:41:56,860
One might even say desperate.

533
00:41:58,550 --> 00:42:01,680
You think Daenerys will execute me and pardon you?

534
00:42:03,180 --> 00:42:05,450
I'd say the reverse is just as likely.

535
00:42:27,220 --> 00:42:29,270
Everyone looks happy enough from up here.

536
00:42:31,370 --> 00:42:32,270
What?

537
00:42:33,300 --> 00:42:35,650
I was thinking about all the times your brother

538
00:42:35,650 --> 00:42:37,410
made me go with him down from the Red Keep

539
00:42:37,410 --> 00:42:39,410
into the streets of King's Landing.

540
00:42:39,410 --> 00:42:41,920
- Why? - He liked to walk among the people.

541
00:42:41,920 --> 00:42:43,740
He liked to sing to them.

542
00:42:44,600 --> 00:42:46,780
- He sang to them? - Yes.

543
00:42:47,660 --> 00:42:50,410
Rhaegar would pick a spot on the Hook

544
00:42:50,410 --> 00:42:53,010
or the Street of Seeds and then he'd sing.

545
00:42:53,490 --> 00:42:55,040
Just like all the other minstrels.

546
00:42:55,040 --> 00:42:56,410
And what did you do?

547
00:42:56,410 --> 00:42:58,430
I made sure no one killed him.

548
00:42:58,440 --> 00:43:00,390
And I collected the money.

549
00:43:01,330 --> 00:43:03,470
What? He liked to see how much he could make.

550
00:43:03,470 --> 00:43:05,390
- He was good? - He was very good.

551
00:43:05,390 --> 00:43:06,710
Viserys never told you?

552
00:43:06,710 --> 00:43:09,220
He told me Rhaegar was good at killing people.

553
00:43:10,400 --> 00:43:12,140
Rhaegar never liked killing.

554
00:43:12,140 --> 00:43:13,310
He loved singing.

555
00:43:13,800 --> 00:43:15,350
And what did you do with the money?

556
00:43:15,350 --> 00:43:18,670
Well, one time, he gave it to the next minstrel down the street.

557
00:43:18,670 --> 00:43:21,380
One time, he gave it to an orphanage in Flea Bottom.

558
00:43:21,380 --> 00:43:22,520
One time,

559
00:43:23,430 --> 00:43:25,160
we got horribly drunk.

560
00:43:26,700 --> 00:43:27,680
Your Grace.

561
00:43:29,100 --> 00:43:32,210
Hizdahr is here, waiting in the audience chamber.

562
00:43:33,430 --> 00:43:35,210
How many others are there?

563
00:43:35,210 --> 00:43:37,270
Fifty? A hundred?

564
00:43:37,710 --> 00:43:39,520
Will you be joining us, Ser Barristan?

565
00:43:39,520 --> 00:43:43,080
I think I can protect you from Hizdahr zo Loraq.

566
00:43:43,080 --> 00:43:45,750
I think I can protect me from Hizdahr zo Loraq.

567
00:43:47,000 --> 00:43:48,650
Go, Ser Barristan.

568
00:43:48,650 --> 00:43:50,000
Sing a song for me.

569
00:43:50,590 --> 00:43:51,560
Your Grace.

570
00:43:57,290 --> 00:43:58,920
All men must die,

571
00:43:58,920 --> 00:44:01,600
- but not all can die in glory. - Glory?

572
00:44:01,600 --> 00:44:03,170
Why else do men fight?

573
00:44:03,170 --> 00:44:05,420
Why did your ancestors cross the Narrow Sea

574
00:44:05,420 --> 00:44:06,710
and conquer the Seven Kingdoms?

575
00:44:06,710 --> 00:44:08,830
So their names would live on.

576
00:44:09,250 --> 00:44:10,820
Those who find victory in the fighting pits

577
00:44:10,820 --> 00:44:12,090
will never become kings,

578
00:44:12,090 --> 00:44:14,220
but their names will live on.

579
00:44:14,480 --> 00:44:16,370
It's the best chance they'll ever have.

580
00:44:16,370 --> 00:44:17,500
Is that what you used to tell men

581
00:44:17,500 --> 00:44:20,740
before you set them to butchering each other for sport?

582
00:44:20,740 --> 00:44:23,600
Your Grace, today is the traditional start of the fighting season.

583
00:44:23,600 --> 00:44:25,350
I do not recognize this tradition.

584
00:44:25,350 --> 00:44:27,230
Traditions are the only thing

585
00:44:27,230 --> 00:44:30,380
that will hold this city, your city, together.

586
00:44:32,270 --> 00:44:35,800
Without them, former slaves and former masters have nothing in common.

587
00:44:37,640 --> 00:44:41,320
Nothing but centuries of mistrust and resentment.

588
00:44:42,080 --> 00:44:45,080
I can't promise this is the answer to all our problems,

589
00:44:46,120 --> 00:44:47,500
but it's a start.

