1
00:02:04,100 --> 00:02:06,360
Your Grace, I want to say--

2
00:02:06,370 --> 00:02:07,860
You will not speak.

3
00:02:10,530 --> 00:02:13,010
How do I know you are who you say you are?

4
00:02:13,320 --> 00:02:15,240
If only I were otherwise.

5
00:02:15,240 --> 00:02:18,120
If you are Tyrion Lannister, why shouldn't I kill you

6
00:02:18,120 --> 00:02:20,440
to pay your family back for what it did to mine?

7
00:02:20,440 --> 00:02:22,540
You want revenge against the Lannisters?

8
00:02:23,410 --> 00:02:27,180
I killed my mother Joanna Lannister on the day I was born.

9
00:02:27,290 --> 00:02:31,020
I killed my father Tywin Lannister with a bolt to the heart.

10
00:02:31,210 --> 00:02:33,630
I am the greatest Lannister killer of our time.

11
00:02:33,630 --> 00:02:35,820
So I should welcome you into my service

12
00:02:35,830 --> 00:02:38,480
because you murdered members of your own family?

13
00:02:39,470 --> 00:02:41,550
Into your service?

14
00:02:42,060 --> 00:02:44,720
Your Grace, we have only just met.

15
00:02:44,910 --> 00:02:47,470
It's too soon to know if you deserve my service.

16
00:02:47,470 --> 00:02:49,750
If you'd rather return to the fighting pits,

17
00:02:50,140 --> 00:02:51,630
just say the word.

18
00:02:54,720 --> 00:02:57,050
When I was a young man, I heard a story

19
00:02:57,050 --> 00:02:59,960
about a baby born during the worst storm in living memory.

20
00:03:00,470 --> 00:03:02,970
She had no wealth, no lands, no army,

21
00:03:02,970 --> 00:03:05,890
only a name and a handful of supporters,

22
00:03:05,890 --> 00:03:07,580
most of whom probably thought

23
00:03:07,580 --> 00:03:09,600
they could use that name to benefit themselves.

24
00:03:09,670 --> 00:03:12,230
They kept her alive, moving her from place to place,

25
00:03:12,230 --> 00:03:14,980
often hours ahead of the men who'd been sent to kill her.

26
00:03:15,260 --> 00:03:18,790
She was eventually sold off to some warlord on the edge of the world

27
00:03:18,790 --> 00:03:20,960
and that appeared to be that.

28
00:03:20,960 --> 00:03:22,820
And then a few years later,

29
00:03:22,820 --> 00:03:25,000
the most well-informed person I knew

30
00:03:25,280 --> 00:03:28,260
told me that this girl without wealth, lands, or armies

31
00:03:28,260 --> 00:03:31,500
had somehow acquired all three in a very short span of time,

32
00:03:31,500 --> 00:03:33,910
along with three dragons.

33
00:03:33,920 --> 00:03:38,020
He thought she was our best, last chance to build a better world.

34
00:03:40,230 --> 00:03:42,460
I thought you were worth meeting at the very least.

35
00:03:42,460 --> 00:03:43,980
And why are you worth meeting?

36
00:03:44,130 --> 00:03:46,150
Why should I spend my time listening to you?

37
00:03:46,150 --> 00:03:48,730
Because you cannot build a better world on your own.

38
00:03:49,080 --> 00:03:52,670
You have no one at your side who understands the land you want to rule.

39
00:03:52,790 --> 00:03:54,990
The strengths and weaknesses of the houses

40
00:03:54,990 --> 00:03:56,160
that will either join or oppose you.

41
00:03:56,160 --> 00:03:57,960
I will have a very large army

42
00:03:59,070 --> 00:04:00,480
and very large dragons.

43
00:04:00,480 --> 00:04:03,320
Killing and politics aren't always the same thing.

44
00:04:04,390 --> 00:04:07,420
When I served as Hand of the King, i did quite well with the latter

45
00:04:07,420 --> 00:04:08,690
considering the king in question

46
00:04:08,700 --> 00:04:11,290
preferred torturing animals to leading his people.

47
00:04:12,360 --> 00:04:14,250
I could do an even better job

48
00:04:14,250 --> 00:04:16,590
advising a ruler worth the name.

49
00:04:16,660 --> 00:04:18,890
If that is indeed what you are.

50
00:04:19,210 --> 00:04:20,890
So you want to advise me?

51
00:04:23,600 --> 00:04:24,850
Very well.

52
00:04:26,730 --> 00:04:28,670
What would you have me do with him?

53
00:04:30,290 --> 00:04:33,350
I swore I would kill him if he ever returned.

54
00:04:34,240 --> 00:04:35,370
I know.

55
00:04:39,310 --> 00:04:43,030
Why should the people trust a queen who can't keep her promises?

56
00:04:46,210 --> 00:04:49,240
Whomever Ser Jorah was when he started informing on you,

57
00:04:49,240 --> 00:04:50,930
he is no longer that man.

58
00:04:52,180 --> 00:04:54,070
I can't remember ever seeing a sane man

59
00:04:54,070 --> 00:04:56,570
as devoted to anything as he is to serving you.

60
00:04:56,820 --> 00:04:59,360
He claims he would kill for you and die for you

61
00:04:59,360 --> 00:05:02,390
and nothing I ever witnessed gives me reason to doubt him.

62
00:05:06,830 --> 00:05:08,530
And yet he did betray you.

63
00:05:21,150 --> 00:05:23,940
Did he have an opportunity to confess his betrayal?

64
00:05:23,940 --> 00:05:25,060
Yes.

65
00:05:25,870 --> 00:05:27,660
Many opportunities.

66
00:05:28,510 --> 00:05:29,880
And did he?

67
00:05:30,510 --> 00:05:34,610
No, not until forced to do so.

68
00:05:39,920 --> 00:05:41,190
He worships you.

69
00:05:42,070 --> 00:05:43,850
He is in love with you, I think.

70
00:05:44,680 --> 00:05:46,870
But he did not trust you with the truth.

71
00:05:46,870 --> 00:05:48,470
An unpleasant truth to be sure,

72
00:05:48,470 --> 00:05:50,500
but one of great significance to you.

73
00:05:51,200 --> 00:05:53,930
He did not trust that you would be wise enough to forgive him.

74
00:05:55,280 --> 00:05:56,950
So I should kill him?

75
00:05:58,230 --> 00:06:00,520
A ruler who kills those devoted to her

76
00:06:00,520 --> 00:06:02,660
is not a ruler who inspires devotion.

77
00:06:03,300 --> 00:06:05,500
And you're going to need to inspire devotion,

78
00:06:05,500 --> 00:06:09,320
a lot of it, if you're ever going to rule across the Narrow Sea.

79
00:06:10,980 --> 00:06:14,100
But you cannot have him by your side when you do.

80
00:06:19,570 --> 00:06:21,780
Remove Ser Jorah from the city.

81
00:07:33,250 --> 00:07:34,560
Confess.

82
00:07:35,690 --> 00:07:36,820
My son.

83
00:07:38,780 --> 00:07:39,910
Let me speak to--

84
00:07:40,850 --> 00:07:42,070
Confess.

85
00:07:42,340 --> 00:07:43,710
I meant it.

86
00:07:44,630 --> 00:07:46,870
My face will be the last thing you see--

87
00:08:04,530 --> 00:08:08,020
My name is Lanna. I'm an orphan.

88
00:08:09,730 --> 00:08:11,550
When I was eight, I begged enough money

89
00:08:11,550 --> 00:08:13,580
to buy my first bucket of oysters.

90
00:08:13,740 --> 00:08:17,010
I sold that bucket and made enough money to buy two more.

91
00:08:20,240 --> 00:08:23,400
It took a while, but I finally saved enough

92
00:08:23,400 --> 00:08:25,180
to buy myself an oyster cart.

93
00:08:26,640 --> 00:08:27,860
Now every morning,

94
00:08:27,860 --> 00:08:29,750
I make my way down to the canals.

95
00:08:31,800 --> 00:08:34,850
I pass the fish mongers and the bakers.

96
00:08:39,950 --> 00:08:41,480
I usually see Lhara,

97
00:08:41,480 --> 00:08:43,880
my first customer of the day on her way home.

98
00:08:45,950 --> 00:08:49,870
Then I turn left onto Moonsinger Lane...

99
00:08:52,080 --> 00:08:54,650
turn left onto Ragman Lane

100
00:08:55,060 --> 00:08:56,900
where I do most of my trade.

101
00:08:57,010 --> 00:08:58,860
Lanna is very impressive.

102
00:08:58,970 --> 00:09:00,680
Very industrious.

103
00:09:01,390 --> 00:09:04,380
She will make a fine servant for the Many-Faced God.

104
00:09:04,730 --> 00:09:06,400
How will she serve him?

105
00:09:06,400 --> 00:09:09,210
She will no longer turn left onto Ragman Lane.

106
00:09:09,620 --> 00:09:12,320
She will turn right and go to Ragman Harbor.

107
00:09:12,330 --> 00:09:14,020
What will she do there?

108
00:09:14,200 --> 00:09:15,620
She will see.

109
00:09:16,850 --> 00:09:18,370
See what?

110
00:09:18,920 --> 00:09:20,990
How can a man tell a girl this?

111
00:09:21,500 --> 00:09:22,790
If he knew what she would see,

112
00:09:22,790 --> 00:09:24,650
there would be no reason to send her.

113
00:09:25,000 --> 00:09:27,980
Oysters, clams, and cockles!

114
00:09:45,250 --> 00:09:48,230
Oysters, clams, and cockles!

115
00:09:56,240 --> 00:09:59,100
Oysters, clams, and cockles!

116
00:09:59,810 --> 00:10:01,450
Your oysters fresh?

117
00:10:03,240 --> 00:10:04,560
Best in the city.

118
00:10:04,570 --> 00:10:06,650
You wouldn't lie to an old man, would you?

119
00:10:21,780 --> 00:10:25,280
Very nice. Give me four with vinegar.

120
00:10:28,760 --> 00:10:30,400
It's my 18th voyage.

121
00:10:30,620 --> 00:10:33,040
Returned from all of them without a scratch on me.

122
00:10:39,870 --> 00:10:40,990
Can't do it.

123
00:10:42,260 --> 00:10:44,390
Please, I've three children.

124
00:10:44,390 --> 00:10:45,680
Without me...

125
00:10:45,710 --> 00:10:47,560
Here, take it. You have to.

126
00:10:47,560 --> 00:10:49,050
I've three children.

127
00:10:49,230 --> 00:10:50,770
- What will they do? - Come on.

128
00:10:50,770 --> 00:10:52,660
They've nothing without me.

129
00:10:52,670 --> 00:10:54,120
Please, you have to!

130
00:10:54,120 --> 00:10:56,300
Please, you don't understand!

131
00:10:56,640 --> 00:10:57,780
Please!

132
00:11:04,500 --> 00:11:06,260
The man is a gambler.

133
00:11:07,550 --> 00:11:11,490
He wages that a sailor's ship will make it to its destination.

134
00:11:12,600 --> 00:11:14,890
It is a strange wager for the captain.

135
00:11:15,120 --> 00:11:17,520
He only wins if he loses his life.

136
00:11:19,960 --> 00:11:23,050
So why would a captain make the wager in the first place?

137
00:11:24,740 --> 00:11:27,030
A girl tells a man that she has seen.

138
00:11:29,970 --> 00:11:31,580
If the captain dies,

139
00:11:32,190 --> 00:11:34,570
the thin man pays his family a lot of money.

140
00:11:36,800 --> 00:11:39,740
But perhaps the gambler loses his bet

141
00:11:39,740 --> 00:11:42,030
and decides he does not have to pay after all.

142
00:11:42,340 --> 00:11:44,500
A destitute woman and her small child,

143
00:11:44,500 --> 00:11:47,760
what can they do to such a man if he keeps their money for himself?

144
00:11:50,270 --> 00:11:52,840
To whom can they turn for recourse?

145
00:11:59,060 --> 00:12:00,610
The Many-Faced God.

146
00:12:02,650 --> 00:12:04,870
You said you didn't know what I would see at the docks.

147
00:12:04,880 --> 00:12:07,890
A man had no idea what a girl would see and what she would not.

148
00:12:10,120 --> 00:12:12,730
A girl named Lanna will return to the docks.

149
00:12:13,180 --> 00:12:14,760
She will watch the gambler.

150
00:12:14,760 --> 00:12:16,300
She will come to know as much about him

151
00:12:16,300 --> 00:12:17,910
as she knows about herself.

152
00:12:17,970 --> 00:12:19,290
And then what?

153
00:12:20,230 --> 00:12:24,310
A gift for the thin man.

154
00:12:44,060 --> 00:12:45,400
She's not ready.

155
00:12:46,560 --> 00:12:49,000
Perhaps she is, perhaps she's not.

156
00:12:49,250 --> 00:12:50,720
And if she's not?

157
00:12:51,650 --> 00:12:54,300
It is all the same to the Many-Faced God.

158
00:13:17,640 --> 00:13:20,220
The trial will take place soon.

159
00:13:20,220 --> 00:13:23,830
The High Sparrow will be presenting a substantial case against you.

160
00:13:23,830 --> 00:13:24,940
The charges?

161
00:13:24,940 --> 00:13:27,590
Fornication, treason, incest,

162
00:13:27,590 --> 00:13:29,250
the murder of King Robert.

163
00:13:29,250 --> 00:13:30,370
All lies.

164
00:13:30,370 --> 00:13:31,720
Of course, Your Grace.

165
00:13:36,360 --> 00:13:40,270
My concern is that the Faith does not adhere

166
00:13:40,280 --> 00:13:43,850
to the same standards of proof as the Crown.

167
00:13:43,850 --> 00:13:45,730
I hope you'll excuse me for saying it,

168
00:13:45,730 --> 00:13:48,550
but belief is so often the death of reason.

169
00:13:48,550 --> 00:13:50,400
I wish you had said it sooner.

170
00:13:53,190 --> 00:13:54,800
Is there any word from Jaime?

171
00:13:55,090 --> 00:13:56,730
No, I'm afraid not.

172
00:14:03,390 --> 00:14:06,850
Your Grace, Grand Maester Pycelle

173
00:14:07,760 --> 00:14:11,270
has summoned your Uncle Kevan back from Casterly Rock

174
00:14:11,270 --> 00:14:12,970
to serve as Hand of the King.

175
00:14:12,970 --> 00:14:15,580
He now presides over the small council.

176
00:14:16,960 --> 00:14:19,240
Tell him I need to speak to him.

177
00:14:19,240 --> 00:14:21,560
I implored him to visit you, but he would not.

178
00:14:26,190 --> 00:14:28,340
What about my son, the king?

179
00:14:29,080 --> 00:14:31,410
If you can visit me, then surely the king...

180
00:14:31,420 --> 00:14:33,770
Your arrest and Queen Margaery's arrest,

181
00:14:33,770 --> 00:14:35,330
the king has not taken them well.

182
00:14:35,330 --> 00:14:36,800
He remains in his chambers.

183
00:14:36,800 --> 00:14:40,540
His servants often find his food in the hall left untouched.

184
00:14:40,550 --> 00:14:42,430
You need to talk to him.

185
00:14:42,430 --> 00:14:44,740
You need to talk to my son and tell him to come and see me,

186
00:14:44,740 --> 00:14:45,960
come and see his mother.

187
00:14:45,960 --> 00:14:48,620
He-- I tried, Your Grace.

188
00:14:48,920 --> 00:14:51,070
He wouldn't see me. He won't see anyone.

189
00:14:52,640 --> 00:14:54,170
I can't stay here.

190
00:14:55,540 --> 00:14:58,910
There is a way, Your Grace.

191
00:15:02,870 --> 00:15:04,200
A way out.

192
00:15:06,730 --> 00:15:07,890
Confess?

193
00:15:09,470 --> 00:15:10,970
To the High Sparrow?

194
00:15:10,970 --> 00:15:12,540
I won't.

195
00:15:13,440 --> 00:15:15,050
I made him.

196
00:15:16,400 --> 00:15:18,260
I rose him up from nothing.

197
00:15:18,260 --> 00:15:20,910
I will not kneel before some barefooted commoner

198
00:15:20,910 --> 00:15:22,500
and beg his forgiveness.

199
00:15:30,480 --> 00:15:31,760
Good-bye, my queen.

200
00:15:34,430 --> 00:15:36,130
The work continues.

201
00:16:12,050 --> 00:16:13,100
Why?

202
00:16:15,480 --> 00:16:16,910
Why, Theon?

203
00:16:17,000 --> 00:16:20,170
I'm not Theon. There is no Theon.

204
00:16:20,170 --> 00:16:21,720
- Reek. - Reek.

205
00:16:21,720 --> 00:16:23,770
Why did you tell him, Reek?

206
00:16:25,390 --> 00:16:26,880
I was helping you.

207
00:16:27,570 --> 00:16:29,090
You wanted to escape.

208
00:16:29,090 --> 00:16:30,700
There is no escape.

209
00:16:32,190 --> 00:16:33,420
Not ever.

210
00:16:34,490 --> 00:16:36,640
Theon Greyjoy tried to escape.

211
00:16:38,110 --> 00:16:39,540
The master knew.

212
00:16:40,820 --> 00:16:42,370
He knows everything.

213
00:16:43,590 --> 00:16:45,810
He hunted him and caught him

214
00:16:45,810 --> 00:16:47,360
and strapped him to a cross

215
00:16:48,340 --> 00:16:50,330
and cut away piece after piece

216
00:16:50,550 --> 00:16:52,740
until there was no Theon left.

217
00:16:57,210 --> 00:16:58,360
Good.

218
00:17:01,610 --> 00:17:05,200
If it weren't for you, I'd still have a family.

219
00:17:05,890 --> 00:17:09,430
If I could do what Ramsay did to you right here, right now,

220
00:17:09,480 --> 00:17:11,140
I would.

221
00:17:15,540 --> 00:17:17,190
I deserved everything.

222
00:17:19,600 --> 00:17:21,560
I deserve to be Reek.

223
00:17:22,970 --> 00:17:24,640
I did terrible things.

224
00:17:27,020 --> 00:17:28,310
Turned on Robb.

225
00:17:29,550 --> 00:17:31,040
Captured Winterfell.

226
00:17:32,690 --> 00:17:33,620
Killed those boys.

227
00:17:33,620 --> 00:17:34,770
They weren't "Those boys."

228
00:17:34,770 --> 00:17:37,230
They were Bran and Rickon. They were your brothers.

229
00:17:37,230 --> 00:17:38,840
You've known them since they were born.

230
00:17:38,840 --> 00:17:40,250
They weren't. They were only--

231
00:17:40,280 --> 00:17:41,660
Only what?

232
00:17:42,710 --> 00:17:43,910
- I can't. - Tell me.

233
00:17:43,910 --> 00:17:45,510
I can't, not unless the master says.

234
00:17:45,520 --> 00:17:47,110
- Tell me. They weren't what? - They weren't--

235
00:17:47,110 --> 00:17:49,530
Tell me why Bran and Rickon should be gone

236
00:17:49,530 --> 00:17:51,240
while you still breathe the air.

237
00:17:51,240 --> 00:17:52,780
Tell me to my face, Theon.

238
00:17:52,790 --> 00:17:54,360
Tell me that they weren't your brothers!

239
00:17:54,370 --> 00:17:55,820
They weren't Bran and Rickon!

240
00:17:58,210 --> 00:17:59,590
I couldn't find them.

241
00:18:07,150 --> 00:18:08,600
It was two farm boys.

242
00:18:13,130 --> 00:18:15,660
I killed them and burned them so no one would know.

243
00:18:20,590 --> 00:18:21,730
You didn't?

244
00:18:23,790 --> 00:18:25,610
Do you know where they went, Bran and Rickon?

245
00:18:25,620 --> 00:18:26,940
I can't talk to you anymore.

246
00:18:26,940 --> 00:18:27,870
Theon, you have to tell me.

247
00:18:27,870 --> 00:18:28,890
Do you have any idea where--

248
00:18:28,890 --> 00:18:30,700
Not Theon! Reek!

249
00:18:36,680 --> 00:18:39,740
Our scouts tell us he's got no more than 6,000 men.

250
00:18:40,120 --> 00:18:42,410
More than half of those are mounted, however.

251
00:18:42,410 --> 00:18:44,580
And how high do Stannis's horses jump?

252
00:18:45,360 --> 00:18:47,480
Our walls have been fully repaired.

253
00:18:47,730 --> 00:18:49,570
The gates have been reinforced.

254
00:18:49,880 --> 00:18:51,800
We have enough food for six months.

255
00:18:52,800 --> 00:18:55,840
We are more prepared for a siege than they could ever be.

256
00:18:56,870 --> 00:18:59,140
All we have to do is wait for them to freeze,

257
00:18:59,370 --> 00:19:02,070
starve, and mutiny.

258
00:19:05,350 --> 00:19:06,580
You disagree?

259
00:19:06,580 --> 00:19:08,730
Stannis isn't from the North.

260
00:19:08,820 --> 00:19:10,120
You are, Father.

261
00:19:10,990 --> 00:19:14,080
I think you're missing an opportunity to show the people of the North

262
00:19:14,080 --> 00:19:17,100
how House Bolton treats southern invaders.

263
00:19:17,100 --> 00:19:18,160
And what do you recommend?

264
00:19:18,160 --> 00:19:19,570
That we not sit and wait for Stannis

265
00:19:19,570 --> 00:19:21,830
to decide what sort of fight this is going to be.

266
00:19:21,830 --> 00:19:24,370
That we hit first and hit hard

267
00:19:24,370 --> 00:19:26,490
and leave a feast for the crows.

268
00:19:26,490 --> 00:19:29,860
A smart commander does not abandon a defensive advantage.

269
00:19:30,070 --> 00:19:31,980
As long as we stay behind these walls,

270
00:19:31,980 --> 00:19:33,140
they can't touch us.

271
00:19:33,230 --> 00:19:35,040
Not to mention that the snow is so deep,

272
00:19:35,040 --> 00:19:37,010
we couldn't get an army through to engage them

273
00:19:37,010 --> 00:19:38,340
even if we wanted to.

274
00:19:38,340 --> 00:19:39,730
I don't need an army.

275
00:19:40,840 --> 00:19:42,650
I need 20 good men.

276
00:19:51,240 --> 00:19:52,710
So, have you decided yet?

277
00:19:52,940 --> 00:19:55,210
Whether I'm worthy of your service?

278
00:19:57,620 --> 00:20:00,860
Have you decided yet whether you're going to have me killed?

279
00:20:00,860 --> 00:20:02,590
It's probably my safest option.

280
00:20:05,890 --> 00:20:07,710
I can see why you would think so.

281
00:20:08,350 --> 00:20:10,310
It's what your father would have done.

282
00:20:11,440 --> 00:20:13,140
And what would your father have done?

283
00:20:15,140 --> 00:20:16,420
My father,

284
00:20:16,890 --> 00:20:19,310
who publically sentenced me to death?

285
00:20:19,640 --> 00:20:22,610
I'd say his thoughts on having me killed were abundantly clear.

286
00:20:22,610 --> 00:20:24,010
Is that why you killed him?

287
00:20:27,380 --> 00:20:30,020
Someday, if you decide not to execute me,

288
00:20:30,640 --> 00:20:32,950
I'll tell you all about why I killed my father.

289
00:20:32,990 --> 00:20:35,180
And on that day, should it ever come,

290
00:20:36,400 --> 00:20:38,260
we'll need more wine than this.

291
00:20:40,850 --> 00:20:42,450
I know what my father was.

292
00:20:43,390 --> 00:20:44,590
What he did.

293
00:20:45,860 --> 00:20:47,950
I know the Mad King earned his name.

294
00:20:50,950 --> 00:20:53,450
So, here we sit.

295
00:20:54,040 --> 00:20:57,090
Two terrible children of two terrible fathers.

296
00:20:57,090 --> 00:20:58,280
I'm terrible?

297
00:20:58,670 --> 00:21:00,100
I've heard stories.

298
00:21:00,700 --> 00:21:04,160
Why did you travel to the far side of the world to meet someone terrible?

299
00:21:04,160 --> 00:21:06,180
To see if you were the right kind of terrible.

300
00:21:06,180 --> 00:21:07,130
Which kind is that?

301
00:21:07,130 --> 00:21:09,900
The kind that prevents your people from being even more so.

302
00:21:12,020 --> 00:21:14,170
Well, I did reopen the fighting pits.

303
00:21:14,170 --> 00:21:17,030
Under my rule, murder will once again become entertainment.

304
00:21:17,030 --> 00:21:18,570
Yes, that was wise.

305
00:21:18,840 --> 00:21:22,240
And you agreed to marry someone you loathe for the greater good.

306
00:21:22,460 --> 00:21:23,890
Very impressive.

307
00:21:24,890 --> 00:21:27,460
My own sister married someone she loathed as well,

308
00:21:27,820 --> 00:21:29,080
though not by choice and

309
00:21:29,150 --> 00:21:31,670
certainly not for the greater good, gods forbid.

310
00:21:32,190 --> 00:21:34,070
She ended up having him killed.

311
00:21:35,920 --> 00:21:38,140
Perhaps it won't come to that.

312
00:21:45,680 --> 00:21:48,820
It's not impossible that Varys was right about you after all.

313
00:21:48,820 --> 00:21:51,980
Varys? King Robert's spymaster?

314
00:21:51,980 --> 00:21:54,880
Yes, he's the one who convinced me to come find you.

315
00:21:55,570 --> 00:21:57,280
He was my travelling companion

316
00:21:57,280 --> 00:21:59,550
before Ser Jorah seized that role for himself.

317
00:21:59,550 --> 00:22:01,690
Jorah sent my secrets to Varys.

318
00:22:02,670 --> 00:22:06,460
For 20 years the Spider oversaw the campaign to find and kill me.

319
00:22:06,460 --> 00:22:08,690
He did what he had to do to survive.

320
00:22:08,830 --> 00:22:11,650
He did a lot of other things as well, things he didn't have to do.

321
00:22:12,020 --> 00:22:15,720
I suspect he's the main reason you weren't slaughtered in your crib.

322
00:22:16,790 --> 00:22:17,990
But you trust him?

323
00:22:17,990 --> 00:22:19,250
Yes, oddly.

324
00:22:19,280 --> 00:22:21,860
He may be the only person in the world I trust.

325
00:22:22,910 --> 00:22:24,440
Except my brother.

326
00:22:24,940 --> 00:22:26,960
The brother who killed my father?

327
00:22:27,460 --> 00:22:28,750
That's the one.

328
00:22:28,750 --> 00:22:30,370
Perhaps I will have you killed after all.

329
00:22:30,370 --> 00:22:32,320
Your queenly prerogative.

330
00:22:35,040 --> 00:22:36,540
I had given up on life

331
00:22:37,350 --> 00:22:40,640
until Varys convinced me you might be worth living for.

332
00:22:40,900 --> 00:22:43,050
If you chop off my head, well,

333
00:22:43,120 --> 00:22:45,200
my final days were interesting.

334
00:22:51,690 --> 00:22:53,190
I'm not going to kill you.

335
00:22:55,740 --> 00:22:58,430
No? Banish me?

336
00:22:58,430 --> 00:22:59,580
No.

337
00:22:59,950 --> 00:23:01,780
So if I'm not going to be murdered

338
00:23:01,780 --> 00:23:03,200
and I'm not going to be banished--

339
00:23:03,200 --> 00:23:04,850
You're going to advise me.

340
00:23:06,250 --> 00:23:08,720
While you can still speak in complete sentences.

341
00:23:12,970 --> 00:23:14,140
Advise you on what?

342
00:23:14,140 --> 00:23:15,680
How to get what I want.

343
00:23:15,720 --> 00:23:17,630
The Iron Throne.

344
00:23:19,100 --> 00:23:21,450
Perhaps you should try wanting something else.

345
00:23:21,450 --> 00:23:23,950
If I want jokes, I'll get myself a proper fool.

346
00:23:24,040 --> 00:23:25,700
I'm not entirely joking.

347
00:23:26,140 --> 00:23:28,520
There's more to the world than Westeros after all.

348
00:23:28,770 --> 00:23:30,210
How many hundreds of thousands of lives

349
00:23:30,210 --> 00:23:32,020
have you changed for the better here?

350
00:23:33,030 --> 00:23:34,810
Perhaps this is where you belong,

351
00:23:34,810 --> 00:23:36,640
where you can do the most good.

352
00:23:39,130 --> 00:23:41,870
I fought so that no child born into Slaver's Bay

353
00:23:41,870 --> 00:23:44,840
would ever know what it meant to be bought or sold.

354
00:23:44,930 --> 00:23:47,710
I will continue that fight here and beyond.

355
00:23:48,660 --> 00:23:50,280
But this is not my home.

356
00:23:50,450 --> 00:23:53,160
When you get back to your home, who supports you?

357
00:23:53,160 --> 00:23:54,500
The common people.

358
00:23:54,570 --> 00:23:57,190
Let's be generous and assume that's going to happen.

359
00:23:57,250 --> 00:23:59,660
Here in Slaver's Bay, you had the support of the common people

360
00:23:59,660 --> 00:24:01,540
and only the common people.

361
00:24:02,220 --> 00:24:05,700
What was that like? Ruling without the rich?

362
00:24:06,310 --> 00:24:08,410
House Targaryen is gone.

363
00:24:08,540 --> 00:24:11,640
Not a single person who shares your blood is alive to support you.

364
00:24:11,780 --> 00:24:13,390
The Starks are gone as well.

365
00:24:13,430 --> 00:24:15,390
Our two terrible fathers saw to that.

366
00:24:15,390 --> 00:24:16,910
The remaining members of House Lannister

367
00:24:16,910 --> 00:24:18,920
will never back you, not ever.

368
00:24:19,270 --> 00:24:21,270
Stannis Baratheon won't back you, either.

369
00:24:21,620 --> 00:24:22,640
His entire claim to the throne

370
00:24:22,640 --> 00:24:24,850
rests on the illegitimacy of yours.

371
00:24:25,020 --> 00:24:26,990
That leaves the Tyrells.

372
00:24:26,990 --> 00:24:29,680
Not impossible, not enough.

373
00:24:29,680 --> 00:24:31,020
Lannister, Targaryen,

374
00:24:31,020 --> 00:24:33,160
Baratheon, Stark, Tyrell.

375
00:24:34,120 --> 00:24:35,970
They're all just spokes on a wheel.

376
00:24:36,020 --> 00:24:38,380
This one's on top, then that one's on top.

377
00:24:38,380 --> 00:24:40,260
And on and on it spins,

378
00:24:40,260 --> 00:24:42,220
crushing those on the ground.

379
00:24:42,680 --> 00:24:45,680
It's a beautiful dream, stopping the wheel.

380
00:24:46,650 --> 00:24:49,110
You're not the first person who's ever dreamt it.

381
00:24:50,090 --> 00:24:52,040
I'm not going to stop the wheel.

382
00:24:53,730 --> 00:24:55,780
I'm going to break the wheel.

383
00:25:18,490 --> 00:25:22,100
You said whoever wins will fight at the Great Pit in front of the queen.

384
00:25:22,640 --> 00:25:24,010
I won.

385
00:25:24,400 --> 00:25:26,600
- You struck me. - Have me flogged

386
00:25:26,600 --> 00:25:27,820
if it makes you happy.

387
00:25:27,820 --> 00:25:29,510
But I'm the best you've got.

388
00:25:31,320 --> 00:25:33,370
If I win at the Great Pit,

389
00:25:34,150 --> 00:25:35,980
how much can you sell me for?

390
00:25:38,680 --> 00:25:39,980
You're a free man.

391
00:25:40,430 --> 00:25:42,240
You could have gone anywhere.

392
00:25:42,650 --> 00:25:44,600
Why did you come back?

393
00:25:49,100 --> 00:25:50,500
Let me fight for her

394
00:25:51,020 --> 00:25:52,750
and I belong to you.

395
00:25:58,450 --> 00:25:59,610
Thirsty?

396
00:26:01,570 --> 00:26:02,820
Confess.

397
00:26:06,750 --> 00:26:09,910
I'll get out of here, you realize, before long.

398
00:26:09,910 --> 00:26:10,990
Confess.

399
00:26:11,000 --> 00:26:13,170
I can make you a wealthy woman.

400
00:26:14,860 --> 00:26:16,420
A lady of the court.

401
00:26:16,420 --> 00:26:17,730
Confess.

402
00:26:22,210 --> 00:26:23,320
Or I can make sure you die

403
00:26:23,320 --> 00:26:26,100
in the most hideous way imaginable.

404
00:26:26,100 --> 00:26:28,110
And all I do is sit here

405
00:26:28,160 --> 00:26:31,130
imagining hideous ways for you to die.

406
00:27:16,830 --> 00:27:18,130
Does it hurt?

407
00:27:20,140 --> 00:27:21,280
No.

408
00:27:22,420 --> 00:27:23,680
Good.

409
00:27:27,650 --> 00:27:28,830
How are you?

410
00:27:29,850 --> 00:27:33,100
I'm not the one who got punched and kicked in the face.

411
00:27:35,260 --> 00:27:36,640
You know what I mean.

412
00:27:39,210 --> 00:27:40,370
I'm good.

413
00:27:41,200 --> 00:27:43,930
- Are you scared? - A little.

414
00:27:44,300 --> 00:27:45,620
Me, too.

415
00:27:49,660 --> 00:27:51,380
- Who's there? - Olly.

416
00:27:53,910 --> 00:27:55,190
Come in.

417
00:27:58,160 --> 00:27:59,640
I heard what happened.

418
00:27:59,680 --> 00:28:02,040
Oh, not to worry.

419
00:28:02,650 --> 00:28:05,600
Men brawl from time to time. It's only natural.

420
00:28:08,630 --> 00:28:10,030
Figured you were hungry.

421
00:28:11,820 --> 00:28:13,270
Oh, you're a good lad.

422
00:28:15,570 --> 00:28:17,010
Wanted to ask you something

423
00:28:17,850 --> 00:28:19,310
if you've got the time.

424
00:28:19,650 --> 00:28:21,530
I need to check on baby Sam.

425
00:28:29,030 --> 00:28:32,230
Now then, how can I help?

426
00:28:33,370 --> 00:28:35,660
- It's about the Lord Commander. - Yes?

427
00:28:35,720 --> 00:28:38,790
He's going up to Hardhome to save all them wildlings.

428
00:28:40,840 --> 00:28:43,080
Wildlings killed my mom and dad.

429
00:28:44,070 --> 00:28:45,730
They killed everyone in my village.

430
00:28:45,730 --> 00:28:47,470
We've been fighting them for years.

431
00:28:47,470 --> 00:28:48,920
This wasn't a fight.

432
00:28:48,920 --> 00:28:50,300
We were farmers

433
00:28:50,990 --> 00:28:52,620
and they slaughtered us.

434
00:28:53,950 --> 00:28:55,430
So why is he saving them?

435
00:28:56,090 --> 00:28:57,640
Wildlings are people.

436
00:28:58,740 --> 00:29:01,600
Just like us, there are good ones and bad ones.

437
00:29:01,600 --> 00:29:04,660
The one he's travelling with, the one with the red beard,

438
00:29:05,190 --> 00:29:07,230
he led the raid on my village.

439
00:29:07,230 --> 00:29:09,420
- Oh, Olly. - How can he trust him?

440
00:29:10,740 --> 00:29:13,300
I've seen the army of the dead.

441
00:29:14,380 --> 00:29:16,770
I've seen the white walkers.

442
00:29:16,820 --> 00:29:19,210
And they're coming for us, for all the living.

443
00:29:21,770 --> 00:29:23,010
And when it's time,

444
00:29:24,770 --> 00:29:27,350
we'll need every last man we can find.

445
00:29:27,970 --> 00:29:30,620
But what if we let the wildlings through the gates

446
00:29:30,630 --> 00:29:32,730
and they cut our throats while we sleep?

447
00:29:32,730 --> 00:29:35,080
Jon's taking a risk, but he has to.

448
00:29:35,080 --> 00:29:37,450
We don't stand a chance otherwise.

449
00:29:38,410 --> 00:29:41,720
Sometimes a man has to make hard choices,

450
00:29:41,730 --> 00:29:43,600
choices that might look wrong to others,

451
00:29:43,610 --> 00:29:46,360
but you know are right in the long run.

452
00:29:46,710 --> 00:29:48,220
You believe that?

453
00:29:48,280 --> 00:29:50,060
With all my heart.

454
00:29:57,400 --> 00:29:58,740
Try not to worry, Olly.

455
00:29:59,030 --> 00:30:01,020
I've been worrying about Jon for years.

456
00:30:02,660 --> 00:30:04,260
He always comes back.

457
00:30:46,750 --> 00:30:48,020
Turn us about!

458
00:31:21,070 --> 00:31:22,560
You trust me, Jon Snow?

459
00:31:24,090 --> 00:31:25,530
Does that make me a fool?

460
00:31:26,150 --> 00:31:27,810
We're fools together now.

461
00:31:44,520 --> 00:31:45,710
Lord of Bones.

462
00:31:48,070 --> 00:31:49,390
Been a long time.

463
00:31:50,070 --> 00:31:52,970
Last time I saw you, the little crow was your prisoner.

464
00:31:52,980 --> 00:31:55,690
The other way around now. What happened?

465
00:31:55,990 --> 00:31:57,040
War.

466
00:31:57,120 --> 00:31:59,630
War? You call that a war?

467
00:31:59,940 --> 00:32:02,160
The greatest army the North has ever seen

468
00:32:02,170 --> 00:32:05,100
cut to pieces by some southern king.

469
00:32:05,300 --> 00:32:06,960
We should gather the elders,

470
00:32:07,530 --> 00:32:09,390
find somewhere quiet to talk.

471
00:32:09,390 --> 00:32:11,080
You don't give the orders here.

472
00:32:11,080 --> 00:32:13,070
I'm not giving an order.

473
00:32:15,010 --> 00:32:16,910
Why aren't you in chains?

474
00:32:17,850 --> 00:32:19,260
He's not my prisoner.

475
00:32:20,250 --> 00:32:21,290
No?

476
00:32:21,660 --> 00:32:22,820
What is he?

477
00:32:23,220 --> 00:32:24,510
We're allies.

478
00:32:26,960 --> 00:32:29,000
You fucking traitor.

479
00:32:32,280 --> 00:32:34,110
You fight for the crows now?

480
00:32:36,420 --> 00:32:38,640
I don't fight for the crows.

481
00:32:40,330 --> 00:32:43,690
We're not here to fight. We're here to talk.

482
00:32:43,880 --> 00:32:45,130
Is that right?

483
00:32:46,270 --> 00:32:49,420
You and the pretty crow do a lot of talking, Tormund?

484
00:32:49,930 --> 00:32:51,630
And when you're done talking,

485
00:32:51,830 --> 00:32:54,780
do you get down on your knees and suck his cock?

486
00:33:10,100 --> 00:33:13,260
Gather the elders and let's talk.

487
00:33:39,250 --> 00:33:40,680
My name's Jon Snow.

488
00:33:43,120 --> 00:33:45,170
I'm Lord Commander of the Night's Watch.

489
00:33:48,590 --> 00:33:49,810
We're not friends.

490
00:33:51,030 --> 00:33:52,550
We've never been friends.

491
00:33:54,120 --> 00:33:55,940
We won't become friends today.

492
00:33:57,750 --> 00:33:59,460
This isn't about friendship.

493
00:34:01,980 --> 00:34:03,680
This is about survival.

494
00:34:03,910 --> 00:34:05,850
This is about putting a 700-foot wall

495
00:34:05,860 --> 00:34:08,110
between you and what's out there.

496
00:34:08,110 --> 00:34:10,190
You built that wall to keep us out.

497
00:34:10,190 --> 00:34:13,300
Since when do the crows give two shits if we live?

498
00:34:13,300 --> 00:34:16,540
In normal times we wouldn't. But these aren't normal times.

499
00:34:16,570 --> 00:34:19,820
The white walkers don't care if a man's free folk or crow.

500
00:34:19,820 --> 00:34:22,110
We're all the same to them, meat for their army.

501
00:34:22,910 --> 00:34:25,590
But together we can beat them.

502
00:34:25,590 --> 00:34:27,260
Beat the white walkers?

503
00:34:27,420 --> 00:34:30,160
Good luck with that. Run from them, maybe.

504
00:34:40,130 --> 00:34:41,380
It's not a trick.

505
00:34:44,900 --> 00:34:47,830
It's a gift for those who join us.

506
00:34:52,880 --> 00:34:54,100
Dragonglass.

507
00:34:55,780 --> 00:34:58,880
A man of the Night's Watch used one of these daggers

508
00:34:58,880 --> 00:35:00,130
to kill a walker.

509
00:35:01,070 --> 00:35:02,930
- You saw this? - No.

510
00:35:03,400 --> 00:35:04,730
But I trust the man.

511
00:35:04,780 --> 00:35:07,370
There are old stories about dragonglass.

512
00:35:07,430 --> 00:35:11,110
There are old stories about ice spiders as big as hounds.

513
00:35:11,110 --> 00:35:13,480
And with the things we've seen, you don't believe them?

514
00:35:13,780 --> 00:35:16,160
Come with me and I'll share these weapons.

515
00:35:16,160 --> 00:35:17,550
Come with you where?

516
00:35:17,680 --> 00:35:19,440
There are good lands south of the Wall.

517
00:35:19,440 --> 00:35:21,320
The Night's Watch will let you through the tunnel

518
00:35:21,320 --> 00:35:24,140
and allow your people to farm those lands.

519
00:35:26,830 --> 00:35:28,330
I knew Mance Rayder.

520
00:35:29,220 --> 00:35:30,970
He never wanted a war with the Night's Watch.

521
00:35:30,970 --> 00:35:33,400
He wanted a new life for his people, for you.

522
00:35:33,630 --> 00:35:36,220
We're prepared to give you that new life.

523
00:35:36,750 --> 00:35:37,540
If?

524
00:35:37,540 --> 00:35:41,120
If you swear you'll join us when the real war begins.

525
00:35:44,130 --> 00:35:45,280
Where is Mance?

526
00:35:48,770 --> 00:35:50,530
- He died. - How?

527
00:35:56,490 --> 00:35:58,210
I put an arrow through his heart.

528
00:36:06,520 --> 00:36:08,120
I say we send the Lord Commander

529
00:36:08,120 --> 00:36:11,410
back to Castle Black with no eyes.

530
00:36:13,490 --> 00:36:15,920
Hey, none of you saw Mance die.

531
00:36:16,340 --> 00:36:17,410
I did.

532
00:36:17,910 --> 00:36:20,940
The southern king who broke our army, Stannis,

533
00:36:21,230 --> 00:36:24,010
wanted to burn him alive to send us a message.

534
00:36:24,060 --> 00:36:26,820
Jon Snow defied that cunt's orders.

535
00:36:28,190 --> 00:36:30,350
His arrow was mercy.

536
00:36:31,070 --> 00:36:32,610
What he did took courage.

537
00:36:32,610 --> 00:36:34,250
And that's what we need today,

538
00:36:34,290 --> 00:36:35,950
the courage to make peace

539
00:36:35,950 --> 00:36:38,640
with men we've been killing for generations.

540
00:36:39,430 --> 00:36:41,470
I lost my father, my uncle,

541
00:36:41,470 --> 00:36:43,960
and two brothers fighting the damn crows.

542
00:36:43,960 --> 00:36:46,020
I'm not asking you to forget your dead.

543
00:36:47,100 --> 00:36:48,690
I'll never forget mine.

544
00:36:50,960 --> 00:36:54,040
I lost 50 brothers the night that Mance attacked the Wall.

545
00:36:56,110 --> 00:36:57,410
But I'm asking you

546
00:36:58,720 --> 00:37:00,810
to think about your children now.

547
00:37:02,620 --> 00:37:04,040
They'll never have children of their own

548
00:37:04,040 --> 00:37:05,620
if we don't band together.

549
00:37:07,180 --> 00:37:08,840
The Long Night is coming

550
00:37:09,570 --> 00:37:11,560
and the dead come with it.

551
00:37:12,130 --> 00:37:13,950
No clan can stop them.

552
00:37:14,300 --> 00:37:15,960
The free folk can't stop them.

553
00:37:15,960 --> 00:37:17,350
The Night's Watch can't stop them.

554
00:37:17,350 --> 00:37:19,910
And all the southern kings can't stop them.

555
00:37:21,820 --> 00:37:24,690
Only together, all of us.

556
00:37:24,810 --> 00:37:26,220
And even then it may not be enough,

557
00:37:26,220 --> 00:37:28,490
but at least we'll give the fuckers a fight.

558
00:37:44,510 --> 00:37:46,770
You vouch for this man, Tormund?

559
00:37:49,840 --> 00:37:52,030
He's prettier than both my daughters,

560
00:37:52,870 --> 00:37:54,490
but he knows how to fight.

561
00:37:54,810 --> 00:37:57,270
He's young, but he knows how to lead.

562
00:37:58,720 --> 00:38:00,610
He didn't have to come to Hardhome.

563
00:38:01,200 --> 00:38:02,990
He came because he needs us

564
00:38:04,650 --> 00:38:06,250
and we need him.

565
00:38:10,610 --> 00:38:12,460
My ancestors would spit on me

566
00:38:12,460 --> 00:38:14,460
if I broke bread with a crow.

567
00:38:15,090 --> 00:38:17,490
So would mine, but fuck 'em, they're dead.

568
00:38:27,220 --> 00:38:29,190
I'll never trust a man in black.

569
00:38:33,490 --> 00:38:35,110
But I trust you, Tormund.

570
00:38:36,000 --> 00:38:37,860
If you say this is the way,

571
00:38:39,790 --> 00:38:40,960
we're with you.

572
00:38:44,940 --> 00:38:46,070
This is the way.

573
00:38:48,130 --> 00:38:49,410
I'm with Tormund.

574
00:38:50,030 --> 00:38:52,310
We stay here, we're dead men.

575
00:38:54,170 --> 00:38:57,480
At least with King Crow, there's a chance.

576
00:39:00,680 --> 00:39:02,910
Tormund.

577
00:39:05,700 --> 00:39:08,090
Keep that new life you want to give us.

578
00:39:11,840 --> 00:39:14,200
And keep your glass, King Crow.

579
00:39:16,770 --> 00:39:19,980
As soon as you get on his ships, they're gonna slit your throats

580
00:39:19,990 --> 00:39:22,960
and dump your bodies to the bottom of the Shivering Sea.

581
00:39:25,350 --> 00:39:26,680
That's our enemy.

582
00:39:28,560 --> 00:39:30,510
That has always been our enemy.

583
00:39:46,850 --> 00:39:48,600
I fucking hate Thenns.

584
00:40:08,410 --> 00:40:10,740
- Move it. - Be careful.

585
00:40:11,200 --> 00:40:13,060
- Move 'em along, now. - Cast-off time.

586
00:40:13,160 --> 00:40:14,510
That's it, come on.

587
00:40:18,010 --> 00:40:19,720
How many are with us? 5,000?

588
00:40:20,770 --> 00:40:22,230
I'm not good at counting.

589
00:40:23,620 --> 00:40:25,120
We're leaving too many behind.

590
00:40:25,120 --> 00:40:26,670
The free folk are stubborn.

591
00:40:26,670 --> 00:40:29,160
You know how long it took Mance to band them together?

592
00:40:29,460 --> 00:40:31,590
20 fucking years.

593
00:40:31,920 --> 00:40:33,940
And he knew them better than I ever will.

594
00:40:35,320 --> 00:40:38,810
They're running out of food and there's nothing to hunt.

595
00:40:39,320 --> 00:40:40,520
They'll come around.

596
00:40:43,880 --> 00:40:46,080
- Get yourselves ready. - Aye!

597
00:40:46,340 --> 00:40:48,000
Johnna is gonna look after you.

598
00:40:48,000 --> 00:40:50,790
She's in charge. You listen to her.

599
00:40:52,140 --> 00:40:54,770
- Take her. - There you are.

600
00:40:54,770 --> 00:40:56,020
I want to go with you.

601
00:40:56,020 --> 00:40:58,100
I need to get the old folks on the boats.

602
00:40:58,830 --> 00:41:00,660
I'm right behind you. I promise.

603
00:41:04,840 --> 00:41:05,920
Go on.

604
00:41:09,220 --> 00:41:09,980
Another one.

605
00:41:09,980 --> 00:41:12,270
Keep moving. We'll meet you out there.

606
00:41:15,860 --> 00:41:18,130
Won't be able to take that on the boat. It's too big.

607
00:41:18,510 --> 00:41:21,950
- That's the last one! - Three more! Move on!

608
00:41:22,180 --> 00:41:24,040
There's more dragonglass everywhere.

609
00:41:31,750 --> 00:41:33,650
I've got some more daggers over here.

610
00:41:34,650 --> 00:41:36,130
Put that dagger in his bag.

612
00:42:33,500 --> 00:42:34,730
Steady!

613
00:42:55,270 --> 00:42:56,630
Shut the gates.

614
00:42:56,870 --> 00:42:58,380
Close the gates!

615
00:43:02,830 --> 00:43:04,440
Shut the gates!

616
00:43:09,060 --> 00:43:10,300
Wait!

617
00:43:10,390 --> 00:43:13,080
- Open the gate! - Let us in!

618
00:43:14,430 --> 00:43:15,560
Help us!

619
00:43:26,550 --> 00:43:27,930
Please open it!

620
00:43:28,450 --> 00:43:29,990
Open the gate!

621
00:44:16,620 --> 00:44:18,220
Ready your arrows!

622
00:44:37,570 --> 00:44:41,160
- Wait! Wait! - Keep in line! Keep in line!

623
00:44:41,500 --> 00:44:42,890
Get in line!

624
00:44:44,890 --> 00:44:46,110
Get in line!

625
00:44:47,500 --> 00:44:48,760
Get to the front!

626
00:45:46,050 --> 00:45:47,700
Go on, shoot it!

627
00:45:54,820 --> 00:45:58,340
- Wait, wait! - Duncan, hold the line! Hold the line!

628
00:46:03,780 --> 00:46:05,150
Lord Commander!

629
00:46:05,230 --> 00:46:07,390
Get them to the ship and come back for me!

630
00:46:07,400 --> 00:46:09,020
- But you'll never make-- - Now!

631
00:46:12,950 --> 00:46:15,030
- Let me on! - Let me on!

632
00:46:15,270 --> 00:46:17,200
- Bloody fucking move! - Let go!

633
00:46:18,350 --> 00:46:20,020
You should be on one of those boats.

634
00:46:20,020 --> 00:46:22,700
So should you. My little girls got on.

635
00:46:23,020 --> 00:46:25,390
They're gonna let them pass the Wall even if you're not there?

636
00:46:25,390 --> 00:46:27,950
You have my word. I've given orders.

637
00:46:27,950 --> 00:46:30,870
Don't think you're gonna be there to enforce those orders.

638
00:46:32,840 --> 00:46:35,230
If they get through, everyone dies.

639
00:46:38,660 --> 00:46:41,650
Night's Watch, with me!

640
00:46:41,760 --> 00:46:43,660
Move! Move!

641
00:46:45,410 --> 00:46:46,490
Move!

642
00:47:52,210 --> 00:47:53,660
No, no!

643
00:48:03,080 --> 00:48:06,530
- Tormund, the sleigh! - Okay, okay!

644
00:48:54,570 --> 00:48:55,950
The dragonglass.

645
00:48:56,230 --> 00:48:57,690
You and me, then!

646
00:48:58,740 --> 00:48:59,680
Go!

647
00:50:10,280 --> 00:50:11,630
Get the glass.

648
00:53:17,620 --> 00:53:18,700
Come on!

649
00:53:20,080 --> 00:53:21,090
The dragonglass.

650
00:53:21,100 --> 00:53:24,000
Fuck the glass! We are gonna die here!

651
00:53:55,240 --> 00:53:57,310
Oh, fuck!

652
00:54:03,740 --> 00:54:05,310
Tormund, run!

653
00:54:14,860 --> 00:54:16,930
Wun Wun, to the sea.

654
00:55:00,160 --> 00:55:01,300
Quickly!

655
00:55:01,610 --> 00:55:03,930
- Faster, faster! - Run, run!

656
00:55:03,930 --> 00:55:05,520
Quickly!

657
00:55:08,300 --> 00:55:10,790
- Quickly, row! Row! - Go, go, come on!

658
00:55:40,090 --> 00:55:42,880
Let's go! Now, now!

659
00:55:47,170 --> 00:55:48,870
Come on, row!

