1
00:00:01,390 --> 00:00:03,870
My son Jorah fled Westeros.

2
00:00:03,870 --> 00:00:06,140
He brought dishonor to our house.

3
00:00:06,140 --> 00:00:09,120
I need him to turn this bunch of thieves and runaways

4
00:00:09,120 --> 00:00:10,580
into men of the Night's Watch.

5
00:00:10,580 --> 00:00:12,620
And how's that going, Commander Mormont?

6
00:00:13,620 --> 00:00:15,410
I shall have your head for this.

7
00:00:18,410 --> 00:00:20,250
You're taking us through Valyria.

8
00:00:20,370 --> 00:00:22,580
The Doom still rules Valyria.

9
00:00:26,420 --> 00:00:27,540
Stone Men!

10
00:00:31,040 --> 00:00:32,330
Did any of them touch you?

11
00:00:33,370 --> 00:00:34,340
You?

12
00:00:37,940 --> 00:00:39,390
The Eyrie is mine.

13
00:00:40,330 --> 00:00:41,810
The last time the lords of the Eyrie

14
00:00:41,810 --> 00:00:43,970
formed an alliance with the lords of the North,

15
00:00:43,970 --> 00:00:46,770
they brought down the greatest dynasty this world has ever known.

16
00:00:49,330 --> 00:00:50,710
Cersei sent for me.

17
00:00:50,900 --> 00:00:53,860
I expect I'll be a married woman by the time you return.

18
00:00:54,030 --> 00:00:55,520
I hope I can make her happy.

19
00:00:55,690 --> 00:00:57,110
She suffered enough.

20
00:00:57,150 --> 00:00:58,350
I'll never hurt her.

21
00:00:59,220 --> 00:01:01,490
All sinners are equal before the Gods.

22
00:01:01,490 --> 00:01:05,460
What would you say if I told you of a great sinner in our very midst?

23
00:01:06,030 --> 00:01:08,110
May the Father judge him justly.

24
00:01:08,380 --> 00:01:10,470
- Who do you think you are? - Justice.

25
00:01:11,360 --> 00:01:12,630
Your brother was murdered

26
00:01:12,630 --> 00:01:15,270
and you sit here doing nothing.

27
00:01:15,270 --> 00:01:16,740
The Sand Snakes are with me.

28
00:01:16,740 --> 00:01:19,800
Without Doran, we have no army to march against the Lannisters.

29
00:01:19,800 --> 00:01:22,360
Queen Cersei loves her children.

30
00:01:22,360 --> 00:01:23,790
And we have one of them.

31
00:01:23,790 --> 00:01:25,110
We are rescuing my niece,

32
00:01:25,110 --> 00:01:26,500
bringing her back to her family.

33
00:01:26,500 --> 00:01:27,760
You ever been to Dorne?

34
00:01:31,090 --> 00:01:32,590
The Dornish are crazy.

35
00:01:32,680 --> 00:01:34,420
If he gets to her before we do,

36
00:01:34,420 --> 00:01:36,700
we lose our only chance for revenge.

37
00:01:38,390 --> 00:01:41,490
Here we serve the Many-Faced God. To serve well,

38
00:01:41,490 --> 00:01:43,190
a girl must become no-one.

39
00:01:43,300 --> 00:01:45,460
What do we do with them after we wash them?

40
00:05:40,450 --> 00:05:41,980
What are they doing with the bodies?

41
00:05:42,150 --> 00:05:43,590
Get back to work.

42
00:05:43,830 --> 00:05:46,580
No. I've been here for weeks.

43
00:05:46,580 --> 00:05:48,120
I'm not scrubbing one more corpse

44
00:05:48,120 --> 00:05:49,860
until you tell me why I'm doing it.

45
00:05:50,890 --> 00:05:52,200
You will know why.

46
00:05:52,940 --> 00:05:56,400
- When? - When it's time, not before.

47
00:05:56,970 --> 00:05:58,360
Get back to work.

48
00:05:58,550 --> 00:05:59,840
When do I get to play the game?

49
00:05:59,840 --> 00:06:00,920
Game?

50
00:06:01,510 --> 00:06:04,290
The game. The game of faces.

51
00:06:05,030 --> 00:06:07,640
You tried already. You failed.

52
00:06:07,640 --> 00:06:08,940
I didn't even know I was playing.

53
00:06:08,940 --> 00:06:10,190
Who are you?

54
00:06:12,360 --> 00:06:13,420
No one.

55
00:06:14,760 --> 00:06:16,100
Get back to work.

56
00:06:16,160 --> 00:06:17,290
Who are you?

57
00:06:17,840 --> 00:06:20,710
What are you doing here? How did you get here?

58
00:06:21,740 --> 00:06:25,120
I'm from Westeros just like you.

59
00:06:26,120 --> 00:06:28,580
Daughter of a lord just like you.

60
00:06:29,820 --> 00:06:31,710
Except I was an only child.

61
00:06:32,010 --> 00:06:33,600
Heir to his fortune.

62
00:06:35,250 --> 00:06:36,550
My mother died.

63
00:06:37,660 --> 00:06:41,250
My father remarried and his new wife gave birth to a girl.

64
00:06:43,020 --> 00:06:46,590
My stepmother didn't want any rivals for her precious daughter,

65
00:06:47,380 --> 00:06:49,910
So she tried to kill me with poison.

66
00:06:50,040 --> 00:06:51,180
I found out.

67
00:06:51,540 --> 00:06:53,670
Sought help from the faceless men.

68
00:06:56,460 --> 00:06:58,240
And my father was widowed again.

69
00:07:00,590 --> 00:07:02,490
I've been serving them ever since.

70
00:07:14,270 --> 00:07:17,080
Was that true or a lie?

71
00:07:20,520 --> 00:07:21,300
What?

72
00:07:21,300 --> 00:07:23,510
Did you believe every word I said?

73
00:07:28,450 --> 00:07:29,820
Get back to work.

74
00:07:44,530 --> 00:07:45,590
Who are you?

75
00:07:56,360 --> 00:07:57,670
Who are you?

76
00:08:03,380 --> 00:08:04,420
Arya.

77
00:08:05,780 --> 00:08:07,560
And where did you come from?

78
00:08:07,830 --> 00:08:08,990
Westeros.

79
00:08:13,550 --> 00:08:15,180
My family home is Winterfell.

80
00:08:15,670 --> 00:08:17,460
I'm the youngest daughter of a great lord,

81
00:08:18,080 --> 00:08:19,370
Eddard Stark.

82
00:08:19,490 --> 00:08:20,680
He died in battle.

83
00:08:22,170 --> 00:08:23,260
A lie.

84
00:08:23,540 --> 00:08:26,400
After he was executed, I fled the capital.

85
00:08:28,110 --> 00:08:29,620
Had to kill a stable boy.

86
00:08:29,820 --> 00:08:31,490
Drove my sword through his back.

87
00:08:33,500 --> 00:08:34,600
A lie.

88
00:08:35,260 --> 00:08:36,640
I stabbed him in the gut.

89
00:08:37,250 --> 00:08:39,060
I tried to find my mother and brother,

90
00:08:39,610 --> 00:08:40,790
but I never did.

91
00:08:40,910 --> 00:08:43,260
They were murdered by Walder Frey.

92
00:08:44,540 --> 00:08:47,220
An outlaw kidnapped me, a man called Polliver.

93
00:08:48,900 --> 00:08:51,580
A man called the Hound. Sandor Clegane.

94
00:08:52,740 --> 00:08:54,990
He tried to sell me, but was wounded in a fight.

95
00:08:55,110 --> 00:08:56,610
He begged me to kill him, but I wouldn't.

96
00:08:56,620 --> 00:08:58,420
I left him in the mountains to die.

97
00:08:58,800 --> 00:09:01,360
I wanted him to suffer. I hated him.

98
00:09:03,790 --> 00:09:05,040
I hated him.

99
00:09:06,450 --> 00:09:07,680
That's not a lie!

100
00:09:09,470 --> 00:09:11,750
A girl lies to me,

101
00:09:12,440 --> 00:09:15,280
to the many-faced god, to herself.

102
00:09:15,960 --> 00:09:18,150
Does she truly want to be no one?

103
00:09:19,420 --> 00:09:20,460
Yes.

104
00:09:25,250 --> 00:09:28,400
I'm not playing this stupid game anymore!

105
00:09:28,550 --> 00:09:30,200
We never stop playing.

106
00:09:52,720 --> 00:09:55,930
So, those villages we were supposed to find?

107
00:09:56,510 --> 00:09:58,330
We can't live on berries and roots.

108
00:09:58,330 --> 00:09:59,310
I can.

109
00:10:00,780 --> 00:10:02,000
You're not hungry?

110
00:10:03,240 --> 00:10:04,400
Of course I'm hungry.

111
00:10:05,580 --> 00:10:07,780
You're an awful travelling companion, do you know that?

112
00:10:07,780 --> 00:10:09,730
Possibly the least charming man I've ever met.

113
00:10:09,730 --> 00:10:11,480
I'm not your travelling companion.

114
00:10:11,480 --> 00:10:14,910
We are travelling together in each other's company, therefore...

115
00:10:14,910 --> 00:10:16,450
Do you ever shut up?

116
00:10:17,170 --> 00:10:20,210
I sailed from King's Landing to Pentos in a crate

117
00:10:20,490 --> 00:10:22,520
without ever saying a word.

118
00:10:23,100 --> 00:10:24,190
Why?

119
00:10:27,760 --> 00:10:30,320
It never occurred to you to ask why until now?

120
00:10:32,740 --> 00:10:34,600
You never wondered why Tyrion Lannister

121
00:10:34,600 --> 00:10:37,320
decided to visit a brothel in Volantis?

122
00:10:37,320 --> 00:10:40,310
I'm sure you visited many brothels in many cities.

123
00:10:42,940 --> 00:10:44,290
I killed my father.

124
00:10:46,650 --> 00:10:49,860
He wanted to execute me for a crime I didn't commit.

125
00:10:52,890 --> 00:10:55,040
And he was fucking the woman I loved.

126
00:11:05,640 --> 00:11:07,170
As miserable as you are, Mormont,

127
00:11:07,170 --> 00:11:08,860
at least your father was a good man.

128
00:11:08,950 --> 00:11:10,410
What do you know about my father?

129
00:11:10,540 --> 00:11:13,050
I met him. I visited the wall.

130
00:11:13,950 --> 00:11:15,750
When I asked him about his men,

131
00:11:17,400 --> 00:11:19,670
he knew all their stories, every one of them.

132
00:11:19,960 --> 00:11:22,630
He actually cared about the people under his command.

133
00:11:23,870 --> 00:11:25,670
How do they put it in the watch?

134
00:11:26,470 --> 00:11:28,820
"We shall never see his like again."

135
00:11:41,330 --> 00:11:42,570
You didn't know.

136
00:11:48,080 --> 00:11:50,510
I'm sorry. I am.

137
00:11:53,690 --> 00:11:54,810
How?

138
00:11:56,630 --> 00:11:58,140
I only know what I heard.

139
00:11:58,460 --> 00:11:59,430
How?

140
00:11:59,430 --> 00:12:01,790
He was leading an expedition beyond the wall.

141
00:12:03,100 --> 00:12:04,380
There was a mutiny.

142
00:12:05,930 --> 00:12:07,580
He was murdered by his own men.

143
00:12:19,350 --> 00:12:20,740
We better keep moving.

144
00:13:11,470 --> 00:13:12,820
Valar morghulis.

145
00:13:13,210 --> 00:13:14,640
Valar dohaeris.

146
00:13:16,680 --> 00:13:18,090
I have nowhere else to go.

147
00:13:19,520 --> 00:13:22,040
I've taken her to every healer in Braavos.

148
00:13:23,140 --> 00:13:25,030
I've spent every penny I had.

149
00:13:30,740 --> 00:13:32,740
She suffers every day of her life.

150
00:13:34,410 --> 00:13:35,910
I just want it to end.

151
00:14:04,540 --> 00:14:06,210
It hurts.

152
00:14:07,240 --> 00:14:08,280
I know.

153
00:14:10,710 --> 00:14:12,210
Don't be afraid.

154
00:14:13,330 --> 00:14:14,980
I used to be like you.

155
00:14:16,880 --> 00:14:18,220
I was sick.

156
00:14:19,790 --> 00:14:21,000
I was dying.

157
00:14:24,840 --> 00:14:28,410
But my father never gave up on me.

158
00:14:31,010 --> 00:14:32,270
He loved me

159
00:14:33,790 --> 00:14:35,440
more than anything in the world,

160
00:14:35,440 --> 00:14:37,340
just like your father loves you.

161
00:14:38,200 --> 00:14:39,770
So he brought me here.

162
00:14:41,520 --> 00:14:44,040
My father prayed to the many-faced god.

163
00:14:46,310 --> 00:14:48,600
And I drank the water from his fountain.

164
00:14:49,870 --> 00:14:51,350
It healed me.

165
00:15:04,290 --> 00:15:06,610
I've devoted my life to him now.

166
00:15:08,170 --> 00:15:09,910
You don't want to hurt anymore?

167
00:15:12,650 --> 00:15:14,000
Drink.

168
00:17:58,660 --> 00:18:00,170
Is a girl ready?

169
00:18:01,740 --> 00:18:04,610
To give up her ears, her nose, her tongue?

170
00:18:06,140 --> 00:18:09,260
Her hopes and dreams, her loves and hates?

171
00:18:09,260 --> 00:18:11,820
All that makes a girl who she is?

172
00:18:13,440 --> 00:18:14,640
Forever?

173
00:18:18,830 --> 00:18:19,900
No.

174
00:18:21,560 --> 00:18:24,150
A girl is not ready to become no one.

175
00:18:29,960 --> 00:18:32,340
But she is ready to become someone else.

176
00:18:45,740 --> 00:18:48,750
Why Daenerys? Why is she worth all this?

177
00:18:50,600 --> 00:18:53,700
As I recall, the Mormonts fought against the Targaryens

178
00:18:53,700 --> 00:18:55,120
during Robert's rebellion.

179
00:18:55,800 --> 00:18:57,400
Do you believe in anything?

180
00:18:57,890 --> 00:18:59,360
I believe in lots of things.

181
00:18:59,360 --> 00:19:01,390
In something greater than ourselves, I mean.

182
00:19:01,390 --> 00:19:03,790
The gods, destiny.

183
00:19:04,230 --> 00:19:06,530
Do you believe there's a plan for this world?

184
00:19:08,050 --> 00:19:09,040
No.

185
00:19:09,080 --> 00:19:10,300
Neither did I.

186
00:19:10,300 --> 00:19:12,490
I was a cynic just like you.

187
00:19:13,100 --> 00:19:17,510
Then I saw a girl step into a great fire with three stone eggs.

188
00:19:17,800 --> 00:19:21,170
When the fire burned out, I thought I'd find her blackened bones.

189
00:19:21,180 --> 00:19:24,660
Instead, I saw her, Daenerys,

190
00:19:25,070 --> 00:19:29,240
alive and unhurt, holding her baby dragons.

191
00:19:31,620 --> 00:19:33,810
Have you ever heard baby dragons singing?

192
00:19:34,900 --> 00:19:35,900
No.

193
00:19:36,180 --> 00:19:38,080
It's hard to be a cynic after that.

194
00:19:40,240 --> 00:19:42,440
Doesn't mean she's going to be a great queen.

195
00:19:42,510 --> 00:19:44,000
No, it doesn't.

196
00:19:44,650 --> 00:19:47,060
The Targaryens are famously insane.

197
00:19:47,080 --> 00:19:49,490
What if she conquers the world? Then what?

198
00:19:49,710 --> 00:19:52,090
1,000 years of peace and prosperity?

199
00:19:52,230 --> 00:19:54,290
First we have to conquer the world.

200
00:19:54,420 --> 00:19:55,420
We?

201
00:19:56,070 --> 00:19:58,440
All right, let's assume your dreams come true.

202
00:19:58,620 --> 00:20:01,610
She's ecstatic when you bring her this enemy dwarf.

203
00:20:01,750 --> 00:20:04,590
She hacks off my head and restores your position.

204
00:20:04,860 --> 00:20:07,050
You command her army, sail to Westeros,

205
00:20:07,050 --> 00:20:10,170
defeat all your enemies and watch her climb those steps

206
00:20:10,180 --> 00:20:11,720
and sit on the Iron Throne.

207
00:20:11,720 --> 00:20:14,140
Hurrah. Long live the queen. Then what?

208
00:20:14,240 --> 00:20:15,660
Then she rules.

209
00:20:15,870 --> 00:20:18,770
So a woman who has not spent a single day of her adult life

210
00:20:18,770 --> 00:20:21,830
in Westeros becomes the ruler of Westeros? That's justice?

211
00:20:21,840 --> 00:20:24,000
- She's the rightful heir. - Why?

212
00:20:24,150 --> 00:20:28,020
Because her father, who burned living men for amusement, was the king?

213
00:20:31,260 --> 00:20:34,130
- That's a slave ship. - Why are they anchored?

214
00:20:34,140 --> 00:20:35,790
They probably came ashore for...

215
00:20:35,790 --> 00:20:36,910
Water.

216
00:20:48,590 --> 00:20:50,560
Got a lot of fight in you, huh?

217
00:20:59,730 --> 00:21:01,090
Salt mines?

218
00:21:01,620 --> 00:21:05,240
Yeah, that or a galley slave.

219
00:21:05,240 --> 00:21:06,880
He looks strong enough.

220
00:21:07,020 --> 00:21:08,690
What about the dwarf?

221
00:21:09,820 --> 00:21:11,120
Worthless.

222
00:21:13,160 --> 00:21:14,270
Cut his throat.

223
00:21:14,280 --> 00:21:16,910
Wait. Wait. Wait, wait, wait! Let's discuss this.

224
00:21:16,910 --> 00:21:18,500
And then chop off his cock.

225
00:21:19,110 --> 00:21:20,650
We'll sell it for a fortune.

226
00:21:20,650 --> 00:21:22,730
A dwarf's cock has magic powers.

227
00:21:23,270 --> 00:21:25,020
Wait! Wait!

228
00:21:25,020 --> 00:21:26,420
Wait, wait, wait!

229
00:21:26,420 --> 00:21:29,150
You can't just hand a dry cock to a merchant

230
00:21:29,150 --> 00:21:30,780
and expect him to pay for it.

231
00:21:30,780 --> 00:21:32,640
He has to know it came from a dwarf.

232
00:21:32,640 --> 00:21:36,050
And how could he know unless he sees the dwarf?

233
00:21:36,050 --> 00:21:37,800
It will be a dwarf-sized cock.

234
00:21:37,810 --> 00:21:39,600
Guess again.

235
00:21:44,880 --> 00:21:48,110
The dwarf lives until we find a cock merchant.

236
00:21:56,570 --> 00:21:58,900
Queen Daenerys has outlawed slavery.

237
00:21:58,900 --> 00:22:01,410
We're bound for Volantis, not slaver's bay.

238
00:22:02,940 --> 00:22:05,620
Besides, she reopened the fighting pits.

239
00:22:05,620 --> 00:22:08,590
I've never heard of free men fighting in the pits.

240
00:22:08,840 --> 00:22:10,790
The fighting pits in Meereen?

241
00:22:10,820 --> 00:22:13,730
You're in luck, then. You're about to be rich.

242
00:22:13,850 --> 00:22:17,680
You are looking at one of the great warriors in the Seven Kingdoms.

243
00:22:19,620 --> 00:22:20,670
Him.

244
00:22:21,130 --> 00:22:24,930
Him? He's got to be 60 years old.

245
00:22:25,110 --> 00:22:27,910
Sure, he's a bit long in the tooth,

246
00:22:27,910 --> 00:22:30,350
a bit withered, been in the sun too long.

247
00:22:30,350 --> 00:22:34,280
We can all see that. But he is a veteran of 100 battles.

248
00:22:34,280 --> 00:22:36,010
They wrote songs about him.

249
00:22:42,750 --> 00:22:43,970
That true?

250
00:22:50,110 --> 00:22:52,360
He won the tournament at Lannisport.

251
00:22:52,390 --> 00:22:55,000
Unseating Ser Jaime Lannister himself.

252
00:22:58,440 --> 00:22:59,670
The Kingslayer.

253
00:22:59,680 --> 00:23:02,770
Jousting. You're talking about jousting.

254
00:23:02,790 --> 00:23:05,340
A fancy game for fancy lads.

255
00:23:05,340 --> 00:23:07,020
The men who fight in the pits of Meereen

256
00:23:07,020 --> 00:23:08,280
will swallow him whole.

257
00:23:08,280 --> 00:23:11,100
I killed a Dothraki bloodrider in single combat.

258
00:23:21,800 --> 00:23:22,860
Liar.

259
00:23:22,860 --> 00:23:25,650
It's no lie. His name was Qotho.

260
00:23:25,710 --> 00:23:28,030
He was bloodrider to Khal Drogo.

261
00:23:29,050 --> 00:23:32,630
Take me to Slaver's Bay, put a sword in my hand,

262
00:23:32,750 --> 00:23:34,430
I'll prove my worth.

263
00:23:46,180 --> 00:23:48,630
For my children. Money.

264
00:23:52,940 --> 00:23:54,260
Lord Baelish.

265
00:23:54,960 --> 00:23:56,050
Yes?

266
00:23:58,570 --> 00:24:00,230
Lancel Lannister.

267
00:24:02,790 --> 00:24:04,360
Brother Lancel.

268
00:24:04,670 --> 00:24:06,450
We abandon our family names.

269
00:24:06,460 --> 00:24:08,370
Quite a family to abandon.

270
00:24:08,490 --> 00:24:10,850
The city has changed since you were here last.

271
00:24:11,360 --> 00:24:13,180
We flooded the gutters with wine,

272
00:24:13,240 --> 00:24:15,240
smashed the false idols,

273
00:24:15,710 --> 00:24:17,650
and set the godless on the run.

274
00:24:18,760 --> 00:24:19,940
Well done.

275
00:24:25,360 --> 00:24:27,840
I'm here on urgent business for the Queen Mother.

276
00:24:28,720 --> 00:24:30,800
Should I send word that I'll be delayed?

277
00:24:35,250 --> 00:24:37,060
Step carefully, Lord Baelish.

278
00:24:37,100 --> 00:24:39,370
You'll find there's little tolerance for flesh peddlers

279
00:24:39,370 --> 00:24:41,020
in the new King's Landing.

280
00:24:41,030 --> 00:24:43,580
We both peddle fantasies, Brother Lancel.

281
00:24:43,920 --> 00:24:46,220
Mine just happen to be entertaining.

282
00:24:55,790 --> 00:24:58,360
Do you think it's wise, Your Grace,

283
00:24:59,170 --> 00:25:00,860
arresting the heir to Highgarden?

284
00:25:00,860 --> 00:25:03,660
The Faith arrested the heir to Highgarden.

285
00:25:03,670 --> 00:25:06,800
Of course, and the Faith were armed on your orders.

286
00:25:06,800 --> 00:25:08,200
The King's orders.

287
00:25:08,390 --> 00:25:10,790
Is the King to blame for Ser Loras's perversion?

288
00:25:10,790 --> 00:25:12,950
House Tyrell won't tolerate this insult.

289
00:25:12,950 --> 00:25:14,910
House Tyrell won't tolerate it?

290
00:25:15,700 --> 00:25:17,940
I'm the insulted party, Lord Baelish.

291
00:25:17,940 --> 00:25:19,590
Ser Loras was promised to me.

292
00:25:19,590 --> 00:25:21,730
Instead he chose the company of boys.

293
00:25:21,730 --> 00:25:24,130
One's choice of companion is a curious thing.

294
00:25:27,140 --> 00:25:28,550
Most curious.

295
00:25:30,590 --> 00:25:32,610
Lysa Arryn, for instance.

296
00:25:32,930 --> 00:25:34,870
Thoroughly repellant woman.

297
00:25:35,990 --> 00:25:37,250
Forgive me.

298
00:25:37,960 --> 00:25:39,670
I know you're still in mourning.

299
00:25:40,630 --> 00:25:43,110
Lysa was a good woman.

300
00:25:43,850 --> 00:25:45,020
A kind woman.

301
00:25:45,020 --> 00:25:47,520
She was neither of those things. We both know it.

302
00:25:47,530 --> 00:25:49,380
Still, I pity her son.

303
00:25:49,900 --> 00:25:53,410
How fortunate the young Lord of the Vale has a new father

304
00:25:53,410 --> 00:25:54,530
to counsel him.

305
00:25:54,530 --> 00:25:56,330
I know how hard it can be

306
00:25:56,780 --> 00:25:58,940
to lose both your parents at such a young age.

307
00:25:58,940 --> 00:26:00,390
If war comes to Westeros,

308
00:26:00,390 --> 00:26:02,420
will the knights of the Vale fight for their King?

309
00:26:03,270 --> 00:26:05,630
Young Lord Robin heeds my advice.

310
00:26:06,870 --> 00:26:09,970
And I have always counseled loyalty to the throne.

311
00:26:09,990 --> 00:26:11,120
Good.

312
00:26:16,110 --> 00:26:17,700
If there's nothing else.

313
00:26:19,110 --> 00:26:20,940
There is another matter, Your Grace.

314
00:26:20,940 --> 00:26:23,660
Something so urgent I couldn't trust the words to a raven.

315
00:26:24,070 --> 00:26:26,520
You once charged me with finding Arya Stark.

316
00:26:26,560 --> 00:26:28,290
To my shame, I failed you.

317
00:26:29,700 --> 00:26:31,850
But I have found Sansa Stark.

318
00:26:33,430 --> 00:26:36,660
Alive and well and home again

319
00:26:37,160 --> 00:26:38,730
living at Winterfell.

320
00:26:38,730 --> 00:26:40,270
That's not possible.

321
00:26:40,610 --> 00:26:42,480
My sources are well placed.

322
00:26:44,420 --> 00:26:46,110
They tell me Roose Bolton plans to

323
00:26:46,110 --> 00:26:48,400
marry her to his son Ramsay,

324
00:26:48,700 --> 00:26:51,450
A bastard recently legitimized by King Tommen.

325
00:26:51,450 --> 00:26:55,160
Roose Bolton is Warden of the North by the grace of my father.

326
00:26:55,160 --> 00:26:59,240
Indeed, his reward for stabbing his own king in the heart.

327
00:27:00,350 --> 00:27:02,890
We were fools to trust a Turncloak.

328
00:27:03,010 --> 00:27:05,120
Marrying his son to the last of the Starks

329
00:27:05,120 --> 00:27:06,910
gives him more legitimacy in the north

330
00:27:06,920 --> 00:27:09,280
than an alliance with a hated southern house.

331
00:27:09,280 --> 00:27:12,410
I will skin him and his bastard

332
00:27:12,410 --> 00:27:14,440
like that wretch on their bloody sigil.

333
00:27:14,440 --> 00:27:16,200
I would counsel patience, Your Grace.

334
00:27:16,200 --> 00:27:17,370
Patience?

335
00:27:17,970 --> 00:27:19,530
Sansa helped murder my son.

336
00:27:19,530 --> 00:27:20,960
Roose Bolton is a traitor.

337
00:27:20,960 --> 00:27:23,010
Stannis Baratheon is also a traitor,

338
00:27:23,010 --> 00:27:25,000
marching with his army on Winterfell.

339
00:27:25,190 --> 00:27:26,990
Let Stannis and Roose battle.

340
00:27:27,710 --> 00:27:29,810
Let the enemies of the throne slaughter each other.

341
00:27:29,810 --> 00:27:30,980
And when they're done,

342
00:27:30,980 --> 00:27:33,420
seize Winterfell from whichever thief survives.

343
00:27:33,420 --> 00:27:36,060
Winterfell is 1,000 miles away from here.

344
00:27:36,420 --> 00:27:38,420
The weather has already begun to turn.

345
00:27:38,420 --> 00:27:40,810
That is why it is critical to strike soon

346
00:27:40,810 --> 00:27:43,290
while the victor still licks his wounds.

347
00:27:45,190 --> 00:27:47,740
Surely your uncle Kevan could muster a force.

348
00:27:47,740 --> 00:27:51,120
My uncle Kevan has all the courage of a kitchen mouse.

349
00:27:51,120 --> 00:27:52,410
Ser Jaime, then.

350
00:27:52,410 --> 00:27:55,060
Jaime's away on a sensitive diplomatic mission.

351
00:27:55,890 --> 00:27:57,830
I have no idea when he'll be back.

352
00:27:58,140 --> 00:27:59,720
Perhaps I can help.

353
00:28:00,820 --> 00:28:01,730
The knights of the Vale

354
00:28:01,730 --> 00:28:03,660
are some of the best fighters in Westeros,

355
00:28:03,820 --> 00:28:06,250
trained to battle in the ice and the snow.

356
00:28:06,250 --> 00:28:07,850
Forgive me, Lord Baelish,

357
00:28:09,180 --> 00:28:12,130
You have a reputation as a moneylender and a brothel keeper,

358
00:28:12,130 --> 00:28:14,030
not a military man.

359
00:28:14,030 --> 00:28:16,130
You wouldn't risk a single Lannister soldier

360
00:28:16,190 --> 00:28:18,650
or a single coin from the royal treasury.

361
00:28:19,420 --> 00:28:20,680
What do you have to lose?

362
00:28:21,260 --> 00:28:22,710
A brothel keeper?

363
00:28:23,390 --> 00:28:24,680
And if you succeed?

364
00:28:24,740 --> 00:28:26,830
Name me Warden of the North.

365
00:28:31,610 --> 00:28:33,500
I'll speak to the King this evening,

366
00:28:34,840 --> 00:28:36,720
have him issue a royal decree.

367
00:28:37,150 --> 00:28:39,800
I'll not rest until the lion flies over Winterfell.

368
00:28:40,020 --> 00:28:42,030
And I'll know you're a man of your word

369
00:28:42,200 --> 00:28:45,370
when I see Sansa Stark's head on a spike.

370
00:28:45,370 --> 00:28:46,550
As I said...

371
00:28:47,300 --> 00:28:49,100
I live to serve.

372
00:28:55,390 --> 00:28:57,740
I'm going to ask him tomorrow.

373
00:28:59,300 --> 00:29:01,380
- What if he says no? - He won't.

374
00:29:01,460 --> 00:29:02,970
We've waited long enough.

375
00:29:03,930 --> 00:29:05,690
I want you to be my wife.

376
00:29:06,260 --> 00:29:07,380
Now.

377
00:29:09,580 --> 00:29:10,510
What is it?

378
00:29:10,670 --> 00:29:13,900
Do you want to marry me because our families arranged it?

379
00:29:13,900 --> 00:29:15,130
or do you...

380
00:29:23,370 --> 00:29:25,970
We can't. Not yet.

381
00:29:25,970 --> 00:29:26,980
Why not?

382
00:29:26,980 --> 00:29:29,070
You know why not. Someone will see.

383
00:29:29,290 --> 00:29:31,190
You are going to be my wife.

384
00:29:31,620 --> 00:29:35,210
I am going to be your husband.

385
00:29:35,860 --> 00:29:38,350
We're allowed to walk through the gardens together.

386
00:29:38,940 --> 00:29:41,470
How many other girls have you walked through these gardens?

387
00:29:44,090 --> 00:29:46,830
I like the way your eyes go squinty when you're jealous.

388
00:29:46,830 --> 00:29:49,890
They do not go squinty and you didn't answer the question.

389
00:29:50,520 --> 00:29:52,350
They make a lovely couple.

390
00:29:52,920 --> 00:29:55,370
A Lannister and a Martell.

391
00:29:56,360 --> 00:29:59,310
They have no idea how dangerous that is.

392
00:29:59,780 --> 00:30:01,310
We must protect them.

393
00:30:01,580 --> 00:30:03,360
Yes, my prince.

394
00:30:05,210 --> 00:30:08,100
You haven't had to use that axe of yours in a long time.

395
00:30:09,850 --> 00:30:11,630
I hope you remember how.

396
00:30:12,250 --> 00:30:13,790
I remember how.

397
00:30:16,810 --> 00:30:20,410
*The Dornishman's wife was as fair as the sun,*

398
00:30:20,410 --> 00:30:25,010
*and her kisses were warmer than spring.*

399
00:30:25,810 --> 00:30:29,870
*But the Dornishman's blade was made of black steel,*

400
00:30:29,910 --> 00:30:34,110
*and its kiss was a terrible thing.*

401
00:30:34,660 --> 00:30:38,730
*The Dornishman's wife would sing as she bathed,*

402
00:30:38,870 --> 00:30:41,000
*in a voice that was sweet as a peach.*

403
00:30:41,000 --> 00:30:42,520
All right, that's enough.

404
00:30:42,950 --> 00:30:44,360
I'm coming to the best part.

405
00:30:44,920 --> 00:30:46,250
We're trying to blend in.

406
00:30:46,850 --> 00:30:48,770
Don't want everyone in Dorne to hear your accent.

407
00:30:48,770 --> 00:30:50,710
This song really is all about the ending.

408
00:30:50,710 --> 00:30:53,000
It can wait. There.

409
00:30:56,730 --> 00:30:58,340
That's the Water Gardens.

410
00:30:58,440 --> 00:31:00,710
And once we've got the princess, then what?

411
00:31:03,430 --> 00:31:04,770
I like to improvise.

412
00:31:06,200 --> 00:31:08,130
That explains the golden hand.

413
00:31:28,310 --> 00:31:32,160
- Unbowed. - Unbent. - Unbroken.

414
00:31:34,150 --> 00:31:35,350
For Oberyn.

415
00:31:35,670 --> 00:31:37,060
For Oberyn.

416
00:32:16,590 --> 00:32:18,360
Well, she's made herself at home.

417
00:32:24,450 --> 00:32:25,570
Myrcella.

418
00:32:29,100 --> 00:32:30,350
Uncle Jaime?

419
00:32:31,250 --> 00:32:32,170
I...

420
00:32:33,330 --> 00:32:35,320
I don't understand. What are you doing here?

421
00:32:35,340 --> 00:32:36,360
Let's speak in private.

422
00:32:36,770 --> 00:32:40,790
- I am Trystane Martell. - Trystane is my intended.

423
00:32:41,160 --> 00:32:43,470
Excellent. Good to meet you.

424
00:32:43,470 --> 00:32:44,970
We weren't expecting you, Lord Jaime.

425
00:32:44,970 --> 00:32:47,470
Why don't you let them have some time alone, son?

426
00:32:52,950 --> 00:32:54,740
Let's not do something stupid.

427
00:32:59,770 --> 00:33:01,290
That was something stupid.

428
00:33:01,370 --> 00:33:02,820
We have to go, Myrcella, now.

429
00:33:02,820 --> 00:33:04,750
- You hurt him! - He'll be fine, I promise.

430
00:33:04,750 --> 00:33:05,860
But we have to--

431
00:33:10,270 --> 00:33:11,870
Oh, for fuck's sake.

432
00:33:54,450 --> 00:33:55,440
Take her!

433
00:33:58,160 --> 00:33:59,930
- You're coming with me. - I don't want to.

434
00:33:59,940 --> 00:34:01,850
I wasn't asking, princess.

435
00:34:10,040 --> 00:34:11,340
Ah! Drop your weapons!

436
00:34:19,750 --> 00:34:21,490
I am Obara Sand.

437
00:34:22,290 --> 00:34:24,400
Daughter of Oberyn Martell.

438
00:34:24,810 --> 00:34:27,880
I fight for Dorne. Who do you fight for?

439
00:34:27,880 --> 00:34:29,820
Drop your weapons.

440
00:34:47,860 --> 00:34:50,930
When you were whole, it would have been a good fight.

441
00:35:01,770 --> 00:35:03,510
You fight pretty good for a little girl.

442
00:35:30,660 --> 00:35:32,040
Halt!

443
00:35:35,160 --> 00:35:38,200
Oh, you can smell the shit from five miles away.

444
00:35:39,110 --> 00:35:40,950
Well, why have we stopped? Go on.

445
00:35:44,930 --> 00:35:47,610
Rumors and gossip, that's all they've got.

446
00:35:47,610 --> 00:35:49,310
It's theater, nothing more.

447
00:35:49,530 --> 00:35:52,910
If they arrested all the pillow biters in King's Landing,

448
00:35:53,050 --> 00:35:55,850
there'd be no room left in the dungeons for anyone else.

449
00:35:55,850 --> 00:35:57,550
Everyone knew about him and Renly.

450
00:35:57,740 --> 00:35:59,090
Renly Baratheon shagged

451
00:35:59,090 --> 00:36:01,320
half the stable boys in the seven kingdoms.

452
00:36:01,320 --> 00:36:03,350
Everyone knew, no one cared.

453
00:36:03,350 --> 00:36:04,700
But he was the King's brother.

454
00:36:04,700 --> 00:36:06,620
And Loras is the Queen's brother.

455
00:36:06,620 --> 00:36:09,200
No, no, no, no. This is unacceptable.

456
00:36:09,200 --> 00:36:11,300
- Cersei's behind it. - Yeah, of course she is.

457
00:36:11,300 --> 00:36:13,580
She wants to drag our name through the dirt,

458
00:36:13,580 --> 00:36:15,220
put us in our place.

459
00:36:15,620 --> 00:36:17,530
Get some rest, dear. You look appalling.

460
00:36:17,530 --> 00:36:19,550
Let me deal with Cersei Lannister.

461
00:36:26,200 --> 00:36:29,400
Your grace, I have travelled a long way.

462
00:36:30,130 --> 00:36:31,790
You must be exhausted.

463
00:36:34,420 --> 00:36:37,170
Put the pen down, dear. We both know you're not writing anything.

464
00:36:37,180 --> 00:36:40,540
Ah, yes. The famously tart-tongued Queen of Thorns.

465
00:36:40,540 --> 00:36:43,570
And the famous tart Queen Cersei.

466
00:36:47,980 --> 00:36:48,970
I beg your pardon?

467
00:36:48,970 --> 00:36:52,880
I know you're behind this absurd incarceration of my grandson.

468
00:36:53,360 --> 00:36:55,000
If you apologize for that comment, perhaps I'll--

469
00:36:55,000 --> 00:36:58,260
You'll get your apology when I get Loras.

470
00:36:59,410 --> 00:37:01,000
I was as shocked as anyone

471
00:37:01,020 --> 00:37:03,370
when the Faith arrested Ser Loras.

472
00:37:04,070 --> 00:37:06,230
I have no love for these fanatics,

473
00:37:06,500 --> 00:37:08,300
but what can a Queen Mother do?

474
00:37:10,290 --> 00:37:12,480
Has the Crown suddenly stopped needing

475
00:37:12,490 --> 00:37:15,920
the troops, gold, and wheat my house supplies?

476
00:37:15,920 --> 00:37:17,140
I can assure you,

477
00:37:17,790 --> 00:37:19,850
our alliance with house Tyrell remains--

478
00:37:19,850 --> 00:37:21,310
Do you expect the alliance to continue

479
00:37:21,310 --> 00:37:24,020
after you've thrown our future into prison?

480
00:37:25,420 --> 00:37:26,720
As I said,

481
00:37:26,930 --> 00:37:28,940
I didn't imprison anyone.

482
00:37:29,030 --> 00:37:30,810
As for your veiled threats--

483
00:37:30,870 --> 00:37:32,160
What veil?

484
00:37:34,250 --> 00:37:35,430
The Lannister-Tyrell alliance

485
00:37:35,430 --> 00:37:38,370
brought peace to a war-torn country.

486
00:37:38,830 --> 00:37:39,540
Do you really want to see

487
00:37:39,540 --> 00:37:42,230
the Seven Kingdoms slide back into warfare?

488
00:37:45,270 --> 00:37:47,150
I didn't trust your father.

489
00:37:47,750 --> 00:37:49,780
I didn't particularly like him.

490
00:37:49,970 --> 00:37:53,110
But I respected him. He was no fool.

491
00:37:53,420 --> 00:37:56,940
He understood that sometimes we must work with our rivals

492
00:37:56,950 --> 00:37:58,740
rather than destroy them.

493
00:37:58,760 --> 00:38:00,730
House Lannister has no rival.

494
00:38:03,140 --> 00:38:06,500
The High Septon has called for an inquest, not a trial.

495
00:38:06,620 --> 00:38:08,120
Just a small hearing to determine

496
00:38:08,120 --> 00:38:11,260
whether the charges against Loras have merit,

497
00:38:11,290 --> 00:38:12,740
which I'm sure they don't.

498
00:38:13,180 --> 00:38:16,710
Loras will be freed, our happy alliance will continue...

499
00:38:18,360 --> 00:38:21,230
And we'll forget this unfortunate conversation ever happened.

500
00:38:23,320 --> 00:38:25,170
Good day, Lady Olenna.

501
00:38:43,990 --> 00:38:47,090
You are aware of the rumors concerning you and Renly?

502
00:38:48,440 --> 00:38:50,540
I don't pay attention to rumors.

503
00:38:51,040 --> 00:38:53,990
You were said to be despondent when he died.

504
00:38:54,640 --> 00:38:57,690
Witnesses state that you refused to leave his bedside

505
00:38:57,690 --> 00:39:00,180
even as Stannis's army closed in.

506
00:39:00,730 --> 00:39:04,640
He was my friend. He was my king.

507
00:39:05,200 --> 00:39:07,070
Wasn't Joffrey your king?

508
00:39:07,360 --> 00:39:09,780
He was anointed by the Seven, not Renly.

509
00:39:10,090 --> 00:39:14,480
I was wrong to support Renly's claim, I know that.

510
00:39:15,740 --> 00:39:17,590
But I was forgiven by Joffrey.

511
00:39:18,370 --> 00:39:20,640
I fought for him at the battle of Blackwater.

512
00:39:20,740 --> 00:39:23,470
Yes, wearing Renly's armor.

513
00:39:24,700 --> 00:39:26,240
Why does it matter what I wore?

514
00:39:26,240 --> 00:39:28,420
Do you deny all the charges against you?

515
00:39:29,390 --> 00:39:30,750
Fornication.

516
00:39:31,380 --> 00:39:33,690
Buggery. Blasphemy.

517
00:39:33,690 --> 00:39:35,180
Of course I deny them.

518
00:39:35,180 --> 00:39:37,320
You never lay with Renly Baratheon?

519
00:39:37,710 --> 00:39:38,880
Never.

520
00:39:39,340 --> 00:39:41,340
Nor any other man?

521
00:39:42,130 --> 00:39:43,440
Never.

522
00:39:45,820 --> 00:39:48,120
That will be all, Ser Loras.

523
00:39:55,580 --> 00:39:58,180
Well, I think that's quite enough of that.

524
00:39:58,180 --> 00:40:00,880
The Faith calls Queen Margaery forward.

525
00:40:01,330 --> 00:40:02,730
You call me forward?

526
00:40:02,730 --> 00:40:05,300
Yes, we have some questions for you.

527
00:40:06,110 --> 00:40:08,850
- I am the Queen. - You are.

528
00:40:09,230 --> 00:40:11,520
And according to the law of the Seven,

529
00:40:11,520 --> 00:40:14,110
neither kings nor queens are exempt

530
00:40:14,110 --> 00:40:17,000
from testimony at a holy inquest.

531
00:40:35,010 --> 00:40:38,400
How do you respond to these charges against your brother?

532
00:40:38,970 --> 00:40:40,340
They are lies.

533
00:40:40,590 --> 00:40:42,330
- All of them? - All of them.

534
00:40:42,810 --> 00:40:44,110
Queen Margaery,

535
00:40:45,300 --> 00:40:46,710
in the presence of the gods,

536
00:40:46,710 --> 00:40:48,960
do you swear that your brother is innocent

537
00:40:48,960 --> 00:40:50,660
of these charges against him

538
00:40:50,890 --> 00:40:52,610
to the best of your knowledge?

539
00:40:52,610 --> 00:40:54,310
Yes, I swear it.

540
00:40:56,090 --> 00:40:58,020
Thank you, your Grace.

541
00:41:23,700 --> 00:41:24,990
Do you know this man?

542
00:41:26,090 --> 00:41:28,660
Yes, very well.

543
00:41:29,250 --> 00:41:31,670
He is Ser Loras Tyrell, heir to Highgarden.

544
00:41:32,480 --> 00:41:34,080
How did you come to meet?

545
00:41:34,820 --> 00:41:36,540
I squired for him.

546
00:41:37,170 --> 00:41:38,780
He took a liking to me.

547
00:41:38,870 --> 00:41:41,390
He summoned me to his chamber the first day we met.

548
00:41:43,460 --> 00:41:46,320
And what occurred in his chamber?

549
00:41:46,590 --> 00:41:51,190
We engaged in intimate relations.

550
00:41:51,790 --> 00:41:53,230
You lay with him?

551
00:41:53,390 --> 00:41:54,900
That night and many others.

552
00:41:54,900 --> 00:41:57,600
Liar. He's a liar.

553
00:41:58,340 --> 00:42:00,780
Is there anyone else who can support your claim?

554
00:42:01,460 --> 00:42:02,310
Yes.

555
00:42:03,260 --> 00:42:04,840
Yes, Queen Margaery.

556
00:42:06,070 --> 00:42:09,360
She walked in on us once not long ago.

557
00:42:09,570 --> 00:42:11,110
She didn't seem surprised.

558
00:42:12,230 --> 00:42:15,780
This testimony is an insult to a great house.

559
00:42:15,910 --> 00:42:19,250
Why should the Faith or anyone else take the word of a squire

560
00:42:19,250 --> 00:42:20,650
over the heir to Highgarden?

561
00:42:20,650 --> 00:42:22,420
He has a birthmark, your Grace.

562
00:42:23,230 --> 00:42:25,220
Quite high on his thigh.

563
00:42:25,980 --> 00:42:28,630
Wine-colored and roughly the shape of Dorne.

564
00:42:29,310 --> 00:42:31,120
No! Liar!

565
00:42:33,720 --> 00:42:36,980
What are you doing? Let us pass.

566
00:42:36,980 --> 00:42:39,680
The Faith is satisfied there is enough evidence

567
00:42:39,680 --> 00:42:41,480
to bring a formal trial

568
00:42:42,120 --> 00:42:43,400
for Ser Loras

569
00:42:44,360 --> 00:42:45,640
and Queen Margaery.

570
00:42:45,650 --> 00:42:46,500
What?

571
00:42:47,240 --> 00:42:48,950
Bearing false witness before the gods

572
00:42:48,950 --> 00:42:51,220
is as grave a sin as any, my lady.

573
00:42:52,160 --> 00:42:53,070
Take her.

574
00:42:53,470 --> 00:42:56,150
No. Tommen.

575
00:42:56,510 --> 00:42:57,350
Tommen!

576
00:42:59,200 --> 00:43:01,530
You can't do this. I am the queen.

577
00:43:01,710 --> 00:43:03,940
Tommen! Tommen!

578
00:43:05,040 --> 00:43:06,490
I am your queen. How dare you?

579
00:43:06,490 --> 00:43:07,950
Take your hands off me!

580
00:43:10,000 --> 00:43:10,970
Tommen!

581
00:43:34,580 --> 00:43:35,630
What do you want?

582
00:43:36,050 --> 00:43:39,270
Lord Ramsay sent me to draw you a bath, my lady.

583
00:43:40,280 --> 00:43:41,800
You want to be clean and fresh

584
00:43:41,810 --> 00:43:43,480
for your new husband, don't you?

585
00:44:00,970 --> 00:44:02,270
You're so beautiful,

586
00:44:03,430 --> 00:44:05,320
but you need to keep him happy.

587
00:44:06,440 --> 00:44:09,290
Ramsay gets bored easily.

588
00:44:11,040 --> 00:44:12,830
You don't want to end up like--

589
00:44:14,600 --> 00:44:17,030
well, like the others.

590
00:44:18,280 --> 00:44:19,350
What others?

591
00:44:20,030 --> 00:44:21,520
I shouldn't gossip.

592
00:44:21,940 --> 00:44:23,810
Oh, it's good to see the red again.

593
00:44:24,960 --> 00:44:26,480
No point hiding anymore.

594
00:44:26,490 --> 00:44:27,850
What others?

595
00:44:28,080 --> 00:44:30,730
Let's see, there was kyra

596
00:44:30,890 --> 00:44:32,540
the blacksmith's daughter.

597
00:44:32,890 --> 00:44:35,420
She was tall like you, lovely figure.

598
00:44:35,420 --> 00:44:40,130
But she talked and talked and talked

599
00:44:41,300 --> 00:44:42,900
and Ramsay grew tired of that.

600
00:44:44,050 --> 00:44:45,450
Then there was Violet.

601
00:44:45,810 --> 00:44:48,400
She had gorgeous blonde hair.

602
00:44:48,400 --> 00:44:51,490
But she got pregnant.

603
00:44:51,490 --> 00:44:54,240
And, well, that was boring.

604
00:44:55,390 --> 00:44:57,970
Then Tansy.

605
00:44:57,970 --> 00:44:59,580
Such a sweet girl.

606
00:45:00,050 --> 00:45:04,610
Of course, sweet girls get a bit dull

607
00:45:04,930 --> 00:45:06,760
after a while, don't they?

608
00:45:07,170 --> 00:45:09,550
Ramsay let me come with him on that hunt.

609
00:45:09,580 --> 00:45:10,570
Hunt?

610
00:45:14,190 --> 00:45:17,720
Have you ever seen a body after the dogs have been at it?

611
00:45:18,950 --> 00:45:20,660
Not so pretty.

612
00:45:23,030 --> 00:45:25,320
But, well, it's your wedding day.

613
00:45:26,220 --> 00:45:28,250
Why am I talking about such things?

614
00:45:31,050 --> 00:45:32,460
What was your name again?

615
00:45:32,630 --> 00:45:33,580
Myranda.

616
00:45:36,350 --> 00:45:38,670
And how long have you loved him, Myranda?

617
00:45:42,870 --> 00:45:45,840
Did you imagine that he would be with you forever, is that it?

618
00:45:45,850 --> 00:45:47,580
And I came along and ruined it.

619
00:45:50,910 --> 00:45:53,390
I'm Sansa Stark of Winterfell.

620
00:45:54,600 --> 00:45:58,430
This is my home and you can't frighten me.

621
00:46:04,890 --> 00:46:07,440
Are you done with your bath, my lady?

622
00:46:08,230 --> 00:46:10,080
Go. I can finish on my own.

623
00:46:36,380 --> 00:46:37,300
Yes?

624
00:46:46,660 --> 00:46:49,470
I've come to escort you to the godswood, my lady.

625
00:46:54,090 --> 00:46:57,340
If you please, my lady, will you take my arm?

626
00:46:57,390 --> 00:46:58,150
No.

627
00:47:00,430 --> 00:47:03,040
Lord Ramsay, he said I'm to take your arm.

628
00:47:03,050 --> 00:47:04,560
I'm not touching you.

629
00:47:06,760 --> 00:47:07,700
Please.

630
00:47:09,010 --> 00:47:10,180
He'll punish me.

631
00:47:12,460 --> 00:47:14,780
You think I care what he does to you?

632
00:48:32,590 --> 00:48:35,070
Who comes before the old gods this night?

633
00:48:36,380 --> 00:48:39,400
Sansa of the house Stark

634
00:48:40,800 --> 00:48:42,370
comes here to be wed.

635
00:48:44,510 --> 00:48:48,390
A woman grown, trueborn and noble.

636
00:48:49,480 --> 00:48:52,020
She comes to beg the blessings of the gods.

637
00:48:55,130 --> 00:48:56,660
Who comes to claim her?

638
00:49:05,770 --> 00:49:07,680
Ramsay of house Bolton.

639
00:49:09,020 --> 00:49:11,520
Heir to the Dreadfort and winterfell.

640
00:49:14,010 --> 00:49:15,030
Who gives her?

641
00:49:18,750 --> 00:49:23,280
Theon of house Greyjoy, who was--

642
00:49:28,020 --> 00:49:29,820
who was her father's ward.

643
00:49:32,130 --> 00:49:35,450
Lady Sansa, will you take this man?

644
00:50:05,520 --> 00:50:06,810
I take this man.

645
00:50:39,010 --> 00:50:40,930
Are you pleased, my lady?

646
00:50:43,870 --> 00:50:46,450
Good. I want you to be happy.

647
00:50:57,030 --> 00:50:59,300
My father said you're still a virgin.

648
00:51:04,930 --> 00:51:07,600
- Uh, yes. - Why?

649
00:51:11,780 --> 00:51:13,700
Why are you still a virgin?

650
00:51:15,500 --> 00:51:16,910
Afraid of dwarves?

651
00:51:18,660 --> 00:51:20,670
Lord-- lord Tyrion was kind.

652
00:51:20,670 --> 00:51:24,090
He was gentle. He never touched me.

653
00:51:26,120 --> 00:51:27,630
You're not lying to me?

654
00:51:28,060 --> 00:51:29,060
No, my lord.

655
00:51:29,060 --> 00:51:31,680
Lying to your husband on his wedding night,

656
00:51:32,590 --> 00:51:35,350
that would be a bad way to start a marriage.

657
00:51:40,540 --> 00:51:42,280
We're man and wife now.

658
00:51:43,500 --> 00:51:45,190
We should be honest with each other.

659
00:51:46,100 --> 00:51:47,140
Don't you think?

660
00:51:48,700 --> 00:51:49,610
Yes.

661
00:52:00,580 --> 00:52:01,450
Good.

662
00:52:04,700 --> 00:52:06,180
Take off your clothes.

663
00:52:10,180 --> 00:52:11,570
Oh, no, no, no.

664
00:52:13,070 --> 00:52:14,750
You stay here, Reek.

665
00:52:15,600 --> 00:52:16,910
You watch.

666
00:52:29,970 --> 00:52:31,980
Do I need to ask a second time?

667
00:52:32,620 --> 00:52:34,510
I hate asking a second time.

668
00:53:03,040 --> 00:53:04,120
Reek...

669
00:53:05,190 --> 00:53:06,930
I told you to watch.

670
00:53:13,100 --> 00:53:15,430
You've known Sansa since she was a girl.

671
00:53:17,330 --> 00:53:19,050
Now watch her become a woman.

