1
00:02:31,410 --> 00:02:34,510
- Look out! - Fire! Fire!

2
00:03:00,170 --> 00:03:02,770
A band of 20 men, maybe less.

3
00:03:03,220 --> 00:03:05,400
They were in and out before anyone spotted them.

4
00:03:05,400 --> 00:03:07,330
Burnt our food stores to the ground,

5
00:03:07,330 --> 00:03:09,390
all our siege weapons destroyed.

6
00:03:09,690 --> 00:03:11,910
- Dozens of tents were-- - Horses?

7
00:03:12,010 --> 00:03:14,340
We're still getting a count, but hundreds are dead.

8
00:03:14,450 --> 00:03:16,070
20 men rode into our camp

9
00:03:16,070 --> 00:03:18,060
without a single guard sounding the alarm?

10
00:03:18,060 --> 00:03:20,480
The northerners know more about their land than we ever will.

11
00:03:20,480 --> 00:03:21,800
Put last night's guards in chains.

12
00:03:21,800 --> 00:03:23,950
Either they fell asleep or they conspired with the enemy.

13
00:03:23,960 --> 00:03:26,800
- Find out the truth and then hang them. - Your Grace.

14
00:03:27,520 --> 00:03:30,970
Unless there's a thaw, we can't press forward to Winterfell

15
00:03:30,970 --> 00:03:33,640
and we don't have enough food to get us back to Castle Black.

16
00:03:33,640 --> 00:03:35,400
We're not returning to Castle Black.

17
00:03:35,400 --> 00:03:36,370
Forgive me, Your Grace,

18
00:03:36,370 --> 00:03:38,780
I never claimed to be an expert in military matters,

19
00:03:38,780 --> 00:03:42,180
but if we can't march forward and we won't march back...

20
00:03:55,690 --> 00:03:58,000
Have the dead horses butchered for meat.

21
00:04:39,000 --> 00:04:40,300
Halt!

22
00:04:41,480 --> 00:04:43,130
Halt!

23
00:04:46,660 --> 00:04:48,620
There it is!

24
00:05:29,040 --> 00:05:30,780
Open the gates.

25
00:05:46,980 --> 00:05:48,490
It was a failure.

26
00:05:49,330 --> 00:05:50,600
It wasn't.

27
00:05:51,870 --> 00:05:53,780
I went to save them. I failed.

28
00:05:55,840 --> 00:05:57,370
You didn't fail him.

29
00:05:58,260 --> 00:05:59,300
Or him.

30
00:05:59,860 --> 00:06:01,300
Or her.

31
00:06:02,260 --> 00:06:05,530
Every one of them is alive because of you and no one else.

32
00:06:07,250 --> 00:06:09,330
I don't think that fact's lost on them.

33
00:07:03,150 --> 00:07:06,070
You have a good heart, Jon Snow.

34
00:07:07,020 --> 00:07:08,800
It'll get us all killed.

35
00:07:15,650 --> 00:07:16,970
Out of my way.

36
00:07:43,610 --> 00:07:45,260
You sent for me, Your Grace?

37
00:07:45,260 --> 00:07:47,470
Find some healthy horses and a few knights to guard you.

38
00:07:47,470 --> 00:07:49,170
I'm sending you back to Castle Black.

39
00:07:49,490 --> 00:07:51,630
Tell the Lord Commander his king commands him

40
00:07:51,630 --> 00:07:54,160
to send food, supplies, fresh horses.

41
00:07:54,250 --> 00:07:56,060
In return, when I take the throne,

42
00:07:56,060 --> 00:07:59,030
I'll make sure the Night's Watch has all the men it requires.

43
00:07:59,050 --> 00:08:02,050
He can guard all 19 castles on the Wall if he so wishes.

44
00:08:04,490 --> 00:08:07,490
Your Grace, you named me your Hand.

45
00:08:07,950 --> 00:08:09,040
Yes.

46
00:08:09,150 --> 00:08:11,140
The King's Hand should never abandon the king,

47
00:08:11,140 --> 00:08:12,590
especially in time of war.

48
00:08:12,590 --> 00:08:14,760
You're not abandoning me. You're obeying a command.

49
00:08:14,760 --> 00:08:17,170
A boy with a scroll could deliver this message.

50
00:08:17,170 --> 00:08:19,340
And if Jon Snow refuses the boy with the scroll,

51
00:08:19,340 --> 00:08:20,880
what does the boy say?

52
00:08:21,340 --> 00:08:23,720
I didn't name you Hand for your expertise in military matters.

53
00:08:23,720 --> 00:08:26,140
Ride for Castle Black. Don't come back empty-handed.

54
00:08:33,050 --> 00:08:35,420
Your Grace, perhaps Queen Selyse

55
00:08:35,420 --> 00:08:37,200
and Princess Shireen could accompany me.

56
00:08:37,200 --> 00:08:38,920
My family stays with me.

57
00:08:39,210 --> 00:08:41,610
At least let me take Shireen.

58
00:08:41,810 --> 00:08:43,950
A siege is no place for a little girl.

59
00:08:43,950 --> 00:08:45,750
My family stays with me.

60
00:09:22,600 --> 00:09:23,840
What's this one now?

61
00:09:23,840 --> 00:09:26,410
"The Dance of Dragons: A True Telling"

62
00:09:26,490 --> 00:09:27,970
by Grand Maester Munkun.

63
00:09:28,120 --> 00:09:30,130
Now that sounds like a proper story.

64
00:09:31,040 --> 00:09:33,400
Ser Byron Swann wanted to kill the dragon Vhagar.

65
00:09:33,830 --> 00:09:36,510
He polished his shield for a week so that it was like a mirror.

66
00:09:36,510 --> 00:09:38,760
And he crouched behind it and crept forward,

67
00:09:38,760 --> 00:09:40,930
hoping the dragon would only see its own reflection.

68
00:09:40,930 --> 00:09:44,270
But the dragon saw a dumb man holding a mirrored shield.

69
00:09:44,270 --> 00:09:46,000
And burnt him to a crisp.

70
00:09:46,620 --> 00:09:50,680
Thus ending the dragon-slaying career of Ser Byron Swann.

71
00:09:54,480 --> 00:09:56,520
I made you something, Princess.

72
00:10:03,450 --> 00:10:04,560
Do you like it?

73
00:10:04,560 --> 00:10:05,750
He's beautiful.

74
00:10:07,220 --> 00:10:09,080
- Thank you. - You're very welcome.

75
00:10:09,390 --> 00:10:12,050
Will you make me a doe, too? So that he can have company?

76
00:10:12,060 --> 00:10:13,180
Of course I will.

77
00:10:15,170 --> 00:10:16,900
But why am I getting a present?

78
00:10:18,300 --> 00:10:19,800
Because you deserve it.

79
00:10:21,330 --> 00:10:24,640
My son was always on me, trying to teach me to read.

80
00:10:25,330 --> 00:10:27,020
Gods, I was stubborn about it.

81
00:10:28,550 --> 00:10:30,360
Made it this far without reading.

82
00:10:30,360 --> 00:10:32,350
Seemed to me I could make it to the grave.

83
00:10:34,990 --> 00:10:36,390
Wish I'd listened to him.

84
00:10:38,660 --> 00:10:40,940
This is my own poor way of saying thank you.

85
00:10:44,670 --> 00:10:46,510
For teaching me to be a grown-up.

86
00:10:49,660 --> 00:10:51,630
I'll be gone for a few days, Princess.

87
00:10:52,640 --> 00:10:55,240
I want to hear all about "The Dance of Dragons" when I'm back.

88
00:10:55,430 --> 00:10:57,010
You'll read it yourself.

89
00:11:18,670 --> 00:11:19,950
Prince Doran.

90
00:11:20,000 --> 00:11:22,800
Forgive us. We started without you.

91
00:11:23,620 --> 00:11:25,520
Please, sit.

92
00:11:26,370 --> 00:11:27,860
Princess Myrcella.

93
00:11:28,740 --> 00:11:29,860
Uncle.

94
00:11:30,260 --> 00:11:31,670
What a lovely dress.

95
00:11:31,670 --> 00:11:33,920
- You don't like it? - You must be cold.

96
00:11:33,920 --> 00:11:37,030
Not at all. The Dornish climate agrees with me.

97
00:11:38,920 --> 00:11:40,640
Prince Trystane.

98
00:11:43,740 --> 00:11:45,080
How's your jaw?

99
00:11:45,920 --> 00:11:47,310
A fleabite.

100
00:11:47,310 --> 00:11:49,100
What are you doing in Dorne?

101
00:11:49,100 --> 00:11:51,910
Looking after the safety of my niece, the Princess Myrcella.

102
00:11:51,910 --> 00:11:55,040
And rather than send a raven or speak to me directly,

103
00:11:55,040 --> 00:11:57,230
you decided to enter my country in secret

104
00:11:57,230 --> 00:11:59,220
and abduct our guest by force?

105
00:11:59,220 --> 00:12:01,350
We received a threatening message.

106
00:12:02,580 --> 00:12:05,810
The princess's necklace in the jaws of a viper.

107
00:12:06,840 --> 00:12:08,950
That necklace was stolen from my room.

108
00:12:14,760 --> 00:12:17,380
Oh, excellent.

109
00:12:17,810 --> 00:12:19,460
A last meal before the beheading?

110
00:12:19,600 --> 00:12:21,180
Oh, I can't behead you.

111
00:12:21,750 --> 00:12:23,230
Many in Dorne want war.

112
00:12:24,000 --> 00:12:25,300
But I've seen war.

113
00:12:26,110 --> 00:12:28,620
I've seen the bodies piled on the battlefields.

114
00:12:29,080 --> 00:12:32,150
I've seen the orphans starving in the cities.

115
00:12:32,340 --> 00:12:34,330
I don't want to lead my people into that hell.

116
00:12:34,330 --> 00:12:37,230
No, you want to break bread with the Lannisters.

117
00:12:37,230 --> 00:12:39,660
And that is precisely what we are doing.

118
00:12:41,300 --> 00:12:45,130
Let us drink to Tommen, the First of His Name,

119
00:12:45,130 --> 00:12:47,450
King of the Andals and the First Men,

120
00:12:47,450 --> 00:12:49,430
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms.

121
00:13:07,110 --> 00:13:09,380
King Tommen insists

122
00:13:09,710 --> 00:13:11,890
on his sister's return to the capital?

123
00:13:13,640 --> 00:13:15,190
I'm afraid he does.

124
00:13:16,870 --> 00:13:19,340
I cannot disobey my king's command.

125
00:13:20,050 --> 00:13:22,330
She will return with you to King's Landing.

126
00:13:22,470 --> 00:13:26,160
And my son Prince Trystane will accompany you both.

127
00:13:26,160 --> 00:13:29,260
If the alliance between the Iron Throne and Dorne is to continue,

128
00:13:29,710 --> 00:13:31,910
their engagement must stand.

129
00:13:32,560 --> 00:13:33,880
I accept.

130
00:13:33,880 --> 00:13:35,930
One more thing. My brother was named

131
00:13:35,930 --> 00:13:38,440
to the small council before his death.

132
00:13:38,840 --> 00:13:42,790
Your father understood the importance of keeping Dorne in the fold.

133
00:13:42,790 --> 00:13:43,880
With Oberyn gone,

134
00:13:43,880 --> 00:13:46,470
Trystane will take his place on the small council.

135
00:13:47,110 --> 00:13:48,600
You have my word.

136
00:13:48,600 --> 00:13:50,950
The word of a kingslayer.

137
00:13:52,450 --> 00:13:56,500
No wonder you can't stand. You have no spine.

138
00:13:57,760 --> 00:13:59,690
You are mother to four of my nieces,

139
00:13:59,690 --> 00:14:01,490
girls I love very much.

140
00:14:01,500 --> 00:14:04,410
For their sake, I hope you live a long and happy life.

141
00:14:04,410 --> 00:14:07,350
Speak to me that way again, and you won't.

142
00:14:14,580 --> 00:14:18,250
May I inquire as to the fate of my man Bronn?

143
00:14:18,460 --> 00:14:20,960
Tell me, Ser Jaime, in King's Landing,

144
00:14:21,460 --> 00:14:24,760
how do they punish a commoner who strikes a prince?

145
00:14:24,760 --> 00:14:26,700
He said it was just a fleabite.

146
00:14:28,990 --> 00:14:30,360
The fault is mine.

147
00:14:30,640 --> 00:14:33,130
Bronn is merely a soldier following my orders.

148
00:14:33,150 --> 00:14:35,250
If anyone should be punished, it's me.

149
00:14:36,310 --> 00:14:39,630
Prince Trystane must learn judgment if he is to rule one day.

150
00:14:39,630 --> 00:14:41,100
I'll let him decide.

151
00:14:46,050 --> 00:14:49,010
I have learned the value of mercy from my father.

152
00:14:49,040 --> 00:14:52,090
- I'll set your man free. - You're a good man.

153
00:14:52,560 --> 00:14:54,140
On one condition.

154
00:15:02,190 --> 00:15:04,760
Why do we play? I'm better than you.

155
00:15:04,760 --> 00:15:07,350
I'll always be better than you.

156
00:15:07,350 --> 00:15:10,130
Have I ever missed once?

157
00:15:10,730 --> 00:15:12,970
I don't think I have. I can't recall.

158
00:15:12,970 --> 00:15:15,450
You must love humiliation. Or pain.

159
00:15:15,450 --> 00:15:19,140
Which do you love most, humiliation or pain?

160
00:15:21,080 --> 00:15:22,740
That one hurt, didn't it?

161
00:15:23,480 --> 00:15:24,800
You going to cry?

162
00:15:25,630 --> 00:15:27,040
Give up, little sister.

163
00:15:27,330 --> 00:15:29,800
- You're going to miss. - Oh, I never miss.

164
00:15:29,800 --> 00:15:32,300
You will. You're thinking too much.

165
00:15:32,880 --> 00:15:36,000
Now you're nervous. What if she's right?

166
00:15:39,580 --> 00:15:42,140
- Luck. - Now it's my turn.

167
00:15:42,210 --> 00:15:43,550
You're too slow.

168
00:15:43,810 --> 00:15:45,580
You've always been too slow.

169
00:16:02,160 --> 00:16:04,270
Am I gonna be happy at the end of this walk?

170
00:16:04,270 --> 00:16:06,190
You'll find out very soon.

171
00:16:09,360 --> 00:16:11,200
Say it one more time, handsome.

172
00:16:11,350 --> 00:16:12,600
Who am I?

173
00:16:13,810 --> 00:16:16,080
The most beautiful woman in the world.

174
00:16:16,650 --> 00:16:18,160
And that's the truth.

175
00:16:18,240 --> 00:16:19,550
Slut.

176
00:16:20,870 --> 00:16:22,170
Prince Doran,

177
00:16:22,440 --> 00:16:24,360
Ser Bronn of the Blackwater.

178
00:16:25,080 --> 00:16:28,190
I didn't realize there were knights of the Blackwater.

179
00:16:28,480 --> 00:16:29,650
Only the one.

180
00:16:29,650 --> 00:16:32,340
I believe you've already met Prince Trystane.

181
00:16:33,080 --> 00:16:34,150
Prince.

182
00:16:34,850 --> 00:16:36,320
Sorry about the other day.

183
00:16:36,410 --> 00:16:38,670
Prince Trystane here is a man of mercy.

184
00:16:38,790 --> 00:16:41,120
He's agreed to grant you your freedom.

185
00:16:42,900 --> 00:16:44,270
I'm glad to hear it.

186
00:16:46,690 --> 00:16:47,880
Pie looks good.

187
00:16:47,880 --> 00:16:50,430
There was one condition.

188
00:16:59,660 --> 00:17:01,500
Perhaps some soup instead.

189
00:17:04,390 --> 00:17:06,980
Oysters, clams, and cockles.

190
00:17:08,860 --> 00:17:11,660
Oysters, clams, and cockles.

191
00:17:12,680 --> 00:17:15,420
Oysters, clams, and cockles.

192
00:17:16,250 --> 00:17:18,430
Oysters, clams, and cock--

193
00:17:18,430 --> 00:17:20,150
How much for your little clam?

194
00:17:28,620 --> 00:17:31,180
Oysters, clams, and cockles.

195
00:17:34,410 --> 00:17:37,120
Oysters, clams, and cockles.

196
00:18:05,140 --> 00:18:06,210
Come on.

197
00:18:09,310 --> 00:18:10,970
Some oysters, girl!

198
00:18:12,220 --> 00:18:14,040
I'm talking to you.

199
00:18:15,010 --> 00:18:16,080
Is, uh...

200
00:18:19,870 --> 00:18:21,030
- Girl! - Tie her up!

201
00:18:21,270 --> 00:18:23,270
Are you deaf? Girl!

202
00:18:25,250 --> 00:18:26,430
Girl!

203
00:18:32,330 --> 00:18:33,370
My lord.

204
00:18:37,770 --> 00:18:38,680
My lord.

205
00:18:39,520 --> 00:18:40,910
Lord Tyrell.

206
00:18:41,140 --> 00:18:42,940
On behalf of the Iron Bank,

207
00:18:43,030 --> 00:18:44,570
may I be the first to welcome you

208
00:18:44,570 --> 00:18:46,970
to the Free City of Braavos.

209
00:18:46,970 --> 00:18:48,640
I hope your journey was trouble-free.

210
00:18:48,640 --> 00:18:50,590
A bit of chop the last few days.

211
00:18:50,600 --> 00:18:52,340
Nothing too awful.

212
00:18:52,430 --> 00:18:55,280
Good to see the old chap still guarding the harbor.

213
00:18:55,360 --> 00:18:57,430
And how goes the harvest in the Reach?

214
00:18:57,430 --> 00:18:59,800
Ah, the vintners say this might be

215
00:18:59,800 --> 00:19:03,020
the best year for red grapes in half a century.

216
00:19:03,130 --> 00:19:06,120
If we come to a satisfactory arrangement,

217
00:19:06,120 --> 00:19:10,790
I'll be sure to send a cask of the Arbor's finest your way.

218
00:19:11,070 --> 00:19:13,330
I'm afraid I don't partake.

219
00:19:20,940 --> 00:19:25,230
Some consider usury distasteful, dishonorable.

220
00:19:25,570 --> 00:19:27,400
Pure nonsense, of course.

221
00:19:27,400 --> 00:19:29,590
I'm glad we see eye to eye on this matter.

222
00:19:29,810 --> 00:19:32,030
Did you know that at one point Maegor the third

223
00:19:32,030 --> 00:19:34,720
tried to outlaw it in the Seven Kingdoms?

224
00:19:34,730 --> 00:19:37,360
Wanted to arrest anyone caught charging interest

225
00:19:37,360 --> 00:19:39,660
and cut off both their hands.

226
00:19:39,660 --> 00:19:41,950
Most unfortunate for the glovers.

227
00:19:41,990 --> 00:19:43,960
If a man charges no interest on a loan,

228
00:19:43,960 --> 00:19:46,000
then he has nothing to gain and everything to lose,

229
00:19:46,000 --> 00:19:47,610
so why chance it?

230
00:19:47,630 --> 00:19:49,430
Whereas the promise of reward

231
00:19:49,430 --> 00:19:51,110
makes a man willing to gamble.

232
00:19:51,780 --> 00:19:55,370
We are not gamblers here at the Iron Bank, Lord Tyrell.

233
00:19:55,370 --> 00:19:57,820
You are the world's best gamblers.

234
00:19:57,830 --> 00:20:01,690
And all those bets you won built this.

235
00:20:13,250 --> 00:20:14,460
We should celebrate.

236
00:20:14,460 --> 00:20:17,040
I'm afraid I still have a good deal of work to do.

237
00:20:17,040 --> 00:20:18,830
Oh, nonsense. Work's over. Do you sing?

238
00:20:18,840 --> 00:20:20,490
- I don't have that gift. - Oh, it's not a gift.

239
00:20:20,490 --> 00:20:22,330
It's a skill. Anyone can learn it.

240
00:20:22,340 --> 00:20:26,680
*So give me a kiss by the Long Canal*

241
00:20:26,680 --> 00:20:30,330
*And give me two kisses in Salty Town*

242
00:20:30,460 --> 00:20:35,460
*For we're going to die tomorrow*

243
00:20:35,650 --> 00:20:38,950
*The bareheaded beggar, the king with his crown...*

244
00:20:39,210 --> 00:20:41,720
Thought that old shit would never stop singing.

245
00:20:41,730 --> 00:20:43,120
Wasn't bad, though.

246
00:20:43,450 --> 00:20:45,750
The Tyrells can all rot in hell.

247
00:20:45,980 --> 00:20:47,600
Treasonous cunts.

248
00:20:47,980 --> 00:20:50,480
They were going to make that boy-fucker Renly king.

249
00:20:51,590 --> 00:20:53,110
This is the place, lads.

250
00:20:53,910 --> 00:20:56,220
The sleekest little minks in Braavos.

251
00:20:56,370 --> 00:20:58,600
- You buying? - Oh, I'm buying.

252
00:20:59,000 --> 00:21:00,960
But I never was good at sharing.

253
00:21:22,060 --> 00:21:24,220
Sell your fish somewhere else.

254
00:21:24,220 --> 00:21:27,300
Oh, let her in, Brusco. I'm hungry.

255
00:21:27,970 --> 00:21:29,510
Come here, sweetness.

256
00:21:33,390 --> 00:21:36,440
They say oysters get the juices flowing.

257
00:21:36,460 --> 00:21:38,500
We'll take half a dozen.

258
00:21:40,090 --> 00:21:41,550
Three coppers.

259
00:21:42,950 --> 00:21:45,950
Here's a silver because the lady likes you.

260
00:22:12,080 --> 00:22:13,250
Too old.

261
00:22:17,370 --> 00:22:18,300
Brea.

262
00:22:33,610 --> 00:22:35,000
Too old.

263
00:22:37,090 --> 00:22:40,440
I have just the one. Anara.

264
00:22:41,830 --> 00:22:44,140
Our most expensive girl.

265
00:22:45,020 --> 00:22:48,050
But well worth it, I assure you.

266
00:22:53,290 --> 00:22:54,780
Too old.

267
00:23:02,880 --> 00:23:04,900
Do you have what I want or not?

268
00:23:05,130 --> 00:23:08,070
Of course. Of course.

269
00:23:14,580 --> 00:23:15,820
These fresh?

270
00:23:20,010 --> 00:23:22,610
Come on, the lads are hungry.

271
00:23:26,080 --> 00:23:29,530
Nothing better for your cockstand than fresh oysters.

272
00:23:31,030 --> 00:23:32,240
- Thank you. - I'll have one.

273
00:23:33,940 --> 00:23:35,090
Any vinegar?

274
00:23:36,760 --> 00:23:38,920
Who let this girl in? Shoo! Shoo!

275
00:23:59,500 --> 00:24:00,610
Good.

276
00:24:10,770 --> 00:24:12,490
I'll tell you when we're done.

277
00:24:18,420 --> 00:24:20,430
You'll have a fresh one for me tomorrow?

278
00:24:21,240 --> 00:24:22,530
Of course.

279
00:24:27,260 --> 00:24:28,930
I'll have you whipped, girl.

280
00:24:28,930 --> 00:24:30,970
Go, go on. Out, out, go.

281
00:24:45,040 --> 00:24:46,520
Valar morghulis.

282
00:25:02,640 --> 00:25:03,600
And?

283
00:25:04,420 --> 00:25:06,150
The thin man wasn't hungry today.

284
00:25:06,560 --> 00:25:08,610
Perhaps that is why a man is thin.

285
00:25:09,710 --> 00:25:10,770
Tomorrow.

286
00:25:10,900 --> 00:25:11,990
Tomorrow.

287
00:25:15,070 --> 00:25:16,450
A girl has work to do.

288
00:25:30,350 --> 00:25:32,180
Your rebellion is over.

289
00:25:34,410 --> 00:25:36,730
You can swear your allegiance to me now...

290
00:25:38,150 --> 00:25:39,450
or you can die.

291
00:26:15,180 --> 00:26:17,150
I believe in second chances.

292
00:26:19,530 --> 00:26:21,950
I don't believe in third chances.

293
00:26:50,500 --> 00:26:52,240
You write like a seven-year-old.

294
00:26:53,560 --> 00:26:56,210
Your maester kindly agreed to copy it over for me.

295
00:26:56,210 --> 00:26:57,730
He didn't try to make you pay?

296
00:26:59,830 --> 00:27:01,290
Maybe he's changed.

297
00:27:02,430 --> 00:27:05,150
The queen will be thrilled to know you're bringing her daughter home.

298
00:27:05,380 --> 00:27:06,510
She will.

299
00:27:06,940 --> 00:27:08,740
You love her very much, don't you?

300
00:27:08,930 --> 00:27:10,720
Of course, she's my niece.

301
00:27:11,550 --> 00:27:13,190
I wasn't talking about her.

302
00:27:15,260 --> 00:27:17,100
You think I disapprove.

303
00:27:17,640 --> 00:27:18,760
Why?

304
00:27:19,210 --> 00:27:22,070
Because people disapprove of that sort of thing where you are from?

305
00:27:22,080 --> 00:27:24,710
They disapproved of Oberyn and me where you are from.

306
00:27:25,430 --> 00:27:28,990
Here no one blinked an eye.

307
00:27:30,160 --> 00:27:31,450
100 years ago,

308
00:27:31,450 --> 00:27:33,330
no one would have blinked an eye at you

309
00:27:34,280 --> 00:27:36,370
if you'd been named Targaryen.

310
00:27:37,840 --> 00:27:39,090
It's always changing,

311
00:27:39,090 --> 00:27:41,960
who we're supposed to love and who we're not.

312
00:27:43,270 --> 00:27:45,210
The only thing that stays the same

313
00:27:45,630 --> 00:27:47,790
is that we want who we want.

314
00:27:57,830 --> 00:28:00,120
I know your daughter had no part in the terrible thing

315
00:28:00,120 --> 00:28:02,230
that happened to the man I love.

316
00:28:05,270 --> 00:28:07,480
Perhaps even you are innocent of that.

317
00:28:26,170 --> 00:28:27,140
Father.

318
00:28:31,810 --> 00:28:33,060
Aren't you cold?

319
00:28:35,290 --> 00:28:37,340
No. What are you reading?

320
00:28:38,330 --> 00:28:41,220
- "The Dance of Dragons." - What's it about?

321
00:28:41,220 --> 00:28:43,650
It's the story of the fight between Rhaenyra Targaryen

322
00:28:43,660 --> 00:28:46,570
and her half-brother Aegon for control over the Seven Kingdoms.

323
00:28:47,270 --> 00:28:49,550
Both of them thought they belonged on the Iron Throne.

324
00:28:50,260 --> 00:28:52,830
When people started declaring for one of them or the other,

325
00:28:52,860 --> 00:28:55,060
their fight divided the kingdoms in two.

326
00:28:55,330 --> 00:28:58,410
Brothers fought brothers, dragons fought dragons.

327
00:29:00,210 --> 00:29:03,590
By the time it was over, thousands were dead.

328
00:29:04,640 --> 00:29:07,270
And it was a disaster for the Targaryens as well.

329
00:29:07,550 --> 00:29:09,300
They never truly recovered.

330
00:29:10,240 --> 00:29:11,820
"The Dance of Dragons."

331
00:29:14,060 --> 00:29:15,470
Why is that a dance?

332
00:29:16,330 --> 00:29:17,740
It's just what they call it.

333
00:29:18,120 --> 00:29:19,470
Doesn't make much sense.

334
00:29:19,890 --> 00:29:21,240
I think it's poetic.

335
00:29:28,120 --> 00:29:29,560
If you had to choose

336
00:29:31,230 --> 00:29:34,420
between Rhaenyra and Aegon...

337
00:29:36,210 --> 00:29:37,480
who would you have chosen?

338
00:29:38,020 --> 00:29:39,550
I wouldn't have chosen either.

339
00:29:40,740 --> 00:29:43,230
It's all the choosing sides that made everything so horrible.

340
00:29:43,340 --> 00:29:45,200
Sometimes a person has to choose.

341
00:29:47,650 --> 00:29:50,920
Sometimes the world forces his hand.

342
00:29:52,920 --> 00:29:55,890
If a man knows what he is...

343
00:29:57,230 --> 00:29:59,860
and remains true to himself...

344
00:30:03,550 --> 00:30:05,260
the choice is no choice at all.

345
00:30:06,280 --> 00:30:08,220
He must fulfill his destiny...

346
00:30:11,110 --> 00:30:14,400
and become who he is meant to be.

347
00:30:16,840 --> 00:30:18,820
However much he may hate it.

348
00:30:20,390 --> 00:30:21,840
It's all right, Father.

349
00:30:23,520 --> 00:30:25,540
You don't even know what I'm talking about.

350
00:30:26,520 --> 00:30:27,720
It doesn't matter.

351
00:30:28,080 --> 00:30:29,330
I want to help you.

352
00:30:30,560 --> 00:30:32,010
Is there any way I can help?

353
00:30:39,790 --> 00:30:41,060
Yes, there is.

354
00:30:41,400 --> 00:30:42,840
Good. I want to.

355
00:30:45,900 --> 00:30:47,960
I'm the Princess Shireen of House Baratheon.

356
00:30:48,190 --> 00:30:49,500
And I'm your daughter.

357
00:31:04,650 --> 00:31:05,880
Forgive me.

358
00:31:47,790 --> 00:31:50,430
Where's my father? I want to see my father.

359
00:31:50,430 --> 00:31:52,620
It will all be over soon, Princess.

360
00:31:58,070 --> 00:31:59,130
No.

361
00:32:01,300 --> 00:32:02,690
Where's my father?

362
00:32:03,370 --> 00:32:06,070
No, you can't do this. Father, where are you?

363
00:32:06,120 --> 00:32:08,090
Please, let me see my father.

364
00:32:08,330 --> 00:32:10,740
Father, where are you? Don't let her do this.

365
00:32:12,300 --> 00:32:13,570
Please let go!

366
00:32:15,180 --> 00:32:18,300
Let me see my father! Where are you? Please!

367
00:32:19,470 --> 00:32:21,330
- It's what the Lord wants. - No.

368
00:32:21,450 --> 00:32:24,080
- Please! Let go! No! - It's a good thing.

369
00:32:24,080 --> 00:32:26,180
- A great thing. - Stop. Stop!

370
00:32:26,700 --> 00:32:28,300
- Please! - Hear us now, my Lord.

371
00:32:28,300 --> 00:32:30,910
- You can't do this! - For you, we offer up this girl

372
00:32:30,910 --> 00:32:33,650
- Please! - that you may cleanse her with your fire

373
00:32:33,650 --> 00:32:35,660
and that its light may lead our way.

374
00:32:35,660 --> 00:32:37,860
Please! No, please let me see my father.

375
00:32:37,860 --> 00:32:39,860
If we don't act, we'll all starve here.

376
00:32:40,080 --> 00:32:41,140
All of us.

377
00:32:42,100 --> 00:32:43,520
But if we make this sacrifice...

378
00:32:43,520 --> 00:32:46,230
Accept this token of our faith, my Lord,

379
00:32:46,230 --> 00:32:48,250
and lead us from the darkness.

380
00:32:49,050 --> 00:32:51,810
- Lord of Light, show us the way. - Mother!

381
00:32:51,880 --> 00:32:53,460
Mother, please!

382
00:32:55,840 --> 00:32:57,640
Mother, please! Mother!

383
00:32:57,790 --> 00:32:59,240
- Mother! - We can't.

384
00:32:59,280 --> 00:33:00,380
There's no other way.

385
00:33:00,380 --> 00:33:01,880
- She has king's blood. - Please don't do this!

386
00:33:01,880 --> 00:33:03,560
Lord of Light, protect us.

387
00:33:03,560 --> 00:33:04,600
Please! Father, please!

388
00:33:04,610 --> 00:33:07,320
- For the night is dark and full of terrors. - Father, please!

389
00:33:08,320 --> 00:33:09,130
Father!

390
00:33:09,130 --> 00:33:11,310
Father, don't do this! Please!

391
00:33:11,310 --> 00:33:14,760
Mother, no! Please! Please, help!

392
00:33:14,770 --> 00:33:16,390
Don't do this!

393
00:33:16,950 --> 00:33:19,940
Please, Father! Mother, help!

394
00:33:20,020 --> 00:33:23,040
- No. - No, please! Don't do this!

395
00:33:23,040 --> 00:33:25,280
Don't do this, please, Mother!

396
00:33:26,550 --> 00:33:30,000
Please, Mother! Mother, help!

397
00:33:30,400 --> 00:33:33,280
Mother, help! Help!

398
00:33:33,550 --> 00:33:35,620
Please don't do this, Mother!

399
00:33:35,620 --> 00:33:36,720
Please!

400
00:33:37,130 --> 00:33:38,790
Please, Mother! Please!

401
00:33:39,350 --> 00:33:41,710
Please! No!

402
00:33:41,730 --> 00:33:45,230
Please! No!

403
00:34:02,620 --> 00:34:05,520
No!

404
00:34:54,970 --> 00:34:56,110
Where have you been?

405
00:34:56,690 --> 00:34:58,460
Just making sure everything is in order.

419
00:36:29,380 --> 00:36:30,570
They're waiting for you.

420
00:36:32,410 --> 00:36:33,650
Clap your hands.

421
00:37:03,800 --> 00:37:05,190
That one, the smaller man.

422
00:37:05,190 --> 00:37:07,000
No question, that's where you should put your money.

423
00:37:07,000 --> 00:37:08,230
The smaller man it is.

424
00:37:08,230 --> 00:37:10,190
I'm not putting my money anywhere.

425
00:37:10,190 --> 00:37:12,300
Kings and queens never bet on the games.

426
00:37:12,570 --> 00:37:14,520
Perhaps you should go find someone who does.

427
00:37:15,170 --> 00:37:17,850
People used to bet against me when I fought in the pits.

428
00:37:18,040 --> 00:37:20,760
He would have bet against me. Common novice mistake.

429
00:37:20,760 --> 00:37:22,560
I've spent much of my life in this arena.

430
00:37:22,570 --> 00:37:25,010
And in my experience, large men do triumph

431
00:37:25,010 --> 00:37:27,080
over smaller men far more often than not.

432
00:37:27,090 --> 00:37:30,050
Has your experience ever involved any actual fighting?

433
00:37:30,430 --> 00:37:32,020
You yourself?

434
00:37:32,020 --> 00:37:33,390
Have you ever tried to kill another man

435
00:37:33,390 --> 00:37:34,870
who was trying to kill you?

436
00:37:36,910 --> 00:37:39,930
Whenever I got into the pit against a beast like that one,

437
00:37:39,940 --> 00:37:42,760
the crowd saw me, all skin and bone back then,

438
00:37:42,770 --> 00:37:45,880
then they saw a pile of angry muscles ready to murder me.

439
00:37:45,940 --> 00:37:48,110
They couldn't get their money out fast enough.

440
00:37:48,120 --> 00:37:51,420
But the pile of angry muscles never had any muscles here

441
00:37:51,590 --> 00:37:54,450
or... here.

442
00:37:55,090 --> 00:37:56,680
And the big men were always too slow

443
00:37:56,680 --> 00:37:59,700
to stop my dagger from going where their muscles weren't.

444
00:37:59,700 --> 00:38:03,310
Yes, whenever I saw a beast like that one standing across from me

445
00:38:03,310 --> 00:38:07,050
making his beast faces, I knew I could rest easy.

446
00:38:19,580 --> 00:38:20,940
You don't approve?

447
00:38:21,060 --> 00:38:24,210
There's always been more than enough death in the world for my taste.

448
00:38:24,210 --> 00:38:26,370
I can do without it in my leisure time.

449
00:38:26,370 --> 00:38:29,070
Fair enough. Yet it's an unpleasant question,

450
00:38:29,070 --> 00:38:30,900
but what great thing has ever been accomplished

451
00:38:30,900 --> 00:38:32,700
without killing or cruelty?

452
00:38:32,780 --> 00:38:36,470
It's easy to confuse what is with what ought to be,

453
00:38:36,470 --> 00:38:39,250
especially when what is has worked out in your favor.

454
00:38:39,250 --> 00:38:40,820
I'm not talking about myself.

455
00:38:41,050 --> 00:38:43,650
I'm talking about the necessary conditions for greatness.

456
00:38:43,650 --> 00:38:45,820
That is greatness?

457
00:38:45,930 --> 00:38:49,580
That is a vital part of the great city of Meereen,

458
00:38:49,720 --> 00:38:51,890
which existed long before you or I

459
00:38:52,030 --> 00:38:55,350
and will remain standing long after we have returned to the dirt.

460
00:38:56,440 --> 00:38:58,580
My father would have liked you.

462
00:39:10,310 --> 00:39:13,100
One day your great city will return to the dirt as well.

463
00:39:13,100 --> 00:39:15,020
- At your command? - If need be.

465
00:39:21,510 --> 00:39:23,900
And how many people will die to make this happen?

466
00:39:23,900 --> 00:39:27,110
If it comes to that, they will have died for a good reason.

467
00:39:27,110 --> 00:39:29,080
Those men think they're dying for a good reason.

468
00:39:29,080 --> 00:39:30,540
Someone else's reason.

469
00:39:30,960 --> 00:39:33,200
So your reasons are true and theirs are false?

470
00:39:33,670 --> 00:39:35,770
They don't know their own minds, but you do?

471
00:39:36,200 --> 00:39:38,680
Well said. You're an eloquent man.

472
00:39:39,280 --> 00:39:40,570
Doesn't mean you're wrong.

473
00:39:41,050 --> 00:39:43,190
In my experience, eloquent men are right

474
00:39:43,190 --> 00:39:45,260
every bit as often as imbeciles.

478
00:40:12,580 --> 00:40:14,420
- Your Grace-- - Shut your mouth.

479
00:42:41,830 --> 00:42:43,730
- You can end this. - She cannot.

480
00:42:43,730 --> 00:42:44,530
You can.

481
00:44:23,680 --> 00:44:25,020
Protect your queen!

482
00:44:36,970 --> 00:44:37,810
Go!

483
00:45:03,170 --> 00:45:04,730
Your Grace! Your Grace!

484
00:45:04,730 --> 00:45:06,060
Come with me. I know a way out.

485
00:45:06,060 --> 00:45:07,060
I know a way--

486
00:45:43,570 --> 00:45:44,710
Stay close.

487
00:45:52,180 --> 00:45:53,150
This way.

488
00:46:05,170 --> 00:46:06,660
The other side. Follow me.

489
00:46:10,450 --> 00:46:11,760
Protect your queen!

490
00:49:06,270 --> 00:49:07,540
Drogon!

491
00:50:10,430 --> 00:50:11,540
Valahd.

492
00:00:14,850 --> 00:00:44,850
{\an7}{\pos(39.5,211)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10m -13 -14 l 13 -14 l 13 12 l -13 12 l -13 -14 

493
00:00:14,850 --> 00:00:44,850
{\pos(51.4,231.16)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10 

494
00:00:14,850 --> 00:00:44,850
{\pos(27.7,188.26)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10 

503
00:00:44,850 --> 00:00:54,850
{\an7}{\pos(23,181)} m 350 100 l 350 110 l 360 110 l 360 100 m 360 100 m 100 320 l 100 330 l 110 330 l 110 320 m 110 320 m 250 320 l 250 330 l 260 330 l 260 320 m 260 320 m 270 300 l 270 310 l 280 310 l 280 300 m 280 300 m 360 60 l 360 70 l 370 70 l 370 60 m 370 60 m 170 360 l 170 370 l 180 370 l 180 360 m 180 360 m 130 40 l 130 50 l 140 50 l 140 40 m 140 40 m 140 110 l 140 120 l 150 120 l 150 110 m 150 110 m 190 340 l 190 350 l 200 350 l 200 340 m 200 340 m 40 210 l 40 220 l 50 220 l 50 210 m 50 210 m 280 180 l 280 190 l 290 190 l 290 180 m 290 180 m 180 50 l 180 60 l 190 60 l 190 50 m 190 50 m 160 210 l 160 220 l 170 220 l 170 210 m 170 210 m 290 190 l 290 200 l 300 200 l 300 190 m 300 190 m 190 80 l 190 90 l 200 90 l 200 80 m 200 80 m 170 240 l 170 250 l 180 250 l 180 240 m 180 240 m 300 160 l 300 170 l 310 170 l 310 160 m 310 160 m 70 60 l 70 70 l 80 70 l 80 60 m 80 60 m 340 180 l 340 190 l 350 190 l 350 180 m 350 180 m 320 140 l 320 150 l 330 150 l 330 140 m 330 140 m 90 280 l 90 290 l 100 290 l 100 280 m 100 280 m 340 200 l 340 210 l 350 210 l 350 200 m 350 200 m 230 170 l 230 180 l 240 180 l 240 170 m 240 170 m 210 170 l 210 180 l 220 180 l 220 170 m 220 170 m 240 180 l 240 190 l 250 190 l 250 180 m 250 180 m 120 160 l 120 170 l 130 170 l 130 160 m 130 160 m 130 130 l 130 140 l 140 140 l 140 130 m 140 130 m 270 130 l 270 140 l 280 140 l 280 130 m 280 130 m 140 180 l 140 190 l 150 190 l 150 180 m 150 180 m 120 220 l 120 230 l 130 230 l 130 220 m 130 220 m 130 230 l 130 240 l 140 240 l 140 230 m 140 230 m 50 250 l 50 260 l 60 260 l 60 250 m 60 250 m 290 200 l 290 210 l 300 210 l 300 200 m 300 200 m 310 100 l 310 110 l 320 110 l 320 100 m 320 100 m 80 160 l 80 170 l 90 170 l 90 160 m 90 160 m 330 80 l 330 90 l 340 90 l 340 80 m 340 80 m 200 110 l 200 120 l 210 120 l 210 110 m 210 110 m 100 180 l 100 190 l 110 190 l 110 180 m 110 180 m 340 310 l 340 320 l 350 320 l 350 310 m 350 310 m 230 220 l 230 230 l 240 230 l 240 220 m 240 220 m 110 190 l 110 200 l 120 200 l 120 190 m 120 190 m 350 220 l 350 230 l 360 230 l 360 220 m 360 220 m 220 90 l 220 100 l 230 100 l 230 90 m 230 90 m 200 330 l 200 340 l 210 340 l 210 330 m 210 330 m 100 360 l 100 370 l 110 370 l 110 360 m 110 360 m 220 350 l 220 360 l 230 360 l 230 350 m 230 350 m 140 130 l 140 140 l 150 140 l 150 130 m 150 130 m 120 290 l 120 300 l 130 300 l 130 290 m 130 290 m 150 80 l 150 90 l 160 90 l 160 80 m 160 80 m 280 320 l 280 330 l 290 330 l 290 320 m 290 320 m 190 140 l 190 150 l 200 150 l 200 140 m 200 140 m 40 90 l 40 100 l 50 100 l 50 90 m 50 90 m 160 330 l 160 340 l 170 340 l 170 330 m 170 330 m 50 40 l 50 50 l 60 50 l 60 40 m 60 40 m 320 280 l 320 290 l 330 290 l 330 280 m 330 280 m 90 140 l 90 150 l 100 150 l 100 140 m 100 140 m 100 50 l 100 60 l 110 60 l 110 50 m 110 50 m 340 60 l 340 70 l 350 70 l 350 60 m 350 60 m 80 210 l 80 220 l 90 220 l 90 210 m 90 210 m 230 310 l 230 320 l 240 320 l 240 310 m 240 310 m 90 240 l 90 250 l 100 250 l 100 240 m 100 240 m 200 240 l 200 250 l 210 250 l 210 240 m 210 240 m 100 310 l 100 320 l 110 320 l 110 310 m 110 310 m 230 50 l 230 60 l 240 60 l 240 50 m 240 50 m 210 210 l 210 220 l 220 220 l 220 210 m 220 210 m 220 260 l 220 270 l 230 270 l 230 260 m 230 260 m 270 350 l 270 360 l 280 360 l 280 350 m 280 350 m 120 40 l 120 50 l 130 50 l 130 40 m 130 40 m 130 330 l 130 340 l 140 340 l 140 330 m 140 330 m 180 300 l 180 310 l 190 310 l 190 300 m 190 300 m 40 320 l 40 330 l 50 330 l 50 320 m 50 320 m 310 240 l 310 250 l 320 250 l 320 240 m 320 240 m 60 340 l 60 350 l 70 350 l 70 340 m 70 340 m 300 70 l 300 80 l 310 80 l 310 70 m 310 70 m 330 260 l 330 270 l 340 270 l 340 260 m 340 260 m 80 280 l 80 290 l 90 290 l 90 280 m 90 280 m 230 360 l 230 370 l 240 370 l 240 360 m 240 360 m 350 40 l 350 50 l 360 50 l 360 40 m 360 40 m 240 310 l 240 320 l 250 320 l 250 310 m 250 310 m 310 360 l 310 370 l 320 370 l 320 360 m 320 360 m 200 150 l 200 160 l 210 160 l 210 150 m 210 150 m 100 220 l 100 230 l 110 230 l 110 220 m 110 220 m 220 360 l 220 370 l 230 370 l 230 360 m 230 360 m 270 240 l 270 250 l 280 250 l 280 240 m 280 240 m 360 80 l 360 90 l 370 90 l 370 80 m 370 80 m 40 230 l 40 240 l 50 240 l 50 230 m 50 230 m 280 200 l 280 210 l 290 210 l 290 200 m 290 200 m 180 110 l 180 120 l 190 120 l 190 110 m 190 110 m 290 170 l 290 180 l 300 180 l 300 170 m 300 170 m 170 220 l 170 230 l 180 230 l 180 220 m 180 220 m 300 140 l 300 150 l 310 150 l 310 140 m 310 140 m 70 80 l 70 90 l 80 90 l 80 80 m 80 80 m 320 80 l 320 90 l 330 90 l 330 80 m 330 80 m 350 130 l 350 140 l 360 140 l 360 130 m 360 130 m 90 100 l 90 110 l 100 110 l 100 100 m 100 100 m 330 130 l 330 140 l 340 140 l 340 130 m 340 130 m 340 260 l 340 270 l 350 270 l 350 260 m 350 260 m 110 200 l 110 210 l 120 210 l 120 200 m 120 200 m 350 270 l 350 280 l 360 280 l 360 270 m 360 270 m 90 360 l 90 370 l 100 370 l 100 360 m 100 360 m 220 120 l 220 130 l 230 130 l 230 120 m 230 120 m 200 280 l 200 290 l 210 290 l 210 280 m 210 280 m 130 190 l 130 200 l 140 200 l 140 190 m 140 190 m 270 150 l 270 160 l 280 160 l 280 150 m 280 150 m 150 50 l 150 60 l 160 60 l 160 50 m 160 50 m 130 210 l 130 220 l 140 220 l 140 210 m 140 210 m 280 270 l 280 280 l 290 280 l 290 270 m 290 270 m 180 180 l 180 190 l 190 190 l 190 180 m 190 180 m 160 140 l 160 150 l 170 150 l 170 140 m 170 140 m 290 260 l 290 270 l 300 270 l 300 260 m 300 260 m 170 150 l 170 160 l 180 160 l 180 150 m 180 150 m 40 40 l 40 50 l 50 50 l 50 40 m 50 40 m 310 280 l 310 290 l 320 290 l 320 280 m 320 280 m 50 170 l 50 180 l 60 180 l 60 170 m 60 170 m 80 180 l 80 190 l 90 190 l 90 180 m 90 180 m 320 70 l 320 80 l 330 80 l 330 70 m 330 70 m 60 140 l 60 150 l 70 150 l 70 140 m 70 140 m 90 190 l 90 200 l 100 200 l 100 190 m 100 190 m 330 60 l 330 70 l 340 70 l 340 60 m 340 60 m 70 230 l 70 240 l 80 240 l 80 230 m 80 230 m 100 160 l 100 170 l 110 170 l 110 160 m 110 160 m 340 290 l 340 300 l 350 300 l 350 290 m 350 290 m 210 80 l 210 90 l 220 90 l 220 80 m 220 80 m 110 130 l 110 140 l 120 140 l 120 130 m 120 130 m 350 320 l 350 330 l 360 330 l 360 320 m 360 320 m 240 270 l 240 280 l 250 280 l 250 270 m 250 270 m 220 70 l 220 80 l 230 80 l 230 70 m 230 70 m 250 260 l 250 270 l 260 270 l 260 260 m 260 260 m 220 330 l 220 340 l 230 340 l 230 330 m 230 330 m 120 310 l 120 320 l 130 320 l 130 310 m 130 310 m 360 120 l 360 130 l 370 130 l 370 120 m 370 120 m 160 50 l 160 60 l 170 60 l 170 50 m 170 50 m 140 210 l 140 220 l 150 220 l 150 210 m 150 210 m 290 350 l 290 360 l 300 360 l 300 350 m 300 350 m 190 240 l 190 250 l 200 250 l 200 240 m 200 240 m 170 80 l 170 90 l 180 90 l 180 80 m 180 80 m 150 320 l 150 330 l 160 330 l 160 320 m 160 320 m 300 320 l 300 330 l 310 330 l 310 320 m 310 320 m 160 350 l 160 360 l 170 360 l 170 350 m 170 350 m 50 100 l 50 110 l 60 110 l 60 100 m 60 100 m 320 300 l 320 310 l 330 310 l 330 300 m 330 300 m 300 100 l 300 110 l 310 110 l 310 100 m 310 100 m 90 120 l 90 130 l 100 130 l 100 120 m 100 120 m 70 280 l 70 290 l 80 290 l 80 280 m 80 280 m 340 40 l 340 50 l 350 50 l 350 40 m 350 40 m 80 230 l 80 240 l 90 240 l 90 230 m 90 230 m 300 360 l 300 370 l 310 370 l 310 360 m 310 360 m 90 220 l 90 230 l 100 230 l 100 220 m 100 220 m 230 70 l 230 80 l 240 80 l 240 70 m 240 70 m 210 270 l 210 280 l 220 280 l 220 270 m 220 270 m 260 320 l 260 330 l 270 330 l 270 320 m 270 320 m 220 240 l 220 250 l 230 250 l 230 240 m 230 240 m 270 290 l 270 300 l 280 300 l 280 290 m 280 290 m 120 60 l 120 70 l 130 70 l 130 60 m 130 60 m 360 190 l 360 200 l 370 200 l 370 190 m 370 190 m 130 70 l 130 80 l 140 80 l 140 70 m 140 70 m 150 250 l 150 260 l 160 260 l 160 250 m 160 250 m 40 340 l 40 350 l 50 350 l 50 340 m 50 340 m 280 150 l 280 160 l 290 160 l 290 150 m 290 150 m 180 60 l 180 70 l 190 70 l 190 60 m 190 60 m 310 260 l 310 270 l 320 270 l 320 260 m 320 260 m 170 270 l 170 280 l 180 280 l 180 270 m 180 270 m 320 210 l 320 220 l 330 220 l 330 210 m 330 210 m 60 320 l 60 330 l 70 330 l 70 320 m 70 320 m 300 50 l 300 60 l 310 60 l 310 50 m 310 50 m 330 240 l 330 250 l 340 250 l 340 240 m 340 240 m 310 160 l 310 170 l 320 170 l 320 160 m 320 160 m 340 150 l 340 160 l 350 160 l 350 150 m 350 150 m 80 300 l 80 310 l 90 310 l 90 300 m 90 300 m 320 190 l 320 200 l 330 200 l 330 190 m 330 190 m 100 200 l 100 210 l 110 210 l 110 200 m 110 200 m 80 360 l 80 370 l 90 370 l 90 360 m 90 360 m 210 120 l 210 130 l 220 130 l 220 120 m 220 120 m 110 250 l 110 260 l 120 260 l 120 250 m 120 250 m 240 70 l 240 80 l 250 80 l 250 70 m 250 70 m 250 60 l 250 70 l 260 70 l 260 60 m 260 60 m 120 130 l 120 140 l 130 140 l 130 130 m 130 130 m 360 100 l 360 110 l 370 110 l 370 100 m 370 100 m 130 80 l 130 90 l 140 90 l 140 80 m 140 80 m 190 300 l 190 310 l 200 310 l 200 300 m 200 300 m 150 140 l 150 150 l 160 150 l 160 140 m 160 140 m 40 250 l 40 260 l 50 260 l 50 250 m 50 250 m 280 220 l 280 230 l 290 230 l 290 220 m 290 220 m 160 170 l 160 180 l 170 180 l 170 170 m 170 170 m 50 200 l 50 210 l 60 210 l 60 200 m 60 200 m 170 200 l 170 210 l 180 210 l 180 200 m 180 200 m 60 270 l 60 280 l 70 280 l 70 270 m 70 270 m 70 100 l 70 110 l 80 110 l 80 100 m 80 100 m 320 100 l 320 110 l 330 110 l 330 100 m 330 100 m 200 80 l 200 90 l 210 90 l 210 80 m 210 80 m 230 210 l 230 220 l 240 220 l 240 210 m 240 210 m 220 100 l 220 110 l 230 110 l 230 100 m 230 100 m 200 300 l 200 310 l 210 310 l 210 300 m 210 300 m 210 310 l 210 320 l 220 320 l 220 310 m 220 310 m 260 40 l 260 50 l 270 50 l 270 40 m 270 40 m 130 170 l 130 180 l 140 180 l 140 170 m 140 170 m 140 140 l 140 150 l 150 150 l 150 140 m 150 140 m 130 270 l 130 280 l 140 280 l 140 270 m 140 270 m 280 290 l 280 300 l 290 300 l 290 290 m 290 290 m 190 130 l 190 140 l 200 140 l 200 130 m 200 130 m 170 130 l 170 140 l 180 140 l 180 130 m 180 130 m 150 290 l 150 300 l 160 300 l 160 290 m 160 290 m 300 230 l 300 240 l 310 240 l 310 230 m 310 230 m 40 60 l 40 70 l 50 70 l 50 60 m 50 60 m 70 190 l 70 200 l 80 200 l 80 190 m 80 190 m 80 120 l 80 130 l 90 130 l 90 120 m 90 120 m 330 40 l 330 50 l 340 50 l 340 40 m 340 40 m 70 250 l 70 260 l 80 260 l 80 250 m 80 250 m 290 360 l 290 370 l 300 370 l 300 360 m 300 360 m 100 60 l 100 70 l 110 70 l 110 60 m 110 60 m 340 350 l 340 360 l 350 360 l 350 350 m 350 350 m 80 260 l 80 270 l 90 270 l 90 260 m 90 260 m 230 260 l 230 270 l 240 270 l 240 260 m 240 260 m 350 340 l 350 350 l 360 350 l 360 340 m 360 340 m 90 270 l 90 280 l 100 280 l 100 270 m 100 270 m 240 210 l 240 220 l 250 220 l 250 210 m 250 210 m 220 50 l 220 60 l 230 60 l 230 50 m 230 50 m 250 240 l 250 250 l 260 250 l 260 240 m 260 240 m 210 320 l 210 330 l 220 330 l 220 320 m 220 320 m 360 240 l 360 250 l 370 250 l 370 240 m 370 240 m 260 310 l 260 320 l 270 320 l 270 310 m 270 310 m 220 310 l 220 320 l 230 320 l 230 310 m 230 310 m 270 60 l 270 70 l 280 70 l 280 60 m 280 60 m 120 330 l 120 340 l 130 340 l 130 330 m 130 330 m 130 280 l 130 290 l 140 290 l 140 280 m 140 280 m 160 70 l 160 80 l 170 80 l 170 70 m 170 70 m 140 350 l 140 360 l 150 360 l 150 350 m 150 350 m 290 330 l 290 340 l 300 340 l 300 330 m 300 330 m 170 60 l 170 70 l 180 70 l 180 60 m 180 60 m 150 340 l 150 350 l 160 350 l 160 340 m 160 340 m 300 300 l 300 310 l 310 310 l 310 300 m 310 300 m 280 100 l 280 110 l 290 110 l 290 100 m 290 100 m 310 230 l 310 240 l 320 240 l 320 230 m 320 230 m 170 320 l 170 330 l 180 330 l 180 320 m 180 320 m 60 70 l 60 80 l 70 80 l 70 70 m 70 70 m 300 80 l 300 90 l 310 90 l 310 80 m 310 80 m 70 300 l 70 310 l 80 310 l 80 300 m 80 300 m 310 130 l 310 140 l 320 140 l 320 130 m 320 130 m 100 90 l 100 100 l 110 100 l 110 90 m 110 90 m 340 100 l 340 110 l 350 110 l 350 100 m 350 100 m 80 330 l 80 340 l 90 340 l 90 330 m 90 330 m 230 350 l 230 360 l 240 360 l 240 350 m 240 350 m 90 200 l 90 210 l 100 210 l 100 200 m 100 200 m 240 280 l 240 290 l 250 290 l 250 280 m 250 280 m 70 360 l 70 370 l 80 370 l 80 360 m 80 360 m 100 350 l 100 360 l 110 360 l 110 350 m 110 350 m 250 330 l 250 340 l 260 340 l 260 330 m 260 330 m 230 90 l 230 100 l 240 100 l 240 90 m 240 90 m 240 100 l 240 110 l 250 110 l 250 100 m 250 100 m 220 220 l 220 230 l 230 230 l 230 220 m 230 220 m 270 310 l 270 320 l 280 320 l 280 310 m 280 310 m 120 80 l 120 90 l 130 90 l 130 80 m 130 80 m 360 50 l 360 60 l 370 60 l 370 50 m 370 50 m 140 100 l 140 110 l 150 110 l 150 100 m 150 100 m 150 270 l 150 280 l 160 280 l 160 270 m 160 270 m 40 200 l 40 210 l 50 210 l 50 200 m 50 200 m 280 170 l 280 180 l 290 180 l 290 170 m 290 170 m 180 40 l 180 50 l 190 50 l 190 40 m 190 40 m 160 200 l 160 210 l 170 210 l 170 200 m 170 200 m 290 120 l 290 130 l 300 130 l 300 120 m 300 120 m 190 90 l 190 100 l 200 100 l 200 90 m 200 90 m 320 230 l 320 240 l 330 240 l 330 230 m 330 230 m 60 300 l 60 310 l 70 310 l 70 300 m 70 300 m 330 220 l 330 230 l 340 230 l 340 220 m 340 220 m 70 70 l 70 80 l 80 80 l 80 70 m 80 70 m 310 180 l 310 190 l 320 190 l 320 180 m 320 180 m 340 130 l 340 140 l 350 140 l 350 130 m 350 130 m 80 80 l 80 90 l 90 90 l 90 80 m 90 80 m 320 130 l 320 140 l 330 140 l 330 130 m 330 130 m 350 160 l 350 170 l 360 170 l 360 160 m 360 160 m 200 190 l 200 200 l 210 200 l 210 190 m 210 190 m 100 260 l 100 270 l 110 270 l 110 260 m 110 260 m 340 230 l 340 240 l 350 240 l 350 230 m 350 230 m 210 180 l 210 190 l 220 190 l 220 180 m 220 180 m 260 250 l 260 260 l 270 260 l 270 250 m 270 250 m 240 170 l 240 180 l 250 180 l 250 170 m 250 170 m 220 170 l 220 180 l 230 180 l 230 170 m 230 170 m 270 200 l 270 210 l 280 210 l 280 200 m 280 200 m 250 40 l 250 50 l 260 50 l 260 40 m 260 40 m 210 360 l 210 370 l 220 370 l 220 360 m 220 360 m 40 270 l 40 280 l 50 280 l 50 270 m 50 270 m 160 190 l 160 200 l 170 200 l 170 190 m 170 190 m 300 260 l 300 270 l 310 270 l 310 260 m 310 260 m 40 170 l 40 180 l 50 180 l 50 170 m 50 170 m 70 120 l 70 130 l 80 130 l 80 120 m 80 120 m 80 70 l 80 80 l 90 80 l 90 70 m 90 70 m 320 40 l 320 50 l 330 50 l 330 40 m 330 40 m 200 100 l 200 110 l 210 110 l 210 100 m 210 100 m 340 300 l 340 310 l 350 310 l 350 300 m 350 300 m 350 230 l 350 240 l 360 240 l 360 230 m 360 230 m 200 320 l 200 330 l 210 330 l 210 320 m 210 320 m 250 130 l 250 140 l 260 140 l 260 130 m 260 130 m 210 290 l 210 300 l 220 300 l 220 290 m 220 290 m 360 350 l 360 360 l 370 360 l 370 350 m 370 350 m 260 100 l 260 110 l 270 110 l 270 100 m 270 100 m 150 90 l 150 100 l 160 100 l 160 90 m 160 90 m 280 310 l 280 320 l 290 320 l 290 310 m 290 310 m 160 100 l 160 110 l 170 110 l 170 100 m 170 100 m 170 110 l 170 120 l 180 120 l 180 110 m 180 110 m 150 310 l 150 320 l 160 320 l 160 310 m 160 310 m 300 210 l 300 220 l 310 220 l 310 210 m 310 210 m 40 80 l 40 90 l 50 90 l 50 80 m 50 80 m 280 50 l 280 60 l 290 60 l 290 50 m 290 50 m 160 320 l 160 330 l 170 330 l 170 320 m 170 320 m 310 320 l 310 330 l 320 330 l 320 320 m 320 320 m 320 350 l 320 360 l 330 360 l 330 350 m 330 350 m 60 100 l 60 110 l 70 110 l 70 100 m 70 100 m 330 340 l 330 350 l 340 350 l 340 340 m 340 340 m 70 270 l 70 280 l 80 280 l 80 270 m 80 270 m 100 40 l 100 50 l 110 50 l 110 40 m 110 40 m 340 330 l 340 340 l 350 340 l 350 330 m 350 330 m 60 360 l 60 370 l 70 370 l 70 360 m 70 360 m 350 280 l 350 290 l 360 290 l 360 280 m 360 280 m 90 250 l 90 260 l 100 260 l 100 250 m 100 250 m 200 230 l 200 240 l 210 240 l 210 230 m 210 230 m 100 300 l 100 310 l 110 310 l 110 300 m 110 300 m 250 220 l 250 230 l 260 230 l 260 220 m 260 220 m 210 220 l 210 230 l 220 230 l 220 220 m 220 220 m 360 260 l 360 270 l 370 270 l 370 260 m 370 260 m 220 290 l 220 300 l 230 300 l 230 290 m 230 290 m 270 320 l 270 330 l 280 330 l 280 320 m 280 320 m 130 340 l 130 350 l 140 350 l 140 340 m 140 340 m 180 250 l 180 260 l 190 260 l 190 250 m 190 250 m 140 330 l 140 340 l 150 340 l 150 330 m 150 330 m 190 200 l 190 210 l 200 210 l 200 200 m 200 200 m 170 40 l 170 50 l 180 50 l 180 40 m 180 40 m 300 280 l 300 290 l 310 290 l 310 280 m 310 280 m 40 310 l 40 320 l 50 320 l 50 310 m 50 310 m 280 120 l 280 130 l 290 130 l 290 120 m 290 120 m 310 250 l 310 260 l 320 260 l 320 250 m 320 250 m 50 300 l 50 310 l 60 310 l 60 300 m 60 300 m 170 300 l 170 310 l 180 310 l 180 300 m 180 300 m 320 260 l 320 270 l 330 270 l 330 260 m 330 260 m 300 60 l 300 70 l 310 70 l 310 60 m 310 60 m 70 320 l 70 330 l 80 330 l 80 320 m 80 320 m 310 150 l 310 160 l 320 160 l 320 150 m 320 150 m 340 80 l 340 90 l 350 90 l 350 80 m 350 80 m 320 160 l 320 170 l 330 170 l 330 160 m 330 160 m 240 300 l 240 310 l 250 310 l 250 300 m 250 300 m 200 140 l 200 150 l 210 150 l 210 140 m 210 140 m 100 330 l 100 340 l 110 340 l 110 330 m 110 330 m 250 310 l 250 320 l 260 320 l 260 310 m 260 310 m 120 360 l 120 370 l 130 370 l 130 360 m 130 360 m 110 280 l 110 290 l 120 290 l 120 280 m 120 280 m 260 200 l 260 210 l 270 210 l 270 200 m 270 200 m 200 360 l 200 370 l 210 370 l 210 360 m 210 360 m 250 90 l 250 100 l 260 100 l 260 90 m 260 90 m 120 100 l 120 110 l 130 110 l 130 100 m 130 100 m 360 70 l 360 80 l 370 80 l 370 70 m 370 70 m 130 110 l 130 120 l 140 120 l 140 110 m 140 110 m 140 80 l 140 90 l 150 90 l 150 80 m 150 80 m 190 290 l 190 300 l 200 300 l 200 290 m 200 290 m 150 130 l 150 140 l 160 140 l 160 130 m 160 130 m 280 190 l 280 200 l 290 200 l 290 190 m 290 190 m 180 100 l 180 110 l 190 110 l 190 100 m 190 100 m 160 220 l 160 230 l 170 230 l 170 220 m 170 220 m 50 230 l 50 240 l 60 240 l 60 230 m 60 230 m 190 110 l 190 120 l 200 120 l 200 110 m 200 110 m 300 170 l 300 180 l 310 180 l 310 170 m 310 170 m 40 120 l 40 130 l 50 130 l 50 120 m 50 120 m 310 40 l 310 50 l 320 50 l 320 40 m 320 40 m 80 100 l 80 110 l 90 110 l 90 100 m 90 100 m 330 140 l 330 150 l 340 150 l 340 140 m 340 140 m 100 240 l 100 250 l 110 250 l 110 240 m 110 240 m 340 210 l 340 220 l 350 220 l 350 210 m 350 210 m 210 160 l 210 170 l 220 170 l 220 160 m 220 160 m 240 190 l 240 200 l 250 200 l 250 190 m 250 190 m 220 150 l 220 160 l 230 160 l 230 150 m 230 150 m 270 220 l 270 230 l 280 230 l 280 220 m 280 220 m 250 180 l 250 190 l 260 190 l 260 180 m 260 180 m 120 170 l 120 180 l 130 180 l 130 170 m 130 170 m 360 300 l 360 310 l 370 310 l 370 300 m 370 300 m 270 120 l 270 130 l 280 130 l 280 120 m 280 120 m 140 190 l 140 200 l 150 200 l 150 190 m 150 190 m 120 230 l 120 240 l 130 240 l 130 230 m 130 230 m 130 220 l 130 230 l 140 230 l 140 220 m 140 220 m 180 130 l 180 140 l 190 140 l 190 130 m 190 130 m 160 130 l 160 140 l 170 140 l 170 130 m 170 130 m 50 240 l 50 250 l 60 250 l 60 240 m 60 240 m 290 270 l 290 280 l 300 280 l 300 270 m 300 270 m 170 160 l 170 170 l 180 170 l 180 160 m 180 160 m 60 230 l 60 240 l 70 240 l 70 230 m 70 230 m 300 240 l 300 250 l 310 250 l 310 240 m 310 240 m 50 180 l 50 190 l 60 190 l 60 180 m 60 180 m 80 170 l 80 180 l 90 180 l 90 170 m 90 170 m 320 60 l 320 70 l 330 70 l 330 60 m 330 60 m 90 40 l 90 50 l 100 50 l 100 40 m 100 40 m 330 70 l 330 80 l 340 80 l 340 70 m 340 70 m 50 360 l 50 370 l 60 370 l 60 360 m 60 360 m 340 280 l 340 290 l 350 290 l 350 280 m 350 280 m 110 180 l 110 190 l 120 190 l 120 180 m 120 180 m 350 330 l 350 340 l 360 340 l 360 330 m 360 330 m 240 260 l 240 270 l 250 270 l 250 260 m 250 260 m 120 300 l 120 310 l 130 310 l 130 300 m 130 300 m 150 110 l 150 120 l 160 120 l 160 110 m 160 110 m 280 330 l 280 340 l 290 340 l 290 330 m 290 330 m 160 40 l 160 50 l 170 50 l 170 40 m 170 40 m 140 200 l 140 210 l 150 210 l 150 200 m 150 200 m 290 280 l 290 290 l 300 290 l 300 280 m 300 280 m 40 100 l 40 110 l 50 110 l 50 100 m 50 100 m 280 70 l 280 80 l 290 80 l 290 70 m 290 70 m 160 340 l 160 350 l 170 350 l 170 340 m 170 340 m 310 340 l 310 350 l 320 350 l 320 340 m 320 340 m 170 350 l 170 360 l 180 360 l 180 350 m 180 350 m 320 290 l 320 300 l 330 300 l 330 290 m 330 290 m 60 80 l 60 90 l 70 90 l 70 80 m 70 80 m 90 130 l 90 140 l 100 140 l 100 130 m 100 130 m 100 100 l 100 110 l 110 110 l 110 100 m 110 100 m 340 70 l 340 80 l 350 80 l 350 70 m 350 70 m 230 300 l 230 310 l 240 310 l 240 300 m 240 300 m 90 230 l 90 240 l 100 240 l 100 230 m 100 230 m 270 360 l 270 370 l 280 370 l 280 360 m 280 360 m 100 280 l 100 290 l 110 290 l 110 280 m 110 280 m 210 200 l 210 210 l 220 210 l 220 200 m 220 200 m 270 340 l 270 350 l 280 350 l 280 340 m 280 340 m 120 50 l 120 60 l 130 60 l 130 50 m 130 50 m 130 320 l 130 330 l 140 330 l 140 320 m 140 320 m 140 310 l 140 320 l 150 320 l 150 310 m 150 310 m 190 220 l 190 230 l 200 230 l 200 220 m 200 220 m 40 330 l 40 340 l 50 340 l 50 330 m 50 330 m 50 280 l 50 290 l 60 290 l 60 280 m 60 280 m 320 200 l 320 210 l 330 210 l 330 200 m 330 200 m 300 40 l 300 50 l 310 50 l 310 40 m 310 40 m 330 250 l 330 260 l 340 260 l 340 250 m 340 250 m 70 340 l 70 350 l 80 350 l 80 340 m 80 340 m 310 170 l 310 180 l 320 180 l 320 170 m 320 170 m 340 140 l 340 150 l 350 150 l 350 140 m 350 140 m 320 180 l 320 190 l 330 190 l 330 180 m 330 180 m 330 190 l 330 200 l 340 200 l 340 190 m 340 190 m 250 290 l 250 300 l 260 300 l 260 290 m 260 290 m 230 130 l 230 140 l 240 140 l 240 130 m 240 130 m 210 130 l 210 140 l 220 140 l 220 130 m 220 130 m 240 60 l 240 70 l 250 70 l 250 60 m 250 60 m 270 270 l 270 280 l 280 280 l 280 270 m 280 270 m 120 120 l 120 130 l 130 130 l 130 120 m 130 120 m 360 90 l 360 100 l 370 100 l 370 90 m 370 90 m 130 90 l 130 100 l 140 100 l 140 90 m 140 90 m 150 150 l 150 160 l 160 160 l 160 150 m 160 150 m 40 240 l 40 250 l 50 250 l 50 240 m 50 240 m 160 160 l 160 170 l 170 170 l 170 160 m 170 160 m 50 210 l 50 220 l 60 220 l 60 210 m 60 210 m 170 210 l 170 220 l 180 220 l 180 210 m 180 210 m 50 150 l 50 160 l 60 160 l 60 150 m 60 150 m 340 170 l 340 180 l 350 180 l 350 170 m 350 170 m 80 40 l 80 50 l 90 50 l 90 40 m 90 40 m 40 360 l 40 370 l 50 370 l 50 360 m 50 360 m 350 120 l 350 130 l 360 130 l 360 120 m 360 120 m 200 70 l 200 80 l 210 80 l 210 70 m 210 70 m 100 140 l 100 150 l 110 150 l 110 140 m 110 140 m 230 180 l 230 190 l 240 190 l 240 180 m 240 180 m 350 260 l 350 270 l 360 270 l 360 260 m 360 260 m 240 130 l 240 140 l 250 140 l 250 130 m 250 130 m 220 130 l 220 140 l 230 140 l 230 130 m 230 130 m 260 70 l 260 80 l 270 80 l 270 70 m 270 70 m 270 140 l 270 150 l 280 150 l 280 140 m 280 140 m 120 250 l 120 260 l 130 260 l 130 250 m 130 250 m 130 200 l 130 210 l 140 210 l 140 200 m 140 200 m 280 280 l 280 290 l 290 290 l 290 280 m 290 280 m 160 150 l 160 160 l 170 160 l 170 150 m 170 150 m 140 270 l 140 280 l 150 280 l 150 270 m 150 270 m 190 180 l 190 190 l 200 190 l 200 180 m 200 180 m 170 140 l 170 150 l 180 150 l 180 140 m 180 140 m 40 50 l 40 60 l 50 60 l 50 50 m 50 50 m 70 160 l 70 170 l 80 170 l 80 160 m 80 160 m 80 190 l 80 200 l 90 200 l 90 190 m 90 190 m 320 320 l 320 330 l 330 330 l 330 320 m 330 320 m 90 180 l 90 190 l 100 190 l 100 180 m 100 180 m 70 220 l 70 230 l 80 230 l 80 220 m 80 220 m 340 340 l 340 350 l 350 350 l 350 340 m 350 340 m 230 270 l 230 280 l 240 280 l 240 270 m 240 270 m 110 120 l 110 130 l 120 130 l 120 120 m 120 120 m 350 350 l 350 360 l 360 360 l 360 350 m 360 350 m 240 200 l 240 210 l 250 210 l 250 200 m 250 200 m 360 230 l 360 240 l 370 240 l 370 230 m 370 230 m 270 70 l 270 80 l 280 80 l 280 70 m 280 70 m 120 320 l 120 330 l 130 330 l 130 320 m 130 320 m 360 130 l 360 140 l 370 140 l 370 130 m 370 130 m 130 290 l 130 300 l 140 300 l 140 290 m 140 290 m 140 340 l 140 350 l 150 350 l 150 340 m 150 340 m 290 340 l 290 350 l 300 350 l 300 340 m 300 340 m 190 270 l 190 280 l 200 280 l 200 270 m 200 270 m 150 350 l 150 360 l 160 360 l 160 350 m 160 350 m 40 280 l 40 290 l 50 290 l 50 280 m 50 280 m 160 280 l 160 290 l 170 290 l 170 280 m 170 280 m 310 200 l 310 210 l 320 210 l 320 200 m 320 200 m 320 310 l 320 320 l 330 320 l 330 310 m 330 310 m 60 60 l 60 70 l 70 70 l 70 60 m 70 60 m 100 80 l 100 90 l 110 90 l 110 80 m 110 80 m 80 320 l 80 330 l 90 330 l 90 320 m 90 320 m 90 210 l 90 220 l 100 220 l 100 210 m 100 210 m 240 350 l 240 360 l 250 360 l 250 350 m 250 350 m 100 340 l 100 350 l 110 350 l 110 340 m 110 340 m 260 330 l 260 340 l 270 340 l 270 330 m 270 330 m 360 40 l 360 50 l 370 50 l 370 40 m 370 40 m 140 290 l 140 300 l 150 300 l 150 290 m 150 290 m 190 320 l 190 330 l 200 330 l 200 320 m 200 320 m 40 350 l 40 360 l 50 360 l 50 350 m 50 350 m 280 160 l 280 170 l 290 170 l 290 160 m 290 160 m 180 70 l 180 80 l 190 80 l 190 70 m 190 70 m 290 130 l 290 140 l 300 140 l 300 130 m 300 130 m 170 260 l 170 270 l 180 270 l 180 260 m 180 260 m 60 330 l 60 340 l 70 340 l 70 330 m 70 330 m 330 230 l 330 240 l 340 240 l 340 230 m 340 230 m 70 40 l 70 50 l 80 50 l 80 40 m 80 40 m 310 190 l 310 200 l 320 200 l 320 190 m 320 190 m 190 360 l 190 370 l 200 370 l 200 360 m 200 360 m 340 120 l 340 130 l 350 130 l 350 120 m 350 120 m 320 120 l 320 130 l 330 130 l 330 120 m 330 120 m 90 300 l 90 310 l 100 310 l 100 300 m 100 300 m 340 220 l 340 230 l 350 230 l 350 220 m 350 220 m 110 240 l 110 250 l 120 250 l 120 240 m 120 240 m 260 240 l 260 250 l 270 250 l 270 240 m 270 240 m 120 140 l 120 150 l 130 150 l 130 140 m 130 140 m 260 180 l 260 190 l 270 190 l 270 180 m 270 180 m 150 170 l 150 180 l 160 180 l 160 170 m 160 170 m 40 260 l 40 270 l 50 270 l 50 260 m 50 260 m 280 230 l 280 240 l 290 240 l 290 230 m 290 230 m 290 220 l 290 230 l 300 230 l 300 220 m 300 220 m 170 190 l 170 200 l 180 200 l 180 190 m 180 190 m 70 130 l 70 140 l 80 140 l 80 130 m 80 130 m 80 60 l 80 70 l 90 70 l 90 60 m 90 60 m 350 140 l 350 150 l 360 150 l 360 140 m 360 140 m 330 100 l 330 110 l 340 110 l 340 100 m 340 100 m 200 90 l 200 100 l 210 100 l 210 90 m 210 90 m 100 120 l 100 130 l 110 130 l 110 120 m 110 120 m 340 250 l 340 260 l 350 260 l 350 250 m 350 250 m 210 40 l 210 50 l 220 50 l 220 40 m 220 40 m 110 170 l 110 180 l 120 180 l 120 170 m 120 170 m 240 150 l 240 160 l 250 160 l 250 150 m 250 150 m 220 110 l 220 120 l 230 120 l 230 110 m 230 110 m 200 310 l 200 320 l 210 320 l 210 310 m 210 310 m 250 140 l 250 150 l 260 150 l 260 140 m 260 140 m 210 300 l 210 310 l 220 310 l 220 300 m 220 300 m 360 340 l 360 350 l 370 350 l 370 340 m 370 340 m 260 50 l 260 60 l 270 60 l 270 50 m 270 50 m 130 160 l 130 170 l 140 170 l 140 160 m 140 160 m 140 150 l 140 160 l 150 160 l 150 150 m 150 150 m 120 270 l 120 280 l 130 280 l 130 270 m 130 270 m 150 60 l 150 70 l 160 70 l 160 60 m 160 60 m 280 300 l 280 310 l 290 310 l 290 300 m 290 300 m 180 170 l 180 180 l 190 180 l 190 170 m 190 170 m 140 250 l 140 260 l 150 260 l 150 250 m 150 250 m 170 120 l 170 130 l 180 130 l 180 120 m 180 120 m 300 200 l 300 210 l 310 210 l 310 200 m 310 200 m 40 70 l 40 80 l 50 80 l 50 70 m 50 70 m 280 40 l 280 50 l 290 50 l 290 40 m 290 40 m 80 130 l 80 140 l 90 140 l 90 130 m 90 130 m 320 340 l 320 350 l 330 350 l 330 340 m 330 340 m 60 130 l 60 140 l 70 140 l 70 130 m 70 130 m 330 350 l 330 360 l 340 360 l 340 350 m 340 350 m 100 70 l 100 80 l 110 80 l 110 70 m 110 70 m 110 140 l 110 150 l 120 150 l 120 140 m 120 140 m 350 290 l 350 300 l 360 300 l 360 290 m 360 290 m 90 260 l 90 270 l 100 270 l 100 260 m 100 260 m 260 280 l 260 290 l 270 290 l 270 280 m 270 280 m 360 150 l 360 160 l 370 160 l 370 150 m 370 150 m 140 320 l 140 330 l 150 330 l 150 320 m 150 320 m 290 320 l 290 330 l 300 330 l 300 320 m 300 320 m 170 50 l 170 60 l 180 60 l 180 50 m 180 50 m 150 210 l 150 220 l 160 220 l 160 210 m 160 210 m 40 300 l 40 310 l 50 310 l 50 300 m 50 300 m 60 40 l 60 50 l 70 50 l 70 40 m 70 40 m 300 90 l 300 100 l 310 100 l 310 90 m 310 90 m 330 280 l 330 290 l 340 290 l 340 280 m 340 280 m 70 330 l 70 340 l 80 340 l 80 330 m 80 330 m 80 340 l 80 350 l 90 350 l 90 340 m 90 340 m 230 340 l 230 350 l 240 350 l 240 340 m 240 340

