00:02:37,340 --> 00:02:38,880
I'm so sorry, my queen.

2
00:02:40,170 --> 00:02:41,760
He was a good man.

3
00:02:41,760 --> 00:02:44,100
"Barristan the Bold" They called him.

4
00:02:45,320 --> 00:02:47,660
He crossed a continent to serve me.

5
00:02:48,690 --> 00:02:50,170
He was a loyal friend.

6
00:02:52,350 --> 00:02:54,090
And he died in an alley,

7
00:02:54,740 --> 00:02:57,730
butchered by cowards who hide behind masks.

8
00:03:00,570 --> 00:03:02,750
We could pull back to the pyramid district,

9
00:03:03,290 --> 00:03:06,670
secure it, and use it as a base from which to operate.

10
00:03:06,670 --> 00:03:10,210
Then we clean the city out,

11
00:03:10,220 --> 00:03:13,530
neighborhood by neighborhood, street by street,

12
00:03:13,530 --> 00:03:16,040
until the rats have nowhere left to hide.

13
00:03:19,630 --> 00:03:21,480
I prefer your earlier suggestion.

14
00:03:22,300 --> 00:03:24,660
Round up the leaders of each of Meereen's great families

15
00:03:24,660 --> 00:03:26,060
and bring them to me.

16
00:03:27,760 --> 00:03:31,160
But I'm the leader of my family.

17
00:03:34,190 --> 00:03:35,240
No, Your Grace!

18
00:03:35,810 --> 00:03:37,520
I had nothing to do with this.

19
00:03:38,200 --> 00:03:39,100
Your Grace!

37
00:06:10,980 --> 00:06:12,510
Don't want to overfeed them.

38
00:06:16,680 --> 00:06:18,080
Tomorrow perhaps.

39
00:06:54,540 --> 00:06:57,890
"And though Daenerys maintains her grip on Slaver's Bay,

40
00:06:57,890 --> 00:07:01,340
forces rise against her from within and without.

41
00:07:01,350 --> 00:07:05,420
She refuses to leave until the freedom of the former slaves is secure."

42
00:07:07,590 --> 00:07:09,400
She sounds like quite a woman.

43
00:07:09,400 --> 00:07:10,730
And she's alone,

44
00:07:11,130 --> 00:07:12,400
under siege,

45
00:07:12,820 --> 00:07:16,060
no family to guide her or protect her.

46
00:07:16,570 --> 00:07:20,200
Her last relation thousands of miles away,

47
00:07:20,960 --> 00:07:24,020
useless, dying.

48
00:07:25,760 --> 00:07:28,200
Don't say that, Maester Aemon.

49
00:07:28,200 --> 00:07:32,270
A Targaryen alone in the world

50
00:07:33,830 --> 00:07:35,560
is a terrible thing.

51
00:07:39,130 --> 00:07:40,270
Maester Aemon.

52
00:07:40,960 --> 00:07:42,350
Lord Commander.

53
00:07:43,390 --> 00:07:45,740
Sam, I'd like to speak to the maester alone.

54
00:08:01,490 --> 00:08:02,570
How are you feeling?

55
00:08:03,160 --> 00:08:05,490
Oh, like a hundred-year-old man

56
00:08:05,490 --> 00:08:07,810
slowly freezing to death.

57
00:08:12,450 --> 00:08:13,730
I need your advice.

58
00:08:15,560 --> 00:08:17,420
There's something I want to do, something I...

59
00:08:18,160 --> 00:08:19,560
have to do.

60
00:08:19,560 --> 00:08:21,470
But it'll divide the Night's Watch.

61
00:08:22,390 --> 00:08:23,360
Bitterly.

62
00:08:23,360 --> 00:08:26,190
Half the men will hate me the moment I give the order.

63
00:08:26,960 --> 00:08:30,510
Half the men hate you already, Lord Commander.

64
00:08:30,520 --> 00:08:31,330
Do it.

65
00:08:32,880 --> 00:08:33,870
But you don't know what it is.

66
00:08:33,870 --> 00:08:35,780
That doesn't matter.

67
00:08:36,270 --> 00:08:37,380
You do.

68
00:08:40,570 --> 00:08:44,670
You will find little joy in your command.

69
00:08:44,940 --> 00:08:46,900
But with luck,

70
00:08:46,900 --> 00:08:50,710
you will find the strength to do what needs to be done.

71
00:08:52,600 --> 00:08:55,490
Kill the boy, Jon Snow.

72
00:08:56,640 --> 00:08:59,080
Winter is almost upon us.

73
00:09:00,070 --> 00:09:01,350
Kill the boy

74
00:09:02,640 --> 00:09:05,380
and let the man be born.

75
00:09:14,650 --> 00:09:16,680
Where are the rest of the free folk now?

76
00:09:17,530 --> 00:09:18,700
Where have they gone?

77
00:09:23,400 --> 00:09:24,820
Who leads them?

78
00:09:25,570 --> 00:09:27,100
They followed Mance.

79
00:09:27,880 --> 00:09:29,950
They won't follow anyone else.

80
00:09:33,240 --> 00:09:34,330
What about you?

81
00:09:36,690 --> 00:09:38,760
Hard to lead when you're in chains.

82
00:09:42,880 --> 00:09:44,450
What if I unchained you?

83
00:09:44,450 --> 00:09:45,700
Why would you do that?

84
00:09:47,800 --> 00:09:49,600
Because you are not my enemy.

85
00:09:50,770 --> 00:09:52,000
And I'm not yours.

86
00:09:52,000 --> 00:09:54,930
You sure seemed like my enemy when you were killing my friends.

87
00:09:54,930 --> 00:09:57,610
For 8,000 years the Night's Watch have sworn an oath

88
00:09:57,610 --> 00:10:00,140
to be the shield that guards the realms of men.

89
00:10:02,150 --> 00:10:05,660
And for 8,000 years we've fallen short of that oath.

90
00:10:05,660 --> 00:10:07,510
You belong to the realms of men.

91
00:10:08,440 --> 00:10:09,470
All of you.

92
00:10:10,260 --> 00:10:12,850
And now everything is going to change?

93
00:10:13,410 --> 00:10:15,310
- It is. - Why now?

94
00:10:15,320 --> 00:10:19,150
Because now I am Lord Commander of the Night's Watch.

95
00:10:19,850 --> 00:10:21,520
What would you have me do,

96
00:10:22,540 --> 00:10:24,500
Lord Commander?

97
00:10:26,430 --> 00:10:28,030
I'd have you go north of the Wall.

98
00:10:28,660 --> 00:10:31,160
Gather the remaining free folk wherever they are

99
00:10:31,160 --> 00:10:32,510
and bring them back here.

100
00:10:32,910 --> 00:10:35,130
I'll open the gates for them and let them through.

101
00:10:36,240 --> 00:10:38,890
I'll find them lands to settle south of the Wall.

102
00:10:38,890 --> 00:10:42,700
They won't kneel for you and neither will I.

103
00:10:42,700 --> 00:10:44,860
I don't want them to kneel for me.

104
00:10:45,470 --> 00:10:48,140
I want them to fight with me when the time comes.

105
00:10:48,140 --> 00:10:50,850
The day I ask my people to fight with the crows

106
00:10:50,900 --> 00:10:53,630
is the day my people cut my guts from my belly

107
00:10:53,630 --> 00:10:55,120
and make me eat them.

108
00:10:55,120 --> 00:10:57,470
And how many of your people can't fight?

109
00:10:58,160 --> 00:11:00,780
The women, the children, the old, the sick--

110
00:11:00,780 --> 00:11:02,130
what happens to them?

111
00:11:02,730 --> 00:11:04,530
You're condemning them to death.

112
00:11:05,030 --> 00:11:06,350
Worse than death

113
00:11:06,350 --> 00:11:08,970
because you're too proud to make peace.

114
00:11:12,330 --> 00:11:13,960
Or maybe you're not proud.

115
00:11:16,230 --> 00:11:17,840
Maybe you're just a coward.

116
00:11:24,860 --> 00:11:27,730
Easy thing to say to a man in chains.

117
00:11:52,360 --> 00:11:54,010
Your people need a leader.

118
00:11:54,300 --> 00:11:57,500
And they need to get south of the Wall before it's too late.

119
00:11:57,500 --> 00:11:59,350
We don't have much time and they have less.

120
00:11:59,350 --> 00:12:02,270
The walkers are coming and they'll hit your people first.

121
00:12:04,180 --> 00:12:06,880
I'm not asking you to make peace to save your skin.

122
00:12:07,180 --> 00:12:10,710
Make peace to save your people.

123
00:12:19,260 --> 00:12:21,060
Most of them are at Hardhome.

124
00:12:21,780 --> 00:12:22,980
You know where that is?

125
00:12:22,980 --> 00:12:24,680
Up on Storrold's Point.

126
00:12:24,680 --> 00:12:26,930
I can give you 10 horses and nine other men.

127
00:12:26,930 --> 00:12:28,790
You can get there in a week.

128
00:12:28,790 --> 00:12:30,390
We'll need ships.

129
00:12:31,860 --> 00:12:34,660
I'll talk to King Stannis about lending you his fleet.

130
00:12:38,100 --> 00:12:39,440
All right, then.

131
00:12:41,890 --> 00:12:43,310
You're coming with me.

132
00:12:44,630 --> 00:12:47,340
You're the Lord Commander of the Night's Watch.

133
00:12:47,600 --> 00:12:49,340
They need to hear it from you.

134
00:12:49,630 --> 00:12:51,990
They need to know the ships they are boarding

135
00:12:51,990 --> 00:12:54,350
wot be torched in the middle of the sea.

136
00:12:54,710 --> 00:12:59,110
You come with me or I don't go.

137
00:13:07,160 --> 00:13:09,970
You'd bring wildlings here through our gates?

138
00:13:09,970 --> 00:13:11,720
Men, women, and children

139
00:13:11,720 --> 00:13:13,860
will die by the thousands if we do nothing.

140
00:13:13,860 --> 00:13:16,820
Let them die. We got our own to worry about.

141
00:13:17,050 --> 00:13:18,590
Less enemies for us.

142
00:13:20,240 --> 00:13:21,220
Fewer.

143
00:13:21,900 --> 00:13:24,120
- What? - Nothing.

144
00:13:24,700 --> 00:13:28,600
Look, well, there is good farmland in the Gift.

145
00:13:28,960 --> 00:13:30,760
Land that no one uses now.

146
00:13:31,040 --> 00:13:32,270
A dozen abandoned villages.

147
00:13:32,270 --> 00:13:35,320
And why do you think the farmers abandoned those villages?

148
00:13:35,580 --> 00:13:37,960
Because the wildlings raided them for years.

149
00:13:38,530 --> 00:13:39,730
Cut them down.

150
00:13:40,160 --> 00:13:43,580
- Just like they did this boy's people. - Aye!

151
00:13:44,970 --> 00:13:48,070
We've been fighting them for thousands of years.

152
00:13:48,280 --> 00:13:50,230
They've slaughtered villages.

153
00:13:50,640 --> 00:13:52,630
They've slaughtered our brothers.

154
00:13:52,630 --> 00:13:54,220
And we've slaughtered theirs.

155
00:13:56,340 --> 00:14:00,280
I will follow you anywhere, you know that.

156
00:14:01,540 --> 00:14:04,210
- But they killed Grenn. - Yes.

157
00:14:04,210 --> 00:14:06,510
- And they killed Pyp. - Aye.

158
00:14:06,510 --> 00:14:09,170
They killed 50 of our brothers.

159
00:14:09,300 --> 00:14:10,950
I can't forget that.

160
00:14:11,410 --> 00:14:12,860
I can't forgive it.

161
00:14:12,860 --> 00:14:15,000
You were at the Fist of the First Men.

162
00:14:15,630 --> 00:14:18,320
If we abandon them, you know what they become.

163
00:14:18,510 --> 00:14:20,590
We can learn to live with the wildlings

164
00:14:20,590 --> 00:14:22,890
or we can add them to the army of the dead.

165
00:14:23,370 --> 00:14:27,460
Whatever they are now, they're better than that.

166
00:14:55,930 --> 00:14:57,040
Thank you.

167
00:14:57,710 --> 00:14:58,670
Olly.

168
00:15:00,940 --> 00:15:03,170
If you have something you want to say to me,

169
00:15:04,310 --> 00:15:05,380
say it.

170
00:15:12,460 --> 00:15:13,530
It's all right.

171
00:15:15,840 --> 00:15:17,840
You don't mean it, do you?

172
00:15:19,460 --> 00:15:21,830
Telling the wildlings you want to make peace.

173
00:15:22,330 --> 00:15:24,030
You're just doing it to trick them.

174
00:15:24,690 --> 00:15:25,980
It's not a trick.

175
00:15:25,980 --> 00:15:27,530
They burned my village.

176
00:15:27,530 --> 00:15:30,960
They put an arrow through my father's head right in front of me.

177
00:15:30,960 --> 00:15:34,400
They butchered my mother, everyone I ever knew.

178
00:15:42,170 --> 00:15:44,700
I know what it's like to lose the people you love.

179
00:15:47,180 --> 00:15:48,910
I know this is hard for you.

180
00:15:50,820 --> 00:15:52,360
But winter is coming.

181
00:15:54,050 --> 00:15:55,720
We know what's coming with it.

182
00:15:57,410 --> 00:15:59,160
We can't face it alone.

183
00:16:04,870 --> 00:16:07,610
Will there be anything else you need, Lord Commander?

184
00:16:11,040 --> 00:16:11,990
No.

185
00:16:46,130 --> 00:16:48,290
She's far away from the Lannisters.

186
00:16:49,430 --> 00:16:50,710
This is her home.

187
00:16:53,840 --> 00:16:56,430
Maybe Lday Sansa's better off here.

188
00:16:57,520 --> 00:16:59,490
Better off with the Boltons

189
00:16:59,650 --> 00:17:01,910
who murdered her mother and brother?

190
00:17:10,790 --> 00:17:13,850
Sansa's in danger even if she doesn't realize it.

191
00:17:27,860 --> 00:17:28,980
Thank you.

192
00:17:31,450 --> 00:17:33,120
You've lived here a long time?

193
00:17:35,160 --> 00:17:36,340
Aye.

194
00:17:37,500 --> 00:17:39,460
Did you know Lord Eddard?

195
00:17:41,240 --> 00:17:42,650
I knew him

196
00:17:43,730 --> 00:17:45,720
and his father before him.

197
00:17:47,920 --> 00:17:50,280
The Starks are gone now.

198
00:17:50,310 --> 00:17:51,950
Not all of them.

199
00:17:52,380 --> 00:17:54,890
I know who's inside that castle.

200
00:17:55,000 --> 00:17:56,770
Everyone knows.

201
00:17:56,990 --> 00:17:58,530
The Boltons.

202
00:17:58,530 --> 00:18:00,830
I'm not talking about the Boltons.

203
00:18:01,980 --> 00:18:03,840
I need to get a message to her.

204
00:18:04,580 --> 00:18:06,410
To Sansa Stark.

205
00:18:08,390 --> 00:18:09,830
Who are you?

206
00:18:09,830 --> 00:18:12,630
Someone who swore to keep her safe.

207
00:18:12,870 --> 00:18:14,720
Swore to who?

208
00:18:14,730 --> 00:18:16,060
Her mother.

209
00:18:17,180 --> 00:18:19,060
Her mother's dead.

210
00:18:19,060 --> 00:18:21,250
That doesn't release me from an oath.

211
00:18:24,510 --> 00:18:26,800
I served Lady Catelyn.

212
00:18:27,420 --> 00:18:29,130
I serve her still.

213
00:18:31,460 --> 00:18:33,110
Who do you serve?

214
00:18:40,170 --> 00:18:41,210
Come back here.

215
00:18:45,680 --> 00:18:46,780
Myranda.

216
00:18:47,080 --> 00:18:48,620
I saw you staring at her.

217
00:18:48,790 --> 00:18:50,390
I'm going to marry her.

218
00:18:50,650 --> 00:18:53,480
That will involve looking at her from time to time.

219
00:18:57,280 --> 00:18:58,910
You said you'd marry me.

220
00:19:00,160 --> 00:19:01,620
And I meant it.

221
00:19:01,920 --> 00:19:04,120
When I was a bastard named Snow.

222
00:19:04,560 --> 00:19:05,890
But I'm a Bolton now.

223
00:19:06,510 --> 00:19:09,720
What I want is no longer the primary consideration.

224
00:19:10,660 --> 00:19:12,550
I'm furthering a dynasty.

225
00:19:16,030 --> 00:19:17,530
Do you think she's pretty?

226
00:19:18,660 --> 00:19:19,950
Of course I do.

227
00:19:19,960 --> 00:19:21,210
I'm not blind.

228
00:19:35,060 --> 00:19:36,750
You think she's pretty, too.

229
00:19:40,130 --> 00:19:42,350
I'm looking forward to our wedding night.

230
00:19:42,350 --> 00:19:45,770
But don't worry, I'll have plenty of time for you.

231
00:19:46,140 --> 00:19:48,090
Perhaps I'll marry, too.

232
00:19:53,650 --> 00:19:55,890
You're the kennel master's daughter.

233
00:19:56,470 --> 00:19:59,860
Who are you going to marry, the stable keeper's son?

234
00:20:06,180 --> 00:20:07,450
You're mine.

235
00:20:08,820 --> 00:20:10,510
You're not going anywhere.

236
00:20:11,180 --> 00:20:13,440
Unless I have to listen to more of your jealousy,

237
00:20:13,440 --> 00:20:16,490
Jealousy bores me. You remember what happens to people who bore me.

238
00:20:19,550 --> 00:20:23,160
You're not going to bore me, are you, Myranda?

239
00:20:41,650 --> 00:20:42,710
Never.

240
00:21:10,360 --> 00:21:11,780
Beg pardon, my lady.

241
00:21:11,780 --> 00:21:13,940
I've come to refill the wash basin.

242
00:21:13,940 --> 00:21:15,450
Oh, I don't need--

243
00:21:17,120 --> 00:21:19,700
You still have friends in the North.

244
00:21:19,700 --> 00:21:21,360
If you're ever in trouble,

245
00:21:21,450 --> 00:21:25,020
light a candle in the highest window of the broken tower.

246
00:21:26,340 --> 00:21:28,530
- But who-- - You're not alone.

247
00:22:06,630 --> 00:22:08,150
I like your dress.

248
00:22:10,340 --> 00:22:11,720
Who made it for you?

249
00:22:12,560 --> 00:22:14,540
I made it myself.

250
00:22:14,700 --> 00:22:15,810
Really?

251
00:22:18,610 --> 00:22:20,100
Who-- who are you?

252
00:22:20,560 --> 00:22:23,880
I'm Myranda, the kennel master's daughter.

253
00:22:27,110 --> 00:22:28,090
May I?

254
00:22:34,530 --> 00:22:36,040
Oh, wonderful.

255
00:22:36,710 --> 00:22:38,280
The stitching.

256
00:22:39,790 --> 00:22:41,940
- Who taught you? - My mother.

257
00:22:43,320 --> 00:22:47,080
I'm sorry for what happened to her.

258
00:22:47,080 --> 00:22:48,220
Thank you.

259
00:22:50,160 --> 00:22:51,720
It's good that she taught you.

260
00:22:52,500 --> 00:22:53,900
It was a gift.

261
00:22:53,910 --> 00:22:58,160
Now every time you wear something you made,

262
00:22:58,660 --> 00:23:00,220
you can remember her.

263
00:23:01,050 --> 00:23:02,740
I'd rather have a mother.

264
00:23:02,740 --> 00:23:04,790
I know. It's not the same.

265
00:23:06,390 --> 00:23:08,890
Still, it's good to remember.

266
00:23:09,500 --> 00:23:11,190
Remember the way things were.

267
00:23:13,380 --> 00:23:15,440
I almost forgot.

268
00:23:16,120 --> 00:23:18,850
There's something else

269
00:23:19,440 --> 00:23:21,190
to help you remember.

270
00:23:30,910 --> 00:23:32,870
Down there at the end.

271
00:23:34,740 --> 00:23:35,970
What is it?

272
00:23:36,120 --> 00:23:38,210
That would spoil the surprise.

273
00:23:39,290 --> 00:23:41,600
Go ahead, it's perfectly safe.

274
00:23:42,570 --> 00:23:44,860
You won't believe it when you see it.

275
00:24:47,370 --> 00:24:48,580
Theon?

276
00:24:58,510 --> 00:25:00,400
You shouldn't be here.

277
00:25:21,170 --> 00:25:24,670
You smell particularly ripe this evening.

278
00:25:27,580 --> 00:25:28,910
Pour me some wine.

279
00:25:53,740 --> 00:25:55,500
Do you have something to tell me?

280
00:25:57,430 --> 00:25:58,690
No, my lord.

281
00:25:58,780 --> 00:25:59,930
Reek.

282
00:26:04,720 --> 00:26:05,930
She saw me.

283
00:26:06,740 --> 00:26:07,760
Who?

284
00:26:07,850 --> 00:26:09,930
Sansa. Lady Sansa.

285
00:26:10,690 --> 00:26:12,220
She came to the kennels.

286
00:26:13,730 --> 00:26:15,040
She saw you?

287
00:26:15,040 --> 00:26:17,290
Yes. I'm sorry, master.

288
00:26:17,490 --> 00:26:19,260
Forgive me. I didn't think...

289
00:26:19,260 --> 00:26:20,370
Come here.

290
00:26:29,650 --> 00:26:32,340
You mustn't keep secrets from me, Reek.

291
00:26:32,830 --> 00:26:34,190
Get on your knees.

292
00:26:46,870 --> 00:26:48,370
Give me your hand.

293
00:27:11,090 --> 00:27:12,470
I forgive you.

294
00:27:24,120 --> 00:27:26,820
I trust you find your chamber suitable, my lady.

295
00:27:27,130 --> 00:27:28,880
Yes, thank you, my lord.

296
00:27:29,060 --> 00:27:30,220
Allow me.

297
00:27:34,790 --> 00:27:35,820
Mother.

298
00:27:36,420 --> 00:27:37,920
Thank you, Ramsay.

299
00:27:48,360 --> 00:27:52,850
My lady, we are all a family, we northerners.

300
00:27:53,310 --> 00:27:56,420
Our blood ties go back thousands of years.

301
00:27:56,780 --> 00:27:59,880
So I'd like to drink to our wedding.

302
00:28:00,000 --> 00:28:02,770
May our happiness spread from Moat Cailin

303
00:28:02,770 --> 00:28:04,180
to the Last Hearth.

304
00:28:05,080 --> 00:28:06,070
To your wedding.

305
00:28:06,130 --> 00:28:07,510
To your wedding.

306
00:28:14,650 --> 00:28:17,760
It must be difficult for you being in a strange place.

307
00:28:17,850 --> 00:28:20,130
This isn't a strange place. This is my home.

308
00:28:20,910 --> 00:28:22,500
It's the people who are strange.

309
00:28:27,730 --> 00:28:28,540
You're right.

310
00:28:29,320 --> 00:28:30,730
Very strange.

311
00:28:33,790 --> 00:28:35,290
More wine, please.

312
00:28:42,340 --> 00:28:44,910
I heard you two had been reunited.

313
00:28:45,760 --> 00:28:47,500
A fitting place for it.

314
00:28:49,870 --> 00:28:52,150
I like to imagine that the last time you spoke

315
00:28:52,870 --> 00:28:54,490
was in this very room.

316
00:28:58,180 --> 00:28:59,980
Are you still angry with him

317
00:29:00,350 --> 00:29:01,660
after he...

318
00:29:07,060 --> 00:29:08,080
what he did?

319
00:29:08,890 --> 00:29:10,000
Don't worry.

320
00:29:10,510 --> 00:29:12,190
The North remembers.

321
00:29:13,930 --> 00:29:15,610
I punished him for it.

322
00:29:16,180 --> 00:29:18,050
He's not ironborn anymore.

323
00:29:18,790 --> 00:29:21,660
Not Theon Greyjoy anymore.

324
00:29:21,750 --> 00:29:23,010
He's a new man.

325
00:29:25,490 --> 00:29:27,690
A new person, anyway.

326
00:29:28,500 --> 00:29:29,730
Aren't you, Reek?

327
00:29:30,210 --> 00:29:31,350
Yes, master.

328
00:29:31,770 --> 00:29:34,220
That's his new name-- Reek.

329
00:29:34,220 --> 00:29:35,640
Why are you doing this?

330
00:29:38,270 --> 00:29:40,020
Because Reek has something to say to you.

331
00:29:41,460 --> 00:29:42,750
Don't you, Reek?

332
00:29:53,150 --> 00:29:54,180
An apology.

333
00:30:00,620 --> 00:30:03,290
Apologize to Lady Sansa for what you did.

334
00:30:04,830 --> 00:30:07,850
Apologize for murding her two brothers.

335
00:30:14,210 --> 00:30:15,030
I'm sorry.

336
00:30:17,090 --> 00:30:18,300
Look at her, Reek.

337
00:30:19,890 --> 00:30:21,510
An apology doesn't mean anything

338
00:30:21,510 --> 00:30:23,880
if you're not looking the person in the eye.

339
00:30:30,860 --> 00:30:33,150
- I'm sorry. - Sorry about what?

340
00:30:35,200 --> 00:30:36,240
For killing your brothers.

341
00:30:47,100 --> 00:30:50,070
There, over and done with.

342
00:30:50,490 --> 00:30:52,500
Doesn't everyone feel better? I do.

343
00:30:53,310 --> 00:30:55,960
That was getting very tense.

344
00:31:02,160 --> 00:31:03,210
You know what, my lady?

345
00:31:04,950 --> 00:31:07,830
What with him having murdered your brothers

346
00:31:07,830 --> 00:31:10,510
and the rest of your family gone...

347
00:31:12,600 --> 00:31:16,530
Reek here is the nearest thing to a living kin

348
00:31:16,740 --> 00:31:18,120
that you have left.

349
00:31:19,770 --> 00:31:20,730
Reek.

350
00:31:22,140 --> 00:31:23,910
You will give away the bride.

351
00:31:26,820 --> 00:31:29,670
Someone has to. What better person?

352
00:31:30,210 --> 00:31:31,890
Good? Good?

353
00:31:32,640 --> 00:31:34,440
Yes, yes, very good.

354
00:31:35,260 --> 00:31:36,360
Wonderful.

355
00:31:38,850 --> 00:31:40,680
Walda and I have some good news as well,

356
00:31:41,670 --> 00:31:43,080
since we're all together.

357
00:31:48,950 --> 00:31:50,480
We're going to have a baby.

358
00:31:56,860 --> 00:31:58,100
I'm very happy for you.

359
00:31:58,430 --> 00:31:59,960
From the way she's carrying,

360
00:32:00,260 --> 00:32:02,480
Maester Wolkan says it looks like a boy.

361
00:32:18,610 --> 00:32:19,840
How can you be sure?

362
00:32:21,130 --> 00:32:22,420
Sure of what?

363
00:32:22,480 --> 00:32:23,830
That she's pregnant.

364
00:32:24,460 --> 00:32:25,510
I mean...

365
00:32:26,530 --> 00:32:27,790
how can you tell?

366
00:32:28,510 --> 00:32:31,160
Maester Wolkan has assured us beyond all doubt.

367
00:32:39,910 --> 00:32:43,090
So how did you manage it?

368
00:32:43,300 --> 00:32:44,560
Manage what?

369
00:32:45,010 --> 00:32:46,540
Getting her pregnant.

370
00:32:47,500 --> 00:32:49,480
I imagine you're familiar with the procedure.

371
00:32:49,480 --> 00:32:52,630
Of course, but how did you...

372
00:32:52,810 --> 00:32:53,980
find it?

373
00:32:53,980 --> 00:32:55,450
You disgraced yourself at dinner

374
00:32:56,740 --> 00:32:58,960
parading that creature before the Stark girl.

375
00:32:58,960 --> 00:33:00,250
And if it's a boy?

376
00:33:03,880 --> 00:33:05,380
You're worried about your position.

377
00:33:05,380 --> 00:33:07,360
My position is quite clear.

378
00:33:07,900 --> 00:33:09,010
I'm your son

379
00:33:10,510 --> 00:33:12,700
until a better alternative comes along.

380
00:33:22,390 --> 00:33:23,950
You've never asked me about your mother.

381
00:33:29,380 --> 00:33:30,310
Why would I?

382
00:33:31,630 --> 00:33:33,850
She had me, she died.

383
00:33:35,350 --> 00:33:36,700
And here we are.

384
00:33:38,230 --> 00:33:39,730
She was peasant girl.

385
00:33:40,870 --> 00:33:42,640
Pretty in a common sort of way.

386
00:33:43,060 --> 00:33:44,380
She was the miller's wife.

387
00:33:45,580 --> 00:33:48,640
Apparently they had married without my knowledge or consent.

388
00:33:49,210 --> 00:33:50,590
So I had him hanged

389
00:33:51,010 --> 00:33:53,660
and I took her beneath the tree where he was swaying.

390
00:33:54,280 --> 00:33:55,930
She fought me the whole time.

391
00:33:56,110 --> 00:33:58,330
She was lucky I didn't hang her, too.

392
00:33:59,080 --> 00:34:00,730
A year later she came to my gates

393
00:34:00,730 --> 00:34:03,040
with a squalling baby in her arms.

394
00:34:03,070 --> 00:34:05,320
A baby she claimed was mine.

395
00:34:05,530 --> 00:34:06,910
I nearly had her whipped

396
00:34:07,300 --> 00:34:09,250
and the child thrown in the river.

397
00:34:15,010 --> 00:34:16,090
But then I looked at you

398
00:34:16,870 --> 00:34:19,090
and I saw then what I see now.

399
00:34:19,870 --> 00:34:21,400
You are my son.

400
00:34:33,580 --> 00:34:36,610
Stannis Baratheon has an army at Castle Black.

401
00:34:37,250 --> 00:34:38,720
But he won't stay for long.

402
00:34:40,130 --> 00:34:41,840
He wants the Iron Throne,

403
00:34:42,980 --> 00:34:45,910
and the road to King's Landing comes right through Winterfell.

404
00:34:47,270 --> 00:34:49,430
He means to take the North.

405
00:34:51,940 --> 00:34:53,450
But the North is ours.

406
00:34:54,140 --> 00:34:55,790
It's yours and mine.

407
00:34:57,530 --> 00:34:59,090
Will you help me defeat him?

408
00:35:01,660 --> 00:35:02,480
Yes.

409
00:35:11,080 --> 00:35:12,830
Is this every book there is?

410
00:35:14,480 --> 00:35:15,800
Every book there is?

411
00:35:17,300 --> 00:35:20,570
- In the world. - Well, no.

412
00:35:20,570 --> 00:35:23,650
There are thousands and thousands of books out there.

413
00:35:24,620 --> 00:35:26,330
This library is rather small, actually.

414
00:35:26,330 --> 00:35:28,430
Where you grew up, were there more books?

415
00:35:28,430 --> 00:35:30,620
My father's not the most literate man.

416
00:35:33,570 --> 00:35:37,400
They say the Citadel has the largest library in the world.

417
00:35:37,400 --> 00:35:38,510
Where's that?

418
00:35:40,280 --> 00:35:41,390
The Citadel?

419
00:35:42,560 --> 00:35:44,060
In Oldtown.

420
00:35:50,930 --> 00:35:52,690
I'm sorry I don't know things.

421
00:35:52,690 --> 00:35:55,060
Gilly, look at me.

422
00:35:55,990 --> 00:35:59,290
You know how to do a hundred things I can never do.

423
00:35:59,290 --> 00:36:01,540
You can build a fire with wet wood.

424
00:36:01,570 --> 00:36:04,350
You can cook. You can stitch a wound.

425
00:36:04,350 --> 00:36:07,110
I can wash the linens. I can sweep the floor.

426
00:36:07,110 --> 00:36:10,570
- Well... - Why does the Citadel have the biggest library?

427
00:36:10,820 --> 00:36:13,460
It's where they train the maesters.

428
00:36:13,730 --> 00:36:15,020
Like Maester Aemon?

429
00:36:15,230 --> 00:36:17,270
I wanted to be one when I was young.

430
00:36:20,620 --> 00:36:24,520
Instead, I became a man of the Night's Watch.

431
00:36:27,670 --> 00:36:29,600
Far more adventure up here anyway.

432
00:36:31,960 --> 00:36:33,110
I wouldn't have met you.

433
00:36:40,510 --> 00:36:41,890
Your Grace.

434
00:36:49,330 --> 00:36:50,660
You're Samwell Tarly?

435
00:36:52,370 --> 00:36:53,900
I am, Your Grace.

436
00:36:54,530 --> 00:36:56,330
Your father is Randyll Tarly.

437
00:36:59,650 --> 00:37:01,760
He defeated my brother at the Battle of Ashford.

438
00:37:03,800 --> 00:37:05,510
Only battle Robert ever lost.

439
00:37:06,710 --> 00:37:08,570
I told him he shouldn't go so far west so soon,

440
00:37:08,570 --> 00:37:09,940
but he never listened.

441
00:37:12,760 --> 00:37:14,200
Fine soldier, your father.

442
00:37:15,700 --> 00:37:17,080
You don't look like a soldier.

443
00:37:18,730 --> 00:37:20,530
But I'm told you killed a white walker.

444
00:37:21,790 --> 00:37:23,110
I did, Your Grace.

445
00:37:23,630 --> 00:37:24,520
How?

446
00:37:24,580 --> 00:37:26,680
With a dagger made of dragonglass.

447
00:37:26,860 --> 00:37:28,090
Dragonglass?

448
00:37:28,100 --> 00:37:29,500
What the maesters call obsidian.

449
00:37:29,500 --> 00:37:32,180
I know what it is. We have it in Dragonstone.

450
00:37:32,270 --> 00:37:33,880
Why would obsidian kill a walker?

451
00:37:33,880 --> 00:37:35,090
I don't know.

452
00:37:35,890 --> 00:37:37,450
I've been going through all the old manuscripts

453
00:37:37,450 --> 00:37:39,730
hoping to find something, and all I've learned

454
00:37:39,740 --> 00:37:43,300
is that the children of the forest used to hunt with dragonglass.

455
00:37:43,300 --> 00:37:46,960
The Lady Melisandre told me that death marches on the Wall.

456
00:37:50,410 --> 00:37:51,890
I've seen it, Your Grace.

457
00:37:52,070 --> 00:37:53,230
Seen what?

458
00:37:53,680 --> 00:37:55,430
The army of the dead.

459
00:37:56,800 --> 00:37:59,680
- And when they come-- - We have to know how to fight them.

460
00:38:04,210 --> 00:38:06,100
Keep reading, Samwell Tarly.

461
00:38:24,350 --> 00:38:25,260
It's time.

462
00:38:26,450 --> 00:38:27,570
Uh, Your Grace.

463
00:38:28,570 --> 00:38:30,020
Wouldn't it be better to wait?

464
00:38:30,560 --> 00:38:32,150
When Jon Snow returns with the wildlings,

465
00:38:32,150 --> 00:38:33,710
we could have thousands more men.

466
00:38:33,710 --> 00:38:35,230
If Jon Snow returns with the wildlings.

467
00:38:35,240 --> 00:38:36,590
We can't wait that long.

468
00:38:36,950 --> 00:38:38,290
We have the advantage-- more men,

469
00:38:38,300 --> 00:38:40,430
more horses, all fed and rested.

470
00:38:40,820 --> 00:38:43,690
But every day we wait, the odds shift in Bolton's favor.

471
00:38:43,690 --> 00:38:45,410
This could turn to winter at any moment.

472
00:38:45,680 --> 00:38:47,570
We have to act now. Give the order.

473
00:38:47,570 --> 00:38:48,920
We march at sunrise.

474
00:38:49,010 --> 00:38:50,690
I'll choose a dozen men to stay

475
00:38:50,810 --> 00:38:52,970
and guard the queen and the princess.

476
00:38:53,090 --> 00:38:54,680
No need. They're coming with us.

477
00:38:57,140 --> 00:38:59,000
It's a tough road ahead, Your Grace.

478
00:38:59,210 --> 00:39:01,100
- Won't they be safer-- - Here?

479
00:39:02,090 --> 00:39:05,530
Half these watchmen are killers and rapists.

480
00:39:06,500 --> 00:39:08,600
No, they march with us.

481
00:39:12,010 --> 00:39:13,220
As you wish, Your Grace.

482
00:39:39,630 --> 00:39:41,790
Do you think Father will let me go down into the crypt?

483
00:39:41,790 --> 00:39:42,810
Beg your pardon?

484
00:39:43,680 --> 00:39:45,000
At Winterfell.

485
00:39:45,240 --> 00:39:47,160
All the Kings in the North are buried there.

486
00:39:47,430 --> 00:39:49,160
Bran the Builder and King Torrhen and--

487
00:39:49,170 --> 00:39:51,570
First things first. It's a long march ahead.

488
00:39:51,900 --> 00:39:53,610
And then we have to take the castle.

489
00:39:53,700 --> 00:39:54,990
Is there going to be a battle?

490
00:39:55,010 --> 00:39:57,680
Aye, Princess, but you won't be anywhere near--

491
00:39:57,680 --> 00:39:59,870
That's enough talk of battle, Ser Davos.

492
00:40:00,860 --> 00:40:02,420
You'll scare the child.

493
00:40:03,020 --> 00:40:04,220
Yes, my queen.

494
00:40:07,290 --> 00:40:10,080
- I'm not scared. - Well, I am.

495
00:40:10,770 --> 00:40:13,230
When the battle comes, promise you'll protect me.

496
00:40:13,230 --> 00:40:14,520
I promise.

497
00:40:35,300 --> 00:40:38,530
I hope you know what you're doing with these wildlings.

498
00:40:39,080 --> 00:40:40,480
I need those ships.

499
00:40:41,800 --> 00:40:44,980
You'll get them back, I swear it.

500
00:40:46,940 --> 00:40:48,320
Have a safe journey, Your Grace.

501
00:40:50,080 --> 00:40:51,320
And thank you.

502
00:41:20,690 --> 00:41:21,960
Mount up!

503
00:41:22,650 --> 00:41:23,840
Colors!

504
00:42:13,870 --> 00:42:14,770
No.

505
00:42:16,350 --> 00:42:17,690
You're still too weak.

508
00:42:29,140 --> 00:42:30,480
Ser Barristan?

515
00:42:56,500 --> 00:42:57,890
Are you ashamed?

516
00:43:00,120 --> 00:43:02,250
You were ambushed, outnumbered.

517
00:43:02,770 --> 00:43:04,270
There was no way you could have known.

518
00:43:04,270 --> 00:43:05,870
This is not why.

519
00:43:09,190 --> 00:43:11,450
Wounded in war,

520
00:43:12,300 --> 00:43:14,180
there is no shame for this.

521
00:43:14,900 --> 00:43:16,440
I am ashamed

522
00:43:17,020 --> 00:43:19,510
because when the knife go in

523
00:43:19,710 --> 00:43:21,560
and I fall to the ground,

524
00:43:23,150 --> 00:43:24,680
I am afraid.

525
00:43:26,490 --> 00:43:28,280
All men fear death.

526
00:43:28,280 --> 00:43:30,830
No, not death.

527
00:43:34,180 --> 00:43:35,390
I fear

528
00:43:36,430 --> 00:43:41,430
I never again see Missandei from the Island of Naath.

529
00:44:17,870 --> 00:44:20,630
Now you have given the Masters what they deserve.

530
00:44:20,630 --> 00:44:21,920
If I give everyone what they deserve,

531
00:44:21,920 --> 00:44:23,540
I'll have no one left to rule.

532
00:44:24,700 --> 00:44:26,780
Ser Barristan counseled mercy

533
00:44:26,790 --> 00:44:29,650
when I took this city right up to the morning he died.

534
00:44:30,110 --> 00:44:32,650
Daario Naharis thinks I should kill the former Masters

535
00:44:32,650 --> 00:44:34,980
and let the rest of the city fend for itself.

536
00:44:36,440 --> 00:44:37,590
What do you think?

537
00:44:39,490 --> 00:44:41,430
Your Grace, I think that I am not fit

538
00:44:41,430 --> 00:44:43,410
to have an opinion on these matters.

539
00:44:43,890 --> 00:44:46,270
You are as fit as anyone I know.

540
00:44:47,910 --> 00:44:49,630
You know why I'm here.

541
00:44:50,290 --> 00:44:53,290
And you know who will suffer the most if this all falls apart.

542
00:44:53,840 --> 00:44:55,750
So what do you think?

543
00:44:58,920 --> 00:45:01,880
I can only tell you what I have seen, Your Grace.

544
00:45:02,450 --> 00:45:05,400
I have seen you listen to your counselors.

545
00:45:07,160 --> 00:45:09,490
I have seen you lean on their experience

546
00:45:09,490 --> 00:45:11,090
when your own was lacking

547
00:45:11,130 --> 00:45:13,690
and weigh the choices they put before you.

548
00:45:15,920 --> 00:45:18,510
And I have seen you ignore your counselors...

549
00:45:21,350 --> 00:45:23,490
because there was a better choice.

550
00:45:24,190 --> 00:45:26,180
One that only you could see.

551
00:45:43,380 --> 00:45:45,850
My-- my queen, please do not do this.

552
00:45:46,430 --> 00:45:48,040
What about "Valar morghulis"?

553
00:45:48,540 --> 00:45:50,690
I did not want to die a coward.

554
00:45:55,870 --> 00:45:58,260
Apparently I do not want to die at all.

555
00:46:00,710 --> 00:46:02,500
It takes courage to admit fear.

556
00:46:04,250 --> 00:46:05,950
And to admit a mistake.

557
00:46:08,020 --> 00:46:10,130
I came here to tell you that I was wrong.

558
00:46:13,450 --> 00:46:15,820
I was wrong and you were right.

559
00:46:17,820 --> 00:46:19,190
About tradition.

560
00:46:21,580 --> 00:46:24,040
About bringing the people of this city together.

561
00:46:27,940 --> 00:46:29,850
I will reopen the fighting pits.

562
00:46:30,710 --> 00:46:32,490
To free men only.

563
00:46:32,730 --> 00:46:36,820
Slavery will never return to Meereen, not while I live.

564
00:46:36,820 --> 00:46:38,250
Yes, my queen.

565
00:46:42,260 --> 00:46:46,200
And in order to forge a lasting bond with the Meereenese people,

566
00:46:46,510 --> 00:46:49,060
I will marry the leader of an ancient family.

567
00:46:51,420 --> 00:46:54,150
Thankfully a suitor is already on his knees.

568
00:47:22,530 --> 00:47:23,690
Don't worry.

569
00:47:24,540 --> 00:47:27,510
I'll be fine. Nothing broken, I don't think.

570
00:47:30,140 --> 00:47:31,410
Where are we now?

571
00:47:31,920 --> 00:47:33,350
Not the Rhoyne.

572
00:47:39,900 --> 00:47:42,410
Long, sullen silences

573
00:47:42,410 --> 00:47:45,380
and an occasional punch in the face.

574
00:47:47,480 --> 00:47:49,150
The Mormont way.

575
00:47:52,990 --> 00:47:55,330
Let's start over.

576
00:47:57,070 --> 00:47:59,360
I apologize for before.

577
00:47:59,570 --> 00:48:02,220
My mouth sometimes runs away from me.

578
00:48:02,850 --> 00:48:05,260
This doesn't have to be an unpleasant trip.

579
00:48:10,460 --> 00:48:13,210
We're going to be spending a lot of time together on the way to Meereen.

580
00:48:13,530 --> 00:48:14,450
We are.

581
00:48:16,760 --> 00:48:19,640
What would make our time together truly enjoyable

582
00:48:19,640 --> 00:48:20,970
would be some wine.

583
00:48:22,600 --> 00:48:23,740
No wine.

584
00:48:26,290 --> 00:48:29,690
I am a person who drinks.

585
00:48:31,590 --> 00:48:33,970
People who drink need to keep drinking.

586
00:48:33,980 --> 00:48:35,590
Otherwise, they're not...

587
00:48:43,450 --> 00:48:44,630
I know where we are.

588
00:48:45,020 --> 00:48:46,880
You're taking us through Valyria.

589
00:48:47,910 --> 00:48:48,880
I am.

590
00:48:49,560 --> 00:48:51,040
Have you sailed this route before?

591
00:48:51,090 --> 00:48:51,860
No.

592
00:48:52,930 --> 00:48:54,540
You're going to bring Daenerys a souvenir

593
00:48:54,550 --> 00:48:57,000
from her ancestral homeland in case I'm not enough?

594
00:48:57,390 --> 00:48:58,960
I think you'll be plenty.

595
00:49:00,480 --> 00:49:01,930
You know what they say.

596
00:49:03,050 --> 00:49:05,280
The Doom still rules Valyria.

597
00:49:06,270 --> 00:49:08,670
What about the demons and the flames?

598
00:49:09,930 --> 00:49:11,410
Aren't you afraid of the Doom?

599
00:49:12,020 --> 00:49:12,830
No.

600
00:49:14,330 --> 00:49:15,650
But pirates are.

601
00:49:21,490 --> 00:49:23,340
The Smoking Sea.

602
00:49:25,120 --> 00:49:26,890
How many centuries before we learn

603
00:49:26,890 --> 00:49:28,980
how to build cities like this again?

604
00:49:30,330 --> 00:49:32,750
For thousands of years the valyrians were

605
00:49:32,960 --> 00:49:36,170
the best in the world at almost everything.

606
00:49:36,970 --> 00:49:37,790
And then...

607
00:49:38,950 --> 00:49:40,290
And then they weren't.

608
00:49:41,830 --> 00:49:42,970
And then they weren't.

609
00:49:46,820 --> 00:49:50,910
"They held each other close and turned their backs upon the end.

610
00:49:51,650 --> 00:49:53,490
The hills that split asunder

611
00:49:53,960 --> 00:49:56,060
and the black that ate the skies;

612
00:49:56,640 --> 00:49:58,840
The flames that shot so high and hot

613
00:49:58,840 --> 00:50:00,580
that even dragons burned;

614
00:50:00,790 --> 00:50:02,920
Would never be the final sights

615
00:50:02,920 --> 00:50:04,640
that fell upon their eyes.

616
00:50:06,250 --> 00:50:07,720
A fly upon a wall,

617
00:50:08,300 --> 00:50:12,220
the waves the sea wind whipped and churned--"

618
00:50:12,300 --> 00:50:14,580
"The city of a thousand years,

619
00:50:15,030 --> 00:50:16,970
and all that men had learned;

620
00:50:17,350 --> 00:50:19,930
The Doom consumed it all alike,

621
00:50:20,820 --> 00:50:22,760
and neither of them turned."

622
00:50:26,010 --> 00:50:27,290
I would clap.

623
00:50:33,630 --> 00:50:35,420
I suppose this is it, then.

624
00:50:37,170 --> 00:50:38,810
This is what remains.

625
00:51:18,760 --> 00:51:19,910
What was that?

626
00:51:27,190 --> 00:51:28,500
Stone Men!

627
00:51:28,780 --> 00:51:30,270
Don't let them touch you!

628
00:51:47,030 --> 00:51:48,120
Get behind!

629
00:51:51,390 --> 00:51:53,310
Mormont, cut me free!

630
00:51:54,170 --> 00:51:55,150
Mormont!

631
00:52:10,770 --> 00:52:11,740
Mormont!

632
00:52:12,890 --> 00:52:14,040
Mormont!

633
00:52:50,470 --> 00:52:51,360
Tyrion?

634
00:52:55,450 --> 00:52:56,320
Tyrion.

635
00:52:58,140 --> 00:52:58,990
Tyrion.

636
00:53:00,990 --> 00:53:01,860
Tyrion.

637
00:53:04,190 --> 00:53:05,300
You're all right.

638
00:53:15,730 --> 00:53:17,300
You're heavier than you look.

639
00:53:20,510 --> 00:53:22,040
Did any of them touch you?

640
00:53:25,780 --> 00:53:26,650
You?

641
00:53:32,670 --> 00:53:34,330
I've seen greyscale before,

642
00:53:35,630 --> 00:53:36,880
but nothing like that.

643
00:53:37,610 --> 00:53:39,600
I suppose that's why they send them there.

644
00:53:41,850 --> 00:53:43,700
It'd be kinder to put daggers in their hearts

645
00:53:43,700 --> 00:53:44,910
and be done with it.

646
00:53:49,480 --> 00:53:52,510
Thank you for saving me.

647
00:53:55,900 --> 00:53:57,870
Of course, I wouldn't have needed saving

648
00:53:57,870 --> 00:53:59,990
if you hadn't kidnapped me in the first place.

649
00:54:04,530 --> 00:54:06,540
So what now?

650
00:54:06,600 --> 00:54:08,640
We walk up the coast.

651
00:54:08,640 --> 00:54:10,750
With luck, we'll find a fishing village.

652
00:54:11,490 --> 00:54:12,600
Maybe another boat.

653
00:54:13,020 --> 00:54:14,050
Without luck?

654
00:54:15,130 --> 00:54:16,880
We've got a long walk ahead of us.

655
00:54:19,990 --> 00:54:21,950
I'll get some wood for a fire.

656
00:54:22,870 --> 00:54:24,440
Try to get some rest, huh?

657
00:54:25,930 --> 00:54:28,300
That's the best idea you've had all day.

