1
00:02:48,350 --> 00:02:52,930
- Valar morghulis. - Valar dohaeris.

2
00:03:29,740 --> 00:03:32,200
I've been sweeping this floor for days.

3
00:03:32,900 --> 00:03:36,430
- Good. - I didn't come here to sweep floors.

4
00:03:36,870 --> 00:03:39,780
No? Why come then?

5
00:03:40,410 --> 00:03:42,380
You said that I could be your apprentice.

6
00:03:43,100 --> 00:03:46,150
You said you'd teach me how to be a Faceless Man.

7
00:03:46,150 --> 00:03:48,080
A man teaches a girl.

8
00:03:49,940 --> 00:03:53,690
Valar dohaeris. All men must serve.

9
00:03:54,130 --> 00:03:55,870
Faceless men, most of all.

10
00:03:57,870 --> 00:03:59,740
I want to serve.

11
00:04:03,190 --> 00:04:05,340
A girl wants to serve herself.

12
00:04:05,340 --> 00:04:08,890
Here we serve the Many-Faced God. To serve well,

13
00:04:09,720 --> 00:04:11,620
a girl must become no-one.

14
00:04:11,790 --> 00:04:13,680
Which one is the Many-Faced God?

15
00:04:14,270 --> 00:04:17,360
I see the Stranger. I see the Drowned God.

16
00:04:17,490 --> 00:04:20,760
- I see the Weirwood Face. - There is only one god.

17
00:04:21,320 --> 00:04:23,060
A girl knows his name.

18
00:04:23,980 --> 00:04:25,800
And all men know his gift.

19
00:05:03,770 --> 00:05:05,280
Where are they taking him?

20
00:05:33,110 --> 00:05:34,270
Queen Margaery!

21
00:05:36,890 --> 00:05:39,240
Queen Margaery!

22
00:05:39,740 --> 00:05:41,270
Queen Margaery!

23
00:05:45,990 --> 00:05:48,960
- I am his, and he is mine. - I am hers, and she is mine.

24
00:05:48,970 --> 00:05:52,470
From this day until the end of my days.

25
00:06:36,640 --> 00:06:37,810
Did I hurt you?

26
00:06:38,250 --> 00:06:40,360
No. You were lovely.

27
00:06:40,720 --> 00:06:43,140
- It all happened so fast. - Yes.

28
00:06:43,840 --> 00:06:46,500
I was scared maybe I hurt you. It sounded like...

29
00:06:46,500 --> 00:06:47,950
No, no, no...

30
00:06:48,590 --> 00:06:50,080
you're very sweet.

31
00:06:50,560 --> 00:06:53,230
The sweetest king who ever lived.

32
00:06:53,960 --> 00:06:56,650
This is what I want to do all day,

33
00:06:56,650 --> 00:06:58,820
every day for the rest of my life.

34
00:06:58,830 --> 00:07:00,800
Wouldn't that be glorious?

35
00:07:02,520 --> 00:07:04,300
Shouldn't we rest a little while?

36
00:07:04,300 --> 00:07:07,060
Just to catch our breath. There's no rush, is there?

37
00:07:07,170 --> 00:07:08,400
Of course not.

38
00:07:09,610 --> 00:07:10,730
Are you hungry?

39
00:07:10,730 --> 00:07:13,460
Should I have them bring you some cake or pomegranate juice...?

40
00:07:13,460 --> 00:07:14,700
No, I'm fine...

41
00:07:15,410 --> 00:07:17,830
I just want you all to myself.

42
00:07:18,410 --> 00:07:20,760
I want to know everything there is to know

43
00:07:20,760 --> 00:07:23,660
about King Tommen, First of His Name.

44
00:07:24,140 --> 00:07:28,050
King Tommen... it still sounds strange to me.

45
00:07:29,080 --> 00:07:31,830
Does Queen Margaery sound strange to you?

46
00:07:32,690 --> 00:07:34,130
So strange.

47
00:07:34,950 --> 00:07:37,220
- Husband. - Wife.

48
00:07:39,970 --> 00:07:41,730
Sometimes it feels odd.

49
00:07:42,250 --> 00:07:43,400
I'm the king,

50
00:07:44,050 --> 00:07:47,360
I've married the most beautiful woman in the world,

51
00:07:48,270 --> 00:07:50,310
and it's all because my brother died.

52
00:07:51,300 --> 00:07:52,890
I understand.

53
00:07:53,500 --> 00:07:56,320
But it's no your fault. You know that, don't you?

54
00:07:56,770 --> 00:07:58,710
You mustn't feel guilty.

55
00:07:59,790 --> 00:08:01,340
I don't feel guilty.

56
00:08:02,430 --> 00:08:03,610
That's what's odd.

57
00:08:07,280 --> 00:08:08,760
Do you like to sail?

58
00:08:09,240 --> 00:08:12,160
- I love to sail. - I do, too.

59
00:08:13,120 --> 00:08:15,950
I think we're going to be very happy, you and I.

60
00:08:16,530 --> 00:08:17,870
I do, too.

61
00:08:20,820 --> 00:08:25,480
Living in a tower so high, it touches the clouds.

62
00:08:26,870 --> 00:08:29,600
Of course, my grandmother couldn't wait to go home.

63
00:08:29,840 --> 00:08:32,450
The capital is not for everyone, I suppose.

64
00:08:34,660 --> 00:08:36,470
Does your mother like it here?

65
00:08:37,770 --> 00:08:39,010
I don't think so.

66
00:08:39,490 --> 00:08:42,400
She told me never to trust anyone in King's Landing.

67
00:08:43,970 --> 00:08:46,650
It's so wonderful to have her watching over you.

68
00:08:47,000 --> 00:08:49,500
A lioness guarding her cub.

69
00:08:49,700 --> 00:08:52,660
Well, but I'm a man now.

70
00:08:54,900 --> 00:08:55,920
You are.

71
00:08:58,160 --> 00:08:59,470
And the king.

72
00:09:02,200 --> 00:09:04,600
But you'll always be her baby-boy.

73
00:09:05,020 --> 00:09:06,240
I suppose.

74
00:09:07,400 --> 00:09:08,930
I adore her. She has always been

75
00:09:08,930 --> 00:09:11,360
so generous with me, so kind.

76
00:09:12,360 --> 00:09:14,740
And the horror she's had to endure -

77
00:09:15,000 --> 00:09:18,140
losing her husband, her eldest child, and her father.

78
00:09:18,140 --> 00:09:20,620
It's no wonder she's so protective of you.

79
00:09:20,960 --> 00:09:23,460
She'll never let you out of her sight.

80
00:09:27,200 --> 00:09:28,920
You look very much in love.

81
00:09:29,140 --> 00:09:32,140
The first days of marriage are often so blissful.

82
00:09:32,470 --> 00:09:34,560
She's certainly very pretty, isn't she?

83
00:09:35,510 --> 00:09:38,580
Like a doll. She smiles quite a lot.

84
00:09:40,160 --> 00:09:42,150
Do you think she's intelligent?

85
00:09:43,150 --> 00:09:44,560
I can't quite tell.

86
00:09:45,810 --> 00:09:47,120
Not that it matters.

87
00:09:47,120 --> 00:09:48,740
Do you ever miss Casterly Rock?

88
00:09:48,740 --> 00:09:51,010
There's nothing for me in Casterly Rock.

89
00:09:51,800 --> 00:09:53,380
That's where you grew up.

90
00:09:55,240 --> 00:09:57,800
You always told me that you liked the people there better.

91
00:09:58,140 --> 00:10:01,640
You said that King's Landing smelled of horse dung and sour milk.

92
00:10:04,470 --> 00:10:06,970
Why are we speaking of Casterly Rock?

93
00:10:06,970 --> 00:10:08,650
The way that you talked about it,

94
00:10:09,340 --> 00:10:11,430
I always thought that you missed it,

95
00:10:11,840 --> 00:10:14,600
that you... that it was your real home.

96
00:10:14,600 --> 00:10:16,460
This is my real home now.

97
00:10:16,460 --> 00:10:18,210
Where my family lives.

98
00:10:19,050 --> 00:10:21,440
I want you to be happy, mother.

99
00:10:22,280 --> 00:10:23,570
I know that.

100
00:10:25,120 --> 00:10:27,960
I know you do. My sweet boy.

101
00:10:28,040 --> 00:10:30,390
But wouldn't you be happier in Casterly Rock?

102
00:10:32,760 --> 00:10:36,350
I said, "Darling, surely four times is enough."

103
00:10:36,350 --> 00:10:38,200
"Are you trying to set a new record?"

104
00:10:38,200 --> 00:10:40,650
And he said, "Well, what is the record?

105
00:10:40,650 --> 00:10:42,380
I'm sure we can break it."

106
00:10:47,360 --> 00:10:48,580
Mother.

107
00:10:49,430 --> 00:10:50,760
Welcome.

108
00:10:51,990 --> 00:10:53,370
Don't you look lovely.

109
00:10:53,460 --> 00:10:54,810
Marriage agrees with you.

110
00:10:54,810 --> 00:10:57,520
Can we bring you anything to eat or drink?

111
00:10:57,530 --> 00:10:59,090
I wish we had some wine for you.

112
00:10:59,090 --> 00:11:01,110
It's a bit early in the day for us.

113
00:11:02,870 --> 00:11:05,430
No, no, I... I can't stay.

114
00:11:06,110 --> 00:11:08,430
I just wanted to let you know

115
00:11:09,010 --> 00:11:10,810
if there's ever anything I can do for you.

116
00:11:10,810 --> 00:11:12,410
You are very sweet.

117
00:11:12,820 --> 00:11:15,190
Tommen seems quite taken with his new queen.

118
00:11:15,190 --> 00:11:18,220
I absolutely adore him.

119
00:11:18,220 --> 00:11:20,000
You raised a gallant young man.

120
00:11:20,000 --> 00:11:22,490
- I'm forever grateful. - Good.

121
00:11:24,020 --> 00:11:25,100
Good.

122
00:11:25,340 --> 00:11:26,540
I'm glad to hear you're happy.

123
00:11:26,540 --> 00:11:28,830
Ecstatic. I really am.

124
00:11:29,130 --> 00:11:31,680
Exhausted, to be honest, but

125
00:11:31,740 --> 00:11:35,090
what can I expect, he is half lion, half stag.

126
00:11:36,970 --> 00:11:38,540
I'll leave you to it then.

127
00:11:38,870 --> 00:11:40,220
Oh, forgive me,

128
00:11:40,220 --> 00:11:41,910
I haven't been at Court for long,

129
00:11:41,910 --> 00:11:43,510
I get so confused.

130
00:11:43,510 --> 00:11:45,750
What's the proper way to address you now?

131
00:11:45,750 --> 00:11:48,030
Queen Mother or Dowager Queen?

132
00:11:49,920 --> 00:11:51,870
There's no need for such formalities.

133
00:11:51,870 --> 00:11:55,220
In any event, judging from the King's enthusiasm,

134
00:11:55,220 --> 00:11:57,700
the Queen Mother will be a Queen Grandmother soon.

135
00:11:57,710 --> 00:11:59,190
Won't that be a lovely day.

136
00:11:59,190 --> 00:12:01,080
Can you imagine the celebrations?

137
00:12:01,080 --> 00:12:03,450
They'll ring the bells all day and night.

138
00:12:03,450 --> 00:12:04,560
Remember.

139
00:12:06,060 --> 00:12:07,620
Anything you need.

140
00:13:23,070 --> 00:13:25,400
We can't hold the North with terror alone.

141
00:13:25,400 --> 00:13:28,360
You can't hold the North if you let these lesser lords insult us.

142
00:13:28,360 --> 00:13:31,130
I sent you there to collect taxes, not bodies.

143
00:13:31,130 --> 00:13:32,900
Lord Cerwyn refused to pay.

144
00:13:33,940 --> 00:13:36,390
He said the Warden of the North would always be a Stark

145
00:13:36,390 --> 00:13:39,030
and he'd be damned if he'd kiss a traitor's boot.

146
00:13:41,630 --> 00:13:43,140
He left you no choice.

147
00:13:43,850 --> 00:13:45,190
I flayed him living,

148
00:13:45,300 --> 00:13:47,490
along with his wife and brother.

149
00:13:47,730 --> 00:13:49,440
I made his son watch.

150
00:13:51,090 --> 00:13:52,130
And?

151
00:13:52,320 --> 00:13:54,630
The new Lord Cerwyn paid his taxes.

152
00:14:01,490 --> 00:14:03,460
I have something important to tell you.

153
00:14:04,870 --> 00:14:06,660
Stop eating and listen.

154
00:14:16,230 --> 00:14:17,930
We don't have enough men to hold the North

155
00:14:17,930 --> 00:14:20,250
if the other Houses rise up against us.

156
00:14:20,710 --> 00:14:22,000
Do you understand that?

157
00:14:22,000 --> 00:14:23,880
Our pact with the Lannisters protects...

158
00:14:23,880 --> 00:14:25,780
I had a pact with Tywin Lannister.

159
00:14:25,780 --> 00:14:27,570
And Tywin Lannister is dead.

160
00:14:28,190 --> 00:14:30,370
The remaining Lannisters are a thousand miles away

161
00:14:30,370 --> 00:14:31,710
dealing with that fact.

162
00:14:31,710 --> 00:14:34,010
They've never once in the history of the Seven Kingdoms

163
00:14:34,010 --> 00:14:35,940
sent their army this far north.

164
00:14:36,190 --> 00:14:38,770
If you think they will for us, you're a fool.

165
00:14:40,170 --> 00:14:41,510
We've  become a great House

166
00:14:41,510 --> 00:14:43,790
by entering into alliances with other Houses,

167
00:14:43,790 --> 00:14:46,880
and parlaying those alliances into greater power.

168
00:14:47,050 --> 00:14:49,600
The best way to forge a lasting alliance

169
00:14:49,600 --> 00:14:51,980
isn't by peeling a man's skin off.

170
00:14:52,250 --> 00:14:54,250
The best way is marriage.

171
00:14:55,160 --> 00:14:57,860
Now that you're a Bolton by royal decree,

172
00:14:58,460 --> 00:15:00,860
it's high time you married a suitable bride.

173
00:15:04,760 --> 00:15:06,140
And as it happens,

174
00:15:06,480 --> 00:15:10,110
I've found the perfect girl to solidify our hold on the North.

175
00:15:32,090 --> 00:15:34,420
- That's Moat Cailin. - Yes.

176
00:15:34,790 --> 00:15:36,470
A bit shabby, isn't it?

177
00:15:37,090 --> 00:15:38,630
You've been here before.

178
00:15:39,230 --> 00:15:40,880
On our way down to King's Landing,

179
00:15:40,880 --> 00:15:43,170
with my father and Arya and...

180
00:15:44,110 --> 00:15:46,610
- Where are you taking me? - Home.

181
00:15:48,840 --> 00:15:50,830
The Boltons have Winterfell.

182
00:15:54,300 --> 00:15:56,880
Your marriage proposal, it wasn't for you?

183
00:15:58,300 --> 00:15:59,380
No.

184
00:16:00,220 --> 00:16:02,940
Roose Bolton murdered my brother.

185
00:16:02,940 --> 00:16:04,740
He betrayed my family!

186
00:16:04,740 --> 00:16:05,840
He did.

187
00:16:06,240 --> 00:16:08,300
He serves the Lannisters.

188
00:16:08,300 --> 00:16:10,780
- For now. - I won't go.

189
00:16:10,880 --> 00:16:13,190
- Winterfell is your home. - Not anymore.

190
00:16:13,190 --> 00:16:15,870
Always. You're a Stark.

191
00:16:16,180 --> 00:16:19,180
Dying your hair doesn't change that. You're Sansa Stark.

192
00:16:19,180 --> 00:16:22,110
The eldest surviving child of Ned and Catelyn Stark.

193
00:16:22,560 --> 00:16:24,120
Your place is in the North.

194
00:16:24,120 --> 00:16:26,080
I can't marry him. You can't make me.

195
00:16:26,080 --> 00:16:28,410
He is a traitor. A murderer!

196
00:16:28,410 --> 00:16:30,300
You're not marrying Roose Bolton.

197
00:16:30,300 --> 00:16:33,660
No, you'll be marrying his son and heir, Ramsay.

198
00:16:33,890 --> 00:16:36,470
- One day he'll be Warden of the North and you... - No!

199
00:16:36,470 --> 00:16:38,300
- Sansa... - No, you can't make me.

200
00:16:38,300 --> 00:16:39,620
I will starve myself.

201
00:16:39,620 --> 00:16:41,970
I will die before I have to go there.

202
00:16:41,970 --> 00:16:44,170
I won't force you to do anything.

203
00:16:45,170 --> 00:16:47,320
Don't you know by now how much I care for you?

204
00:16:48,680 --> 00:16:51,330
Say the word and we turn the horses round, but listen to me.

205
00:16:51,330 --> 00:16:52,460
Listen.

206
00:16:53,080 --> 00:16:54,950
You've been running all your life.

207
00:16:56,390 --> 00:16:59,110
Terrible things happened to your family and you weep.

208
00:16:59,130 --> 00:17:02,220
You sit alone in a darkened room, mourning their fates.

209
00:17:02,350 --> 00:17:03,880
You've been a bystander to tragedy

210
00:17:03,880 --> 00:17:06,220
from the day they executed your father.

211
00:17:06,920 --> 00:17:09,440
Stop being a bystander. You hear me?

212
00:17:09,440 --> 00:17:10,610
Stop running.

213
00:17:15,850 --> 00:17:17,890
There's no justice in the world.

214
00:17:18,740 --> 00:17:20,390
Not unless we make it.

215
00:17:22,240 --> 00:17:23,720
You loved your family.

216
00:17:25,640 --> 00:17:26,910
Avenge them.

217
00:18:28,430 --> 00:18:29,850
How do we get through there?

218
00:18:30,190 --> 00:18:31,380
We don't.

219
00:18:31,680 --> 00:18:32,950
We go around.

220
00:18:33,340 --> 00:18:34,960
Takes us miles out of the way.

221
00:18:35,980 --> 00:18:38,470
- We'll lose sight of them. - Doesn't matter.

222
00:18:38,520 --> 00:18:39,850
I know where they're going.

223
00:18:44,210 --> 00:18:46,160
Are you getting a bit old to be a squire?

224
00:18:50,940 --> 00:18:53,330
How did you end up squiring for the Imp?

225
00:18:53,730 --> 00:18:55,100
He hates that nickname.

226
00:18:55,100 --> 00:18:57,520
Well, he's not here to complain about it, is he?

227
00:19:01,950 --> 00:19:03,450
I squired for a knight named Ser Lorimer

228
00:19:03,460 --> 00:19:05,610
during the War of the Five Kings.

229
00:19:05,610 --> 00:19:06,940
One night,

230
00:19:06,990 --> 00:19:08,750
he had a bit too much to drink

231
00:19:08,750 --> 00:19:11,430
and he was famished, so he borrowed a ham.

232
00:19:11,430 --> 00:19:14,020
- He borrowed it? - He wasn't a thief.

233
00:19:14,030 --> 00:19:16,650
He was drunk and hungry and he wasn't thinking.

234
00:19:16,650 --> 00:19:17,950
I was drunk too.

235
00:19:18,510 --> 00:19:20,390
He gave me half the ham.

236
00:19:22,120 --> 00:19:23,370
Next morning,

237
00:19:23,860 --> 00:19:26,310
one of the guards saw him passed out

238
00:19:26,310 --> 00:19:29,300
under a wagon with the ham bone still in his hand.

239
00:19:30,170 --> 00:19:31,950
They hanged the man after noon.

240
00:19:33,250 --> 00:19:35,110
They tied the noose for me too,

241
00:19:35,110 --> 00:19:37,610
but Lord Tywin heard my family name was Payne,

242
00:19:37,610 --> 00:19:39,110
so he pardoned me,

243
00:19:39,110 --> 00:19:41,700
and sent me to King's Landing to squire for his son.

244
00:19:41,700 --> 00:19:43,220
As punishment

245
00:19:43,980 --> 00:19:46,640
- for both of you. - It didn't seem that way.

246
00:19:47,080 --> 00:19:49,110
Lord Tyrion was always very good to me.

247
00:19:49,110 --> 00:19:51,260
Yes, all of your lords have been very kind to you.

248
00:19:51,260 --> 00:19:52,750
All except me.

249
00:19:52,930 --> 00:19:55,650
Sorry you had to squire for such a nasty person.

250
00:19:55,650 --> 00:19:58,340
I'm not sorry. You're the best fighter I've ever seen.

251
00:19:58,690 --> 00:20:00,210
You beat The Hound.

252
00:20:01,250 --> 00:20:03,210
I'm proud to be your squire.

253
00:20:08,280 --> 00:20:10,440
I'm sorry I'm always snapping at you.

254
00:20:10,600 --> 00:20:12,910
If you didn't snap at me, I wouldn't learn anything.

255
00:20:16,970 --> 00:20:18,580
You want to be a knight, Pod?

256
00:20:20,270 --> 00:20:21,080
Yes.

257
00:20:21,080 --> 00:20:23,820
Starting tomorrow, we'll train with the sword twice a day,

258
00:20:23,820 --> 00:20:26,890
before we ride in the morning and after you make camp in the evening.

259
00:20:27,510 --> 00:20:29,670
And I'm going to show you how to ride properly.

260
00:20:29,670 --> 00:20:30,460
Thank you.

261
00:20:30,470 --> 00:20:31,700
I can't knight you,

262
00:20:31,700 --> 00:20:33,160
but I can teach you how to fight.

263
00:20:33,160 --> 00:20:34,980
I suppose that's more important.

264
00:20:47,430 --> 00:20:49,200
You weren't a knight, but

265
00:20:49,470 --> 00:20:52,550
you were a Kingsguard to Renly Baratheon, weren't you?

266
00:20:53,490 --> 00:20:54,470
I was.

267
00:20:55,140 --> 00:20:57,230
Lord Tyrion said he was a good man.

268
00:20:59,560 --> 00:21:00,570
He was.

269
00:21:02,560 --> 00:21:04,560
How did you end up serving Renly?

270
00:21:10,760 --> 00:21:11,690
When I was a girl,

271
00:21:11,690 --> 00:21:13,650
my father held a ball.

272
00:21:13,650 --> 00:21:15,030
I'm his only living child,

273
00:21:15,030 --> 00:21:17,160
so he wanted to make a good match for me.

274
00:21:17,170 --> 00:21:19,870
He invited dozens of young lords to Tarth.

275
00:21:19,870 --> 00:21:22,990
I didn't want to go, but he dragged me to the ballroom.

276
00:21:26,130 --> 00:21:27,740
And it was wonderful.

277
00:21:30,100 --> 00:21:33,750
None of the boys noticed how mulish and tall I was.

278
00:21:34,780 --> 00:21:37,120
They shove each other and threatened to duel

279
00:21:37,120 --> 00:21:39,340
when they thought it was their turn to dance.

280
00:21:40,770 --> 00:21:42,210
Whispered in my ear

281
00:21:42,710 --> 00:21:44,010
how they wanted to marry me

282
00:21:44,010 --> 00:21:46,260
and take me back to their castles.

283
00:21:48,490 --> 00:21:51,630
My father smiled at me and I smiled at him.

284
00:21:53,510 --> 00:21:55,470
I had never been so happy.

285
00:21:58,780 --> 00:22:01,290
Till I saw a few of the boys snickering.

286
00:22:03,290 --> 00:22:04,980
And then they all started to laugh,

287
00:22:04,980 --> 00:22:07,020
they couldn't keep the game going any longer.

288
00:22:07,730 --> 00:22:09,540
They were toying with me.

289
00:22:10,920 --> 00:22:13,260
"Brienne the Beauty" they called me.

290
00:22:13,260 --> 00:22:14,770
Great joke.

291
00:22:16,090 --> 00:22:19,780
And I realized I was the ugliest girl alive.

292
00:22:20,690 --> 00:22:23,480
A great lumbering beast.

293
00:22:28,220 --> 00:22:29,350
I tried to run away,

294
00:22:29,350 --> 00:22:32,170
but Renly Baratheon took me in his arms.

295
00:22:32,960 --> 00:22:35,570
"Don't let them see your tears", he told me.

296
00:22:35,750 --> 00:22:37,670
"The nasty little shits

297
00:22:37,670 --> 00:22:40,540
and nasty little shits aren't worth crying over."

298
00:22:41,890 --> 00:22:44,940
He danced with me and none of the other boys could say a word.

299
00:22:46,190 --> 00:22:48,660
Renly was the king's brother after all.

300
00:22:50,870 --> 00:22:52,800
But wasn't he...

301
00:22:54,750 --> 00:22:57,030
Lord Tyrion said he was...

302
00:22:58,420 --> 00:23:01,440
Yes, Pod, he liked men. I'm not an idiot.

303
00:23:01,490 --> 00:23:03,310
He didn't love me. He didn't want me,

304
00:23:03,310 --> 00:23:05,110
he danced with me because he was kind

305
00:23:05,110 --> 00:23:06,900
and he didn't want to see me hurt.

306
00:23:07,760 --> 00:23:10,700
He saved me from being a joke.

307
00:23:10,890 --> 00:23:12,250
From that day

308
00:23:12,620 --> 00:23:14,360
until his last day.

309
00:23:17,090 --> 00:23:19,440
And I couldn't save him in return.

310
00:23:22,980 --> 00:23:25,130
Nothing's more hateful than failing to protect

311
00:23:25,130 --> 00:23:26,590
the one you love.

312
00:23:28,810 --> 00:23:31,440
One day, I will avenge King Renly.

313
00:23:31,670 --> 00:23:33,820
But you said a shadow murdered him.

314
00:23:34,910 --> 00:23:36,360
How do you fight a shadow?

315
00:23:36,360 --> 00:23:39,360
A shadow with the face of Stannis Baratheon.

316
00:23:40,220 --> 00:23:41,660
I know it was Stannis.

317
00:23:41,660 --> 00:23:43,410
I know it in my heart.

318
00:23:46,900 --> 00:23:49,250
Stannis is a man, not a shadow.

319
00:23:50,060 --> 00:23:51,300
And a man

320
00:23:52,190 --> 00:23:53,710
can be killed.

321
00:23:56,620 --> 00:23:58,460
- Lord Commander. - Your Grace.

322
00:23:58,750 --> 00:24:00,310
I'd like to speak alone.

323
00:24:00,760 --> 00:24:02,540
Olly is my steward now, 

324
00:24:03,060 --> 00:24:05,080
as I was Lord Commander Mormont's.

325
00:24:06,000 --> 00:24:07,840
I want him to attend my meetings,

326
00:24:07,880 --> 00:24:10,350
to learn from men with experience.

327
00:24:11,960 --> 00:24:13,860
One day, he might command.

328
00:24:17,820 --> 00:24:20,560
Very well. Have you considered my offer?

329
00:24:22,360 --> 00:24:23,380
I have.

330
00:24:23,570 --> 00:24:25,970
And I thank you for it. You do me great honor.

331
00:24:26,970 --> 00:24:29,560
All my life I wanted to be Jon Stark.

332
00:24:29,560 --> 00:24:30,980
Say the word and you will be.

333
00:24:33,010 --> 00:24:34,930
But I have to refuse you.

334
00:24:36,150 --> 00:24:38,630
I'm Lord Commander of the Night's Watch.

335
00:24:38,940 --> 00:24:40,380
My place is here.

336
00:24:40,380 --> 00:24:43,110
I'm giving you the chance to avenge your family,

337
00:24:44,270 --> 00:24:46,630
to take back the castle where you grew up,

338
00:24:48,890 --> 00:24:50,800
to rule the North.

339
00:24:50,970 --> 00:24:52,820
I wish I could fight beside you.

340
00:24:53,610 --> 00:24:55,340
Believe me, I do.

341
00:24:55,600 --> 00:24:58,710
But I swore a sacred vow at the Godswood.

342
00:24:59,050 --> 00:25:01,810
I pledged my life to the Night's Watch.

343
00:25:01,810 --> 00:25:03,890
You're as stubborn as your father.

344
00:25:05,100 --> 00:25:06,510
And as honorable.

345
00:25:06,790 --> 00:25:08,450
I can imagine no higher praise.

346
00:25:08,450 --> 00:25:10,170
I didn't mean it as praise.

347
00:25:10,180 --> 00:25:12,150
Honor got your father killed.

348
00:25:12,650 --> 00:25:13,540
But if your mind's made up,

349
00:25:13,540 --> 00:25:14,870
I won't try and dissuade you.

350
00:25:14,870 --> 00:25:16,290
May I ask, Your Grace,

351
00:25:16,290 --> 00:25:18,160
how long you plan to stay at Castle Black?

352
00:25:18,160 --> 00:25:19,810
Are you bored of us already?

353
00:25:21,320 --> 00:25:23,510
You saved us from Mance Rayder's army.

354
00:25:23,510 --> 00:25:25,120
We will never forget that.

355
00:25:25,260 --> 00:25:27,110
But it's a question of survival.

356
00:25:27,110 --> 00:25:29,140
The Night's Watch can't continue to

357
00:25:29,140 --> 00:25:32,310
feed your men and the wildling prisoners indefinitely.

358
00:25:32,740 --> 00:25:34,810
Winter is coming.

359
00:25:36,570 --> 00:25:37,660
I know it.

360
00:25:37,860 --> 00:25:40,200
We march on Winterfell within the fortnight,

361
00:25:40,200 --> 00:25:42,140
before the snows trap us here.

362
00:25:43,510 --> 00:25:44,740
And the wildlings?

363
00:25:44,740 --> 00:25:46,660
If they'd rather burn than fight for me,

364
00:25:46,660 --> 00:25:47,200
so be it.

365
00:25:47,200 --> 00:25:48,820
I leave their fate to you.

366
00:25:49,450 --> 00:25:52,310
You could execute them. That's the safest course.

367
00:25:56,580 --> 00:25:58,980
Or you could see if this Tormund fellow is more willing

368
00:25:58,980 --> 00:26:01,160
to compromise than Mance ever was.

369
00:26:01,160 --> 00:26:02,070
I assume the brothers of

370
00:26:02,070 --> 00:26:04,630
the Night's Watch would rather see the wildlings dead.

371
00:26:04,630 --> 00:26:06,380
Most of the brothers, yes.

372
00:26:07,620 --> 00:26:09,820
There's little love for the free folk here.

373
00:26:10,280 --> 00:26:11,930
You're the Lord Commander.

374
00:26:12,140 --> 00:26:13,440
Your decision.

375
00:26:15,440 --> 00:26:17,210
You have many enemies in Castle Black.

376
00:26:17,210 --> 00:26:20,080
Have you considered sending Alliser Thorne elsewhere?

377
00:26:21,560 --> 00:26:23,990
Give him command of Eastwach by the Sea.

378
00:26:24,150 --> 00:26:26,790
I heard it was best to keep your enemies close.

379
00:26:26,790 --> 00:26:28,870
Whoever said that didn't have many enemies.

380
00:26:36,990 --> 00:26:38,540
He sees something in you.

381
00:26:40,210 --> 00:26:42,390
Might not be apparent from his tone,

382
00:26:43,180 --> 00:26:45,370
but it's the truth. He believes in you.

383
00:26:45,370 --> 00:26:47,300
I'm sorry I disappointed him.

384
00:26:51,940 --> 00:26:54,420
The king is a complicated man,

385
00:26:55,240 --> 00:26:57,750
but he wants what's right for the Seven Kingdoms.

386
00:26:57,750 --> 00:26:59,190
As long as he's ruling them.

387
00:26:59,190 --> 00:27:00,740
He's the one true king.

388
00:27:01,630 --> 00:27:03,700
He has a blood right to that throne.

389
00:27:03,700 --> 00:27:07,390
I've sworn to stay clear of the politics of the Seven Kingdoms.

390
00:27:07,400 --> 00:27:08,580
Have you now?

391
00:27:11,810 --> 00:27:14,050
How does the Night's Watch vow go again?

392
00:27:14,680 --> 00:27:16,850
I'll bet you've got it memorized since you got here.

393
00:27:19,790 --> 00:27:22,150
Night gathers and now my watch begins...

394
00:27:22,150 --> 00:27:24,760
Not that bit, the bit at the end.

395
00:27:25,640 --> 00:27:28,030
I'm the sword in the darkness,

396
00:27:28,130 --> 00:27:29,850
the watcher on the walls,

397
00:27:29,850 --> 00:27:32,400
the shield that guards the realm of men.

398
00:27:32,400 --> 00:27:34,200
- I pledge my life... - Right, that's enough.

399
00:27:34,200 --> 00:27:36,490
The shield that guards the realm of men.

400
00:27:37,420 --> 00:27:39,020
That's what you swore to be.

401
00:27:39,260 --> 00:27:40,720
Now, I'm not a learned man,

402
00:27:40,720 --> 00:27:42,920
but the best way to help the most people might not be sitting

403
00:27:42,930 --> 00:27:45,640
in a frozen castle at the edge of the world.

404
00:27:45,640 --> 00:27:48,000
It just might mean wading in the muck,

405
00:27:48,000 --> 00:27:51,190
getting your boots dirty, and doing what needs to be done.

406
00:27:51,220 --> 00:27:52,750
And what needs to be done?

407
00:27:52,750 --> 00:27:54,830
As long as the Boltons rule the North,

408
00:27:55,360 --> 00:27:56,930
the North will suffer.

409
00:27:57,920 --> 00:27:59,410
Just one man's opinion.

410
00:28:29,270 --> 00:28:30,220
What do you want?

411
00:28:31,390 --> 00:28:32,360
Who are you?

412
00:28:34,040 --> 00:28:34,810
What?

413
00:28:34,860 --> 00:28:37,760
You, who walk in here with a coin you never earned,

414
00:28:37,760 --> 00:28:39,840
whose value you do not respect.

415
00:28:45,980 --> 00:28:46,900
Who are you?

416
00:28:49,990 --> 00:28:50,850
No one.

417
00:28:51,150 --> 00:28:52,710
Ou! Cunt!

418
00:28:52,710 --> 00:28:54,750
A lie. A sad little lie.

419
00:28:55,090 --> 00:28:56,790
- Who are you? - I told you, I'm no...

420
00:28:57,310 --> 00:28:58,450
Do that again and...

421
00:28:59,740 --> 00:29:00,790
Who are you?

422
00:29:01,680 --> 00:29:03,080
You're about to find out.

423
00:29:04,590 --> 00:29:05,810
What are you doing?

424
00:29:06,550 --> 00:29:07,660
We were only playing.

425
00:29:08,020 --> 00:29:09,360
The Game of Faces.

426
00:29:09,430 --> 00:29:10,910
That girl is not ready.

427
00:29:10,910 --> 00:29:12,040
Clearly not.

428
00:29:12,170 --> 00:29:13,350
I am ready.

429
00:29:15,180 --> 00:29:16,370
For what?

430
00:29:16,390 --> 00:29:17,700
For every you want,

431
00:29:17,700 --> 00:29:19,620
to be a Faceless Man,

432
00:29:19,620 --> 00:29:20,750
to be no one.

433
00:29:25,620 --> 00:29:27,040
Whose sword is that?

434
00:29:27,370 --> 00:29:29,080
It belongs to Arya Stark.

435
00:29:29,080 --> 00:29:31,400
Arya Stark's sword, Arya Stark's clothes,

436
00:29:31,400 --> 00:29:33,370
Arya Stark's stolen silver.

437
00:29:33,370 --> 00:29:35,150
A man wonders

438
00:29:35,540 --> 00:29:37,660
how is it that no one

439
00:29:37,810 --> 00:29:40,840
came to be surrounded by Arya Stark's things?

440
00:33:45,390 --> 00:33:47,690
What do we do with them after we wash them?

441
00:34:18,960 --> 00:34:20,770
Open gates!

442
00:34:53,240 --> 00:34:56,100
Lady Sansa. Welcome.

443
00:35:02,630 --> 00:35:03,670
Lord Bolton.

444
00:35:05,690 --> 00:35:09,440
May I introduce my son, Ramsay Bolton?

445
00:35:12,140 --> 00:35:15,250
It's an honor to meet you, my lady.

446
00:35:30,750 --> 00:35:32,910
I'll bring you a bowl of hot water.

447
00:35:33,240 --> 00:35:34,770
You must want to wash.

448
00:35:35,860 --> 00:35:36,940
Thank you.

449
00:35:40,360 --> 00:35:42,210
Welcome home, Lady Stark.

450
00:35:44,630 --> 00:35:46,220
The North remembers.

451
00:35:59,810 --> 00:36:00,540
Sam?

452
00:36:02,300 --> 00:36:03,390
Maester Aemon?

453
00:36:03,520 --> 00:36:05,590
He apologizes for not being here.

454
00:36:06,620 --> 00:36:07,900
He's not feeling well.

455
00:36:08,150 --> 00:36:09,440
Take good care of him.

456
00:36:10,100 --> 00:36:11,510
I will drink it then.

457
00:36:11,560 --> 00:36:12,500
Brothers.

458
00:36:13,950 --> 00:36:15,360
As you all know too well,

459
00:36:15,370 --> 00:36:17,850
it's long past time to dig a new latrine pit.

460
00:36:22,050 --> 00:36:24,200
First Builder Yarwyck and I have decided to appoint

461
00:36:24,200 --> 00:36:27,560
a latrine captain to oversee this crucial task.

462
00:36:34,910 --> 00:36:35,720
Brian.

463
00:36:36,680 --> 00:36:38,460
It seems like a good job for a ginger.

464
00:36:46,410 --> 00:36:47,460
Ser Alliser.

465
00:36:51,610 --> 00:36:54,800
You have more experience than any other ranger at Castle Black.

466
00:36:54,960 --> 00:36:57,210
You proved your valour many times over

467
00:36:57,330 --> 00:36:59,810
by defending the Wall from the wildling attack.

468
00:37:02,820 --> 00:37:04,510
I name you First Ranger.

469
00:37:11,660 --> 00:37:12,630
Lord Janos.

470
00:37:13,360 --> 00:37:15,140
I'm giving you command of Greyguard.

471
00:37:16,810 --> 00:37:18,010
Greyguard is a ruin.

472
00:37:18,010 --> 00:37:20,240
Yes, the fort is in a sorry state.

473
00:37:20,290 --> 00:37:21,860
Restore it as best you can.

474
00:37:22,100 --> 00:37:23,550
First Builder Yarwyck can spare 10 of his...

475
00:37:23,550 --> 00:37:25,630
I was charged with the defense of King's Landing

476
00:37:25,640 --> 00:37:27,780
when you were soiling your swaddling clothes.

477
00:37:27,780 --> 00:37:29,180
Keep your ruin.

478
00:37:32,740 --> 00:37:34,210
Alright, alright.

479
00:37:34,330 --> 00:37:35,580
Enough of that.

480
00:37:36,230 --> 00:37:37,820
You mistake me, my Lord.

481
00:37:39,750 --> 00:37:42,470
That was a command, not an offer.

482
00:37:42,730 --> 00:37:45,720
Pack your arms and armour, say your farewells,

483
00:37:46,650 --> 00:37:48,180
and ride for Greyguard.

484
00:37:51,060 --> 00:37:53,800
I will not go meekly off to freeze and die.

485
00:37:54,080 --> 00:37:56,840
Give it to one of the fools who cast a stone for you.

486
00:37:57,080 --> 00:37:58,330
I will not have it.

487
00:37:58,330 --> 00:37:59,660
Did you hear me, boy?

488
00:37:59,660 --> 00:38:01,490
I will not have it!

489
00:38:01,830 --> 00:38:03,990
You refusing to obey my order?

490
00:38:09,840 --> 00:38:12,880
You can stick your order up your bastard arse.

491
00:38:20,340 --> 00:38:22,060
Take Lord Janos outside.

492
00:38:24,500 --> 00:38:26,040
Olly, bring me my sword.

493
00:38:48,400 --> 00:38:49,900
You cannot do this!

494
00:38:49,980 --> 00:38:51,220
Get your hands off me!

495
00:38:51,780 --> 00:38:53,540
Scum! All of you!

496
00:38:58,030 --> 00:39:00,040
If the boy thinks he can frighten me,

497
00:39:00,040 --> 00:39:02,640
je's mistaken, yes, very mistaken.

498
00:39:04,780 --> 00:39:06,580
Disgrace!

499
00:39:06,910 --> 00:39:09,520
I have friends. Important friends in the capital!

500
00:39:09,520 --> 00:39:10,580
You'll see!

501
00:39:46,830 --> 00:39:48,810
If you have any last words, my Lord,

502
00:39:49,890 --> 00:39:50,970
now is the time.

503
00:39:54,340 --> 00:39:56,630
I was wrong. You're the Lord Commander!

504
00:39:56,630 --> 00:39:58,700
We all serve you. I'm sorry.

505
00:39:58,700 --> 00:40:01,330
Not only for this, for all I've done and said.

506
00:40:03,320 --> 00:40:04,230
I was wrong!

507
00:40:06,190 --> 00:40:09,170
My Lord, please, mercy! Mercy!

508
00:40:09,550 --> 00:40:10,790
I'll go! I will!

509
00:40:11,700 --> 00:40:12,790
Please.

510
00:40:13,620 --> 00:40:14,730
I'm afraid.

511
00:40:16,540 --> 00:40:18,840
I've always been afraid.

512
00:41:02,690 --> 00:41:06,030
You have served us well, my son.

513
00:41:06,080 --> 00:41:07,450
Thank you, Father!

514
00:41:07,590 --> 00:41:10,500
Which of the Seven will you worship today?

515
00:41:10,510 --> 00:41:13,700
- The Maiden... - Always the Maiden

516
00:41:14,890 --> 00:41:16,680
And the Stranger.

517
00:41:16,880 --> 00:41:19,630
- Two is extra, you realize... - Yes, yes.

518
00:41:31,330 --> 00:41:32,320
What are you doing?

519
00:41:32,660 --> 00:41:35,590
This establishment belong to Lord Petyr Baelish. You can't...

520
00:41:36,500 --> 00:41:38,560
You have profaned our Faith.

521
00:41:38,560 --> 00:41:41,400
The Faith of our fathers and forefathers.

522
00:41:41,410 --> 00:41:43,510
I am the High Septon of the...

523
00:41:43,510 --> 00:41:45,190
You are a sinner.

524
00:41:45,850 --> 00:41:47,480
And you shall be punished.

525
00:42:02,280 --> 00:42:03,920
Sinner! Sinner!

526
00:42:04,600 --> 00:42:06,210
- Sinner! - Repent!

527
00:42:06,210 --> 00:42:08,050
Sinner! Sinner!

528
00:42:08,050 --> 00:42:10,210
Sinner! Sinner! Sinner!

529
00:42:10,210 --> 00:42:13,770
- Sinner! Sinner! - Shame on you!

530
00:42:14,230 --> 00:42:15,150
Sinner!

531
00:42:25,980 --> 00:42:28,750
Your Grace, Grandmaester, Lord Tyrell...

532
00:42:30,670 --> 00:42:31,870
It doesn't matter.

533
00:42:33,340 --> 00:42:35,490
As the High Septon of the Faith of the Seven

534
00:42:35,490 --> 00:42:37,150
I give voice to the will of the Gods

535
00:42:37,150 --> 00:42:40,290
and I am their foremost servant in this world.

536
00:42:40,530 --> 00:42:43,490
An insult to me is an insult to the Gods.

537
00:42:43,500 --> 00:42:45,910
An assault on my person

538
00:42:46,110 --> 00:42:47,850
is an assault on our very religion.

539
00:42:47,860 --> 00:42:48,810
You were assaulted?

540
00:42:48,810 --> 00:42:49,550
I was.

541
00:42:49,550 --> 00:42:52,250
By those fanatics who call themselves sparrows.

542
00:42:52,610 --> 00:42:54,260
And they humiliated me, they... beat me,

543
00:42:54,260 --> 00:42:57,120
they left me naked and bleeding on the cobblestones.

544
00:42:57,120 --> 00:42:58,890
I am lucky to be alive.

545
00:42:58,900 --> 00:43:02,230
I heard this assault began in Littlefinger's brothel.

546
00:43:03,310 --> 00:43:06,070
High Septon, this is a rather shocking thing to hear.

547
00:43:06,070 --> 00:43:08,800
I tend to both the highest born and the lowliest amongst us.

548
00:43:08,800 --> 00:43:11,080
Even prostitutes may earn the mercy of the Mother.

549
00:43:11,080 --> 00:43:12,450
So you were administering

550
00:43:12,450 --> 00:43:14,980
to the needs of these devout prostitutes?

551
00:43:14,980 --> 00:43:17,860
A man's private affairs ought to stay private.

552
00:43:19,920 --> 00:43:21,570
What do you want from us, High Septon?

553
00:43:21,580 --> 00:43:22,760
Justice!

554
00:43:23,240 --> 00:43:26,160
I ask that you protect our Faith by arresting these criminals

555
00:43:26,160 --> 00:43:28,400
and throwing them in the black cells.

556
00:43:28,400 --> 00:43:30,410
I ask that you execute their leader,

557
00:43:30,410 --> 00:43:32,320
the so-called High Sparrow.

558
00:43:32,320 --> 00:43:34,570
He's a threat to everything we hold sacred.

559
00:43:34,580 --> 00:43:35,840
If he goes unpunished...

560
00:43:35,840 --> 00:43:37,340
And where do I find this man?

561
00:43:38,110 --> 00:43:39,470
This High Sparrow?

562
00:43:49,410 --> 00:43:51,470
I don't think this is a good idea, Your Grace.

563
00:43:51,470 --> 00:43:54,260
Nonsense, Ser Meryn. These are deeply religious people.

564
00:43:54,600 --> 00:43:56,590
Where can I find the High Sparrow?

565
00:43:59,110 --> 00:44:00,700
Seven blessings...

566
00:44:13,160 --> 00:44:14,000
Thank you.

567
00:44:14,090 --> 00:44:15,330
Just a little more.

568
00:44:18,830 --> 00:44:20,250
Thank you for the soup.

569
00:44:23,480 --> 00:44:25,930
The young man said I would find the High Sparrow back here.

570
00:44:25,930 --> 00:44:27,020
Where is he?

571
00:44:27,090 --> 00:44:28,540
High Sparrow?

572
00:44:28,930 --> 00:44:30,680
Sounds ridiculous, doesn't it?

573
00:44:30,680 --> 00:44:33,250
Like Lord Duckling, or King Turtle.

574
00:44:34,290 --> 00:44:35,680
Stll, it's meant to...

575
00:44:36,050 --> 00:44:39,030
We're often stuck with the names our enemies give to us.

576
00:44:39,260 --> 00:44:42,630
The notion that we are all equal in the eyes of the Seven

577
00:44:42,630 --> 00:44:45,890
doesn't sit well with some, so they belittle me.

578
00:44:45,960 --> 00:44:49,040
- Seven blessings to you. - Seven blessings to you, my dear.

579
00:44:50,360 --> 00:44:53,620
It's only a name. Quite an easy burden to bear.

580
00:44:53,980 --> 00:44:55,670
Far easier than hers.

581
00:44:58,940 --> 00:45:00,140
Why no shoes?

582
00:45:00,210 --> 00:45:03,250
Because I gave them away to someone who needed them more.

583
00:45:04,490 --> 00:45:05,840
We all do that.

584
00:45:05,980 --> 00:45:08,950
It stops us from forgetting what we really are.

585
00:45:09,470 --> 00:45:11,590
Is that why you came to King's Landing?

586
00:45:12,140 --> 00:45:13,480
To remind everyone?

587
00:45:13,480 --> 00:45:16,310
Everyone? Hard enough job reminding myself.

588
00:45:17,070 --> 00:45:19,120
Well, I tell them no one's special

589
00:45:19,120 --> 00:45:21,770
and they think I'm special for telling them so.

590
00:45:23,390 --> 00:45:24,750
Perhaps they're right.

591
00:45:25,800 --> 00:45:28,450
It would be comforting to believe that, wouldn't it?

592
00:45:29,690 --> 00:45:32,030
Have the Gods sent you here to tempt me?

593
00:45:33,540 --> 00:45:34,670
I hope not.

594
00:45:36,060 --> 00:45:37,300
I had assumed

595
00:45:38,260 --> 00:45:39,950
you'd only come here to arrest me

596
00:45:39,950 --> 00:45:42,650
for that incident with the High Septon.

597
00:45:42,650 --> 00:45:45,350
An unacceptable way to treat the chosen representative

598
00:45:45,350 --> 00:45:47,470
of the Gods in this world, wouldn't you say?

599
00:45:48,110 --> 00:45:50,110
Hypocrisy is a boil.

600
00:45:50,490 --> 00:45:53,060
Lancing a boil is never pleasant.

601
00:45:54,130 --> 00:45:57,040
Although, they could have been more careful with the blade.

602
00:45:58,060 --> 00:46:00,450
The High Septon came to speak to me today.

603
00:46:02,630 --> 00:46:05,440
He doesn't want me to arrest you. He wants me to execute you.

604
00:46:07,970 --> 00:46:10,580
I wouldn't presume to know your thoughts on the matter.

605
00:46:15,150 --> 00:46:17,400
My thoughts on the matter are in line with your own

606
00:46:17,800 --> 00:46:21,640
The High Septon's behaviour was corrosive, as was his attitude.

607
00:46:21,640 --> 00:46:23,470
Having a man like that reside in the Sept

608
00:46:23,470 --> 00:46:25,390
eats away at the Faith from the inside.

609
00:46:26,990 --> 00:46:29,980
So now he resides in the Red Keep's dungeons instead.

610
00:46:32,040 --> 00:46:33,160
The Faith and the Crown

611
00:46:33,160 --> 00:46:35,300
are the two pillars that hold up this world.

612
00:46:35,330 --> 00:46:37,390
If one collapses, so does the other.

613
00:46:39,110 --> 00:46:41,430
We must do everything necessary

614
00:46:41,700 --> 00:46:43,180
to protect one another.

615
00:47:02,020 --> 00:47:02,860
Your Grace.

616
00:47:02,860 --> 00:47:05,170
Send a raven with this message to Littlefinger

617
00:47:05,170 --> 00:47:07,780
at the Eyrie or wherever he's slithering about.

618
00:47:11,030 --> 00:47:12,530
At once, Your Grace.

619
00:47:13,800 --> 00:47:16,230
- How's your work coming along? - Very well.

620
00:47:16,670 --> 00:47:19,980
- You've made progress? - More than I've expected.

621
00:47:20,250 --> 00:47:21,970
Still a way to go, but...

622
00:47:22,060 --> 00:47:24,120
Very good. I'll leave you to it, then.

623
00:47:24,440 --> 00:47:26,130
Make sure Littlefinger is clear

624
00:47:26,130 --> 00:47:28,840
on the meaning of the word "immediately".

625
00:47:48,140 --> 00:47:49,570
Easy, friend.

626
00:47:52,000 --> 00:47:53,430
Come on, children.

627
00:48:13,430 --> 00:48:14,830
She really is lovely.

628
00:48:16,390 --> 00:48:18,040
I hope I can make her happy.

629
00:48:18,410 --> 00:48:19,500
I hope so too.

630
00:48:20,440 --> 00:48:23,670
I've become quite fond of Lady Sansa during our travels together.

631
00:48:24,380 --> 00:48:25,770
She suffered enough.

632
00:48:26,750 --> 00:48:28,140
I'll never hurt her.

633
00:48:28,650 --> 00:48:29,870
You have my word.

634
00:48:32,660 --> 00:48:34,150
I've heard very little about you,

635
00:48:35,300 --> 00:48:38,160
which makes you quite a rare thing, as lords go.

636
00:48:39,610 --> 00:48:41,420
I haven't been a lord very long.

637
00:48:42,260 --> 00:48:45,250
- I was a bastard. - And you're not anymore.

638
00:48:46,860 --> 00:48:49,210
Allow me a moment alone with Lord Baelish.

639
00:48:49,210 --> 00:48:52,250
Yes, father. And thank you, Lord Baelish.

640
00:48:52,840 --> 00:48:54,480
I'm forever in your debt.

641
00:49:00,770 --> 00:49:01,880
He seems pleased.

642
00:49:02,680 --> 00:49:03,840
Shouldn't he be?

643
00:49:05,330 --> 00:49:07,100
I assure you, she's still a virgin.

644
00:49:07,580 --> 00:49:09,190
Tyrion never consummated the marriage.

645
00:49:09,190 --> 00:49:11,630
By the law of the land, she is no man's wife.

646
00:49:13,030 --> 00:49:14,580
Inspect her, if you must.

647
00:49:14,580 --> 00:49:16,220
I've leave that to the brothel keeper.

648
00:49:16,220 --> 00:49:18,490
It's her name I need, not her virtue.

649
00:49:18,490 --> 00:49:20,580
Then I have delivered everything I've promised.

650
00:49:22,160 --> 00:49:24,180
And you prepared for the consequences.

651
00:49:24,550 --> 00:49:27,050
When the Lannisters hear I've wed Sansa Stark to Ramsay?

652
00:49:27,050 --> 00:49:29,770
The Lannister name doesn't mean what it once did.

653
00:49:29,770 --> 00:49:31,030
Tywin is dead.

654
00:49:31,350 --> 00:49:33,970
He kept his house in power through sheer will.

655
00:49:34,400 --> 00:49:35,450
Without him,

656
00:49:35,670 --> 00:49:37,940
Jaime has one hand and no allies,

657
00:49:38,120 --> 00:49:39,760
Tommen is a soft boy,

658
00:49:40,110 --> 00:49:41,610
not a king to fear.

659
00:49:42,490 --> 00:49:43,930
The Queen will be enraged.

660
00:49:44,020 --> 00:49:46,730
Queen Margaery adores Sansa.

661
00:49:47,190 --> 00:49:48,830
Cersei is Queen Mother,

662
00:49:49,140 --> 00:49:51,840
a title whose importance wanes with each passing day.

663
00:49:51,850 --> 00:49:53,320
And yet she still has friends,

664
00:49:53,760 --> 00:49:56,620
men in important places, whom she can ask for favours.

665
00:49:57,440 --> 00:50:00,250
A message for you, from Cersei Lannister.

666
00:50:01,180 --> 00:50:04,200
A rider arrived from Eyrie, shortly before dawn.

667
00:50:04,650 --> 00:50:06,760
Apparently, she thinks you're still in the Vale.

668
00:50:07,100 --> 00:50:09,270
A message for me, you say.

669
00:50:09,840 --> 00:50:11,560
Strange that the seal is broken.

670
00:50:11,560 --> 00:50:13,930
I'm sure you understand my position, Lord Baelish.

671
00:50:14,220 --> 00:50:16,640
If you received word in the night from the Queen Mother,

672
00:50:17,040 --> 00:50:19,060
it does make me question our new alliance.

673
00:50:20,600 --> 00:50:23,460
Lannisters made you one of the great lords of Westeros.

674
00:50:23,930 --> 00:50:26,230
Yet, here you are in the North, undermining them.

675
00:50:26,930 --> 00:50:28,750
Why gamble with your position?

676
00:50:30,320 --> 00:50:32,350
Every ambitious move is a gamble.

677
00:50:33,240 --> 00:50:36,090
You gambled when you drove a dagger into Robb Stark's heart.

678
00:50:38,610 --> 00:50:40,770
It appears that your gamble paid off.

679
00:50:40,810 --> 00:50:42,380
You're Warden of the North.

680
00:50:42,390 --> 00:50:44,190
I had Tywin Lannister's backing.

681
00:50:44,460 --> 00:50:46,750
Who supports me now? You?

682
00:50:47,340 --> 00:50:48,820
The Eyrie is mine.

683
00:50:49,690 --> 00:50:51,310
The last time the lords of the Eyrie

684
00:50:51,310 --> 00:50:53,520
formed an alliance with the lords of the North,

685
00:50:54,090 --> 00:50:57,020
they brought down the greatest dynasty this world has ever known.

686
00:51:00,900 --> 00:51:02,600
I'd like to borrow one of your birds.

687
00:51:03,070 --> 00:51:04,870
Cersei will expect a reply.

688
00:51:05,770 --> 00:51:07,510
I'd like to read the reply.

689
00:51:30,340 --> 00:51:32,050
I have to get out of this wheelhouse.

690
00:51:32,050 --> 00:51:33,910
Volantis is a large city.

691
00:51:34,190 --> 00:51:35,850
I have to get out of this wheelhouse.

692
00:51:35,850 --> 00:51:37,520
The likelihood of you being spotted here

693
00:51:37,520 --> 00:51:39,380
increases a hundred fold.

694
00:51:39,830 --> 00:51:41,640
I have to get out of this wheelhouse.

695
00:51:42,040 --> 00:51:44,800
I'm not sure how many new ways I can find of saying this.

696
00:51:47,760 --> 00:51:51,690
I will not be of any use to Daenerys Targaryen

697
00:51:51,690 --> 00:51:53,550
if I lose my mind.

698
00:51:53,820 --> 00:51:55,740
I can't remember the last face I saw

699
00:51:55,740 --> 00:51:57,380
that wasn't yours.

700
00:51:57,450 --> 00:51:58,980
It's a perfectly good face.

701
00:51:59,460 --> 00:52:00,750
I am losing my mind.

702
00:52:00,770 --> 00:52:02,690
If anyone recognizes you, you'll lose more than that.

703
00:52:02,690 --> 00:52:05,950
Look, we are thousands of miles from Westeros.

704
00:52:09,200 --> 00:52:10,290
What am I?

705
00:52:11,050 --> 00:52:12,810
One more drunk dwarf.

706
00:52:42,970 --> 00:52:44,600
We have to go now. Come on.

707
00:52:44,600 --> 00:52:45,930
Hold it, hold it!

708
00:52:49,970 --> 00:52:51,920
- Slaves. - Yes.

709
00:52:52,400 --> 00:52:55,090
The Volantene masters are very organized.

710
00:52:55,900 --> 00:52:57,830
Flies for dung shovelers.

711
00:52:58,920 --> 00:53:00,550
Hammers for builders.

712
00:53:01,340 --> 00:53:03,030
Tears for whores.

713
00:53:03,810 --> 00:53:05,320
Lest they forget.

716
00:53:19,250 --> 00:53:20,900
We should keep moving.

720
00:53:36,500 --> 00:53:39,690
The only red priest we had in King's Landing was Thoros of Myr.

721
00:53:40,250 --> 00:53:41,980
This one's much better looking.

725
00:53:49,680 --> 00:53:50,850
Stone Men.

726
00:53:51,610 --> 00:53:54,900
Good luck stopping the spread of grayscale with prayer.

727
00:53:55,180 --> 00:53:57,610
You'd have better luck dancing away the plague.

731
00:54:07,430 --> 00:54:09,530
We're going to meet the saviour.

732
00:54:09,620 --> 00:54:11,090
You should have told me.

733
00:54:11,110 --> 00:54:12,940
Who doesn't want to meet the saviour?

734
00:54:28,930 --> 00:54:30,020
Come on.

735
00:54:31,520 --> 00:54:32,790
Let's find a brothel.

737
00:54:57,020 --> 00:55:00,010
It's even better luck to suck a dwarf's cock.

738
00:55:04,140 --> 00:55:06,660
See? We blend right in.

739
00:55:07,360 --> 00:55:10,840
Just two more travellers mad with lust.

740
00:55:15,670 --> 00:55:16,610
Thank you.

741
00:55:25,940 --> 00:55:28,360
What curious hair.

742
00:55:29,830 --> 00:55:31,430
The Mother of Dragons.

743
00:55:34,260 --> 00:55:37,200
It appears you're not the only Targaryen supporter.

744
00:55:38,200 --> 00:55:39,700
We were just heading east to see you.

745
00:55:40,000 --> 00:55:41,200
I've got a dragon for you.

746
00:55:41,900 --> 00:55:43,600
How much to make him spit fire?

747
00:55:47,910 --> 00:55:52,530
Someone who inspires priests and whores is worth taking seriously.

748
00:55:52,530 --> 00:55:53,990
What makes you worth so much?

749
00:55:53,990 --> 00:55:56,360
- The magic. - I'll bet you bloody are.

750
00:55:59,300 --> 00:56:01,920
Well, she's taken.

751
00:56:04,070 --> 00:56:05,140
Where are you going?

752
00:56:05,140 --> 00:56:07,110
I need to speak to someone with hair.

753
00:56:09,750 --> 00:56:11,170
- Hello? - Hello.

754
00:56:11,840 --> 00:56:14,010
- You've got no drink. - You've got no money.

755
00:56:14,460 --> 00:56:16,420
Do I look like a man without money?

756
00:56:18,230 --> 00:56:19,810
Never trust looks.

757
00:56:20,040 --> 00:56:23,150
Until quite recently, I was one of the richest men in the world.

758
00:56:25,310 --> 00:56:28,050
Who needs wealth when you can make a woman laugh?

759
00:56:30,480 --> 00:56:34,480
I always pay my debts, I'm well known for it.

760
00:56:39,150 --> 00:56:40,310
You like her?

761
00:56:41,650 --> 00:56:42,940
They all like her.

762
00:56:43,400 --> 00:56:45,140
They all want to fuck a queen.

763
00:56:45,290 --> 00:56:47,980
- That's because they never met a queen. - You're just saying that.

764
00:56:48,040 --> 00:56:49,730
You know how to spot a liar.

765
00:56:50,610 --> 00:56:52,330
If I could pick any girl here,

766
00:56:53,180 --> 00:56:54,290
I would pick you.

767
00:56:55,690 --> 00:56:56,660
Why?

768
00:56:57,600 --> 00:56:59,360
Because you have a skeptical mind.

769
00:57:04,540 --> 00:57:06,080
Alright, then. I'm warning you.

770
00:57:06,080 --> 00:57:07,660
We're going to have to wash you first.

771
00:57:08,800 --> 00:57:09,610
Come on.

772
00:57:17,770 --> 00:57:20,340
I'm-I'm sorry, I can't.

773
00:57:22,010 --> 00:57:23,290
Of course you can.

774
00:57:23,960 --> 00:57:25,020
You're shy.

775
00:57:25,680 --> 00:57:26,630
I'm not.

776
00:57:28,520 --> 00:57:29,730
Have another drink.

777
00:57:29,850 --> 00:57:32,400
Gladly, but this, I can't do.

778
00:57:32,830 --> 00:57:35,210
Believe me, no one is more shocked than I am.

779
00:57:35,840 --> 00:57:37,600
I hope it passes.

780
00:57:38,520 --> 00:57:40,500
What will I do in my spare time?

781
00:57:43,920 --> 00:57:46,740
Go for a piss. That's a start.

782
00:58:05,240 --> 00:58:08,610
No need to worry, I was just... Oh...

783
00:58:09,650 --> 00:58:11,300
I thought you were someone else.

784
00:58:12,220 --> 00:58:13,800
Show's almost over.

785
00:58:14,170 --> 00:58:17,240
I'm sure there girls inside who'd be happy to oblige.

786
00:58:18,710 --> 00:58:19,750
You've made some kind of mistake.

787
00:58:19,750 --> 00:58:21,740
Why don't you tell me what you think you are doing and then

788
00:58:24,440 --> 00:58:26,220
I'm taking you to the Queen.

