28
00:00:02,670 --> 00:00:04,480
Did you kill Joffrey?

29
00:00:04,830 --> 00:00:07,830
Well, that was something my new friends wanted very badly.

30
00:00:07,830 --> 00:00:10,530
You don't think I'd let you marry that beast, do you?

31
00:00:10,530 --> 00:00:14,030
We engaged in intimate relations.

32
00:00:14,030 --> 00:00:16,430
Queen Margaery, walked in on us once.

33
00:00:16,430 --> 00:00:19,000
There is enough evidence to bring a formal trial

34
00:00:19,000 --> 00:00:21,310
for Ser Loras and Queen Margaery.

35
00:00:21,310 --> 00:00:22,490
Take her.

36
00:00:22,490 --> 00:00:23,880
Lancel Lannister.

37
00:00:23,880 --> 00:00:25,190
Brother Lancel.

38
00:00:25,190 --> 00:00:26,630
We abandon our family names.

39
00:00:26,630 --> 00:00:28,270
Quite a family to abandon.

40
00:00:29,090 --> 00:00:31,640
To forge a lasting bond with the people,

41
00:00:31,640 --> 00:00:33,870
I will marry the leader of an ancient family,

42
00:00:33,870 --> 00:00:35,680
and reopen the fighting pits.

43
00:00:36,380 --> 00:00:37,820
That's a slave ship.

44
00:00:38,520 --> 00:00:41,600
Take me to Slaver's Bay, put a sword in my hand,

45
00:00:41,600 --> 00:00:43,260
I'll prove my worth.

46
00:00:43,450 --> 00:00:45,200
I want you to be my wife.

47
00:00:45,210 --> 00:00:46,870
We have to go, Myrcella, now.

48
00:00:51,500 --> 00:00:52,960
Drop your weapons.

49
00:00:56,250 --> 00:00:57,790
We're going to have a baby.

50
00:00:57,790 --> 00:01:00,350
From the way she's carrying, it looks like a boy.

51
00:01:00,910 --> 00:01:02,980
Maybe Lday Sansa's better off here.

52
00:01:02,980 --> 00:01:05,570
Sansa's in danger even if she doesn't realize it.

53
00:01:05,570 --> 00:01:06,920
If you're ever in trouble,

54
00:01:06,920 --> 00:01:10,300
light a candle in the highest window of the broken tower.

55
00:01:12,240 --> 00:01:13,740
Will you take this man?

56
00:01:14,140 --> 00:01:15,580
I take this man.

57
00:01:15,580 --> 00:01:17,840
You've known Sansa since she was a girl.

58
00:01:17,840 --> 00:01:19,510
Now watch her become a woman.

59
00:01:21,760 --> 00:01:24,550
I shall take back the North from the thieves who stole it.

60
00:01:24,550 --> 00:01:27,620
I shall mount Roose Bolton's head on a spike.

61
00:01:27,620 --> 00:01:29,900
- Tthe queen and the princess. - They're coming with us.

62
00:01:29,910 --> 00:01:31,590
We march at sunrise.

63
00:01:31,710 --> 00:01:33,060
I'd have you go north of the Wall.

64
00:01:33,060 --> 00:01:35,790
Gather the remaining free folk wherever they are

65
00:01:35,790 --> 00:01:37,060
and bring them back here.

66
00:01:37,070 --> 00:01:39,000
I'll open the gates for them and let them through.

67
00:01:39,000 --> 00:01:41,570
Make peace to save your people.

68
00:01:41,570 --> 00:01:43,210
You're coming with me.

69
00:04:44,000 --> 00:04:46,160
First ranger, you have command of Castle Black.

70
00:04:46,160 --> 00:04:48,610
Lord Commander, it is my duty to tell you

71
00:04:48,610 --> 00:04:52,000
I believe this mission to be reckless, foolhardy,

72
00:04:52,000 --> 00:04:53,860
and an insult to all the brothers

73
00:04:53,860 --> 00:04:56,340
who have died fighting the wildlings.

74
00:04:57,110 --> 00:04:59,260
As always, thank you for your honesty.

75
00:05:06,500 --> 00:05:08,380
Safe travels, Lord Commander.

76
00:05:09,290 --> 00:05:10,570
Thank you, Sam.

77
00:05:17,980 --> 00:05:19,410
It's dragonglass.

78
00:05:19,510 --> 00:05:21,600
It's what I used to kill the white walker.

79
00:05:27,330 --> 00:05:29,270
I hope you don't need them.

80
00:05:30,020 --> 00:05:31,210
Me, too.

81
00:06:05,170 --> 00:06:06,650
There he is.

82
00:06:10,570 --> 00:06:11,970
That laugh.

83
00:06:12,960 --> 00:06:14,160
Egg.

84
00:06:14,960 --> 00:06:17,110
Egg laughed like that.

85
00:06:17,740 --> 00:06:20,710
One of the first things I remember.

86
00:06:23,850 --> 00:06:28,070
His little brother Aegon. He became king.

87
00:06:29,350 --> 00:06:33,920
And before that, he was a jolly fellow,

88
00:06:33,960 --> 00:06:35,510
like this one.

89
00:06:40,470 --> 00:06:44,180
Get him south, gillyflower.

90
00:06:45,650 --> 00:06:48,250
Before it's too late.

91
00:07:39,150 --> 00:07:40,450
Theon, wait.

92
00:07:40,450 --> 00:07:42,860
Not Theon, my lady. Reek.

93
00:07:43,060 --> 00:07:44,180
Help me.

94
00:07:46,850 --> 00:07:48,340
You're his wife now.

95
00:07:49,430 --> 00:07:50,550
Theon.

96
00:07:50,820 --> 00:07:52,130
Do what he says.

97
00:07:52,230 --> 00:07:54,010
Do what he says or he'll hurt you.

98
00:07:54,010 --> 00:07:56,060
He already hurts me every night.

99
00:07:56,830 --> 00:07:58,090
All day I'm locked in this room

100
00:07:58,090 --> 00:07:59,860
And every night he comes...

101
00:08:02,840 --> 00:08:04,220
It can't be any worse.

102
00:08:04,220 --> 00:08:08,250
It can. It can always be worse.

103
00:08:17,300 --> 00:08:19,180
- What did he do to you? - Please.

104
00:08:19,180 --> 00:08:21,760
- You betrayed my family! - I'm sorry! I'm sorry!

105
00:08:21,830 --> 00:08:24,260
You have to help me. Theon, help me.

106
00:08:24,260 --> 00:08:26,310
He'll see us. You don't know him.

107
00:08:27,240 --> 00:08:29,200
My family still has friends in The North.

108
00:08:29,200 --> 00:08:31,960
All I need to do is give a signal and they'll rescue me.

109
00:08:32,440 --> 00:08:34,500
Climb to the top of the broken tower.

110
00:08:34,880 --> 00:08:36,980
Light this candle and put it in the window.

111
00:08:36,980 --> 00:08:39,860
- Promise me, Theon. - Reek! My name is Reek.

112
00:08:42,480 --> 00:08:45,210
Your name is Theon Greyjoy.

113
00:08:46,600 --> 00:08:49,030
Last surviving son of Balon Greyjoy,

114
00:08:49,030 --> 00:08:50,460
Lord of the Iron Islands.

115
00:08:50,460 --> 00:08:51,730
Do you hear me?

116
00:08:54,900 --> 00:08:55,940
Theon...

117
00:08:58,460 --> 00:08:59,680
Promise me.

118
00:10:03,080 --> 00:10:04,610
Yes, Reek?

119
00:10:20,530 --> 00:10:21,680
Egg.

120
00:10:23,190 --> 00:10:24,540
Egg.

121
00:10:27,300 --> 00:10:29,500
Mother's looking for you.

122
00:10:31,130 --> 00:10:32,450
Egg.

123
00:10:34,910 --> 00:10:36,750
Get some sleep, Sam.

124
00:10:37,850 --> 00:10:40,080
You'll have to speak for him tomorrow.

125
00:10:41,800 --> 00:10:43,420
You don't know that.

126
00:10:43,420 --> 00:10:44,810
Get some sleep.

127
00:10:45,960 --> 00:10:47,620
I'll watch over him.

128
00:10:50,690 --> 00:10:52,230
I'm staying, too.

129
00:10:53,310 --> 00:10:55,160
He's always been good to me.

130
00:10:55,550 --> 00:10:57,140
I can't leave him now.

131
00:10:58,230 --> 00:10:59,260
Egg!

132
00:11:11,690 --> 00:11:12,720
Egg.

133
00:11:15,100 --> 00:11:16,810
I dreamed...

134
00:11:17,890 --> 00:11:19,710
that I was old.

135
00:11:30,960 --> 00:11:33,350
His name was Aemon Targaryen.

136
00:11:34,350 --> 00:11:36,530
He came to us from King's Landing.

137
00:11:38,820 --> 00:11:41,740
A maester of the citadel, chained and sworn,

138
00:11:42,070 --> 00:11:45,050
and sworn brother of the night's watch, ever faithful.

139
00:11:46,750 --> 00:11:48,410
No man was wiser

140
00:11:48,920 --> 00:11:52,320
or gentler or kinder.

141
00:11:53,740 --> 00:11:56,830
At the wall, a dozen Lord Commanders

142
00:11:56,830 --> 00:11:59,230
came and went during his years of service,

143
00:11:59,230 --> 00:12:01,430
but he was always there to counsel them.

144
00:12:04,640 --> 00:12:06,200
He was the blood of the dragon...

145
00:12:08,470 --> 00:12:10,340
But now his fire has gone out.

146
00:12:13,310 --> 00:12:15,040
And now his watch is ended.

147
00:12:15,440 --> 00:12:17,870
And now his watch is ended.

148
00:12:46,330 --> 00:12:48,590
You're losing all your friends, Tarly.

149
00:13:26,320 --> 00:13:28,000
My beautiful wife.

150
00:13:34,080 --> 00:13:35,840
When my father told me we were marrying,

151
00:13:35,840 --> 00:13:39,080
I half expected a fat, bearded beast.

152
00:13:43,710 --> 00:13:46,660
Do you know how pleased I was when I saw you?

153
00:13:46,920 --> 00:13:48,720
You've made me very happy.

154
00:13:53,680 --> 00:13:57,120
Our scouts report that Stannis Baratheon rides for Winterfell.

155
00:13:57,190 --> 00:13:58,880
He's a respected commander.

156
00:14:00,020 --> 00:14:03,660
His troops are loyal and battle-tested.

157
00:14:03,670 --> 00:14:07,170
He's hired thousands of foreign sellswords to bolster his army.

158
00:14:07,570 --> 00:14:10,640
But this storm is a stroke of luck for us northerners.

159
00:14:12,310 --> 00:14:15,080
Our people are used to fighting in the frost.

160
00:14:16,860 --> 00:14:19,950
His army is out there now suffering in the snow.

161
00:14:21,780 --> 00:14:23,680
One day I'll be Lord of Wnterfell

162
00:14:23,680 --> 00:14:25,370
and warden of the North.

163
00:14:25,960 --> 00:14:28,460
You'll be my lady and Wardeness.

164
00:14:31,400 --> 00:14:33,840
But isn't your stepmother pregnant?

165
00:14:33,980 --> 00:14:35,310
What of it?

166
00:14:36,440 --> 00:14:38,380
What happens if she has a boy?

167
00:14:39,880 --> 00:14:41,700
Then I'll have a baby brother.

168
00:14:41,820 --> 00:14:43,370
But he'll be the heir.

169
00:14:43,380 --> 00:14:45,530
I'm Lord Bolton's eldest son.

170
00:14:46,130 --> 00:14:47,570
But you're a bastard.

171
00:14:47,570 --> 00:14:50,170
A trueborn will always have the stronger claim.

172
00:14:53,100 --> 00:14:55,700
I've been naturalized by a royal decree from...

173
00:14:55,700 --> 00:14:59,180
Tommen baratheon? Another Bastard.

174
00:15:05,720 --> 00:15:07,980
Bastards can rise high in the world.

175
00:15:09,020 --> 00:15:11,910
Like your half-brother Jon Snow.

176
00:15:13,060 --> 00:15:14,780
Born the bastard of Winterfell,

177
00:15:16,070 --> 00:15:18,870
now the Lord Commander of the Night's Watch.

178
00:15:21,200 --> 00:15:22,290
You didn't know?

179
00:15:23,230 --> 00:15:25,730
Yes, he's done very well for himself.

180
00:15:28,110 --> 00:15:30,390
I nearly forgot why I asked you to join me.

181
00:15:30,940 --> 00:15:32,180
Come, my lady.

182
00:15:43,650 --> 00:15:45,500
Your northern friend.

183
00:15:48,680 --> 00:15:50,520
Reek told me you wanted to leave.

184
00:15:51,760 --> 00:15:52,740
Why?

185
00:15:53,280 --> 00:15:54,570
Winterfell is your home

186
00:15:54,670 --> 00:15:56,230
and I am your husband.

187
00:15:57,340 --> 00:15:58,790
Tough old bird.

188
00:15:59,330 --> 00:16:01,880
Everyone talks when I start peeling them.

189
00:16:02,030 --> 00:16:03,320
But this one,

190
00:16:04,030 --> 00:16:06,950
her heart gave out before I even got to her face.

191
00:16:09,590 --> 00:16:12,230
We do breed them tough in the North.

192
00:16:18,230 --> 00:16:20,200
Bring my wife back to her chamber.

193
00:16:20,990 --> 00:16:23,310
It's far too cold out here for a lady.

194
00:16:24,100 --> 00:16:26,300
You should hold on to your candles.

195
00:16:26,910 --> 00:16:29,560
The nights are so long now.

196
00:17:19,170 --> 00:17:21,320
40 horses died in the night.

197
00:17:22,560 --> 00:17:24,460
We'll lose more come sunset.

198
00:17:24,680 --> 00:17:25,960
We're running out of food.

199
00:17:25,960 --> 00:17:28,570
We can't open the supply line until the snow clears.

200
00:17:34,270 --> 00:17:35,300
What else?

201
00:17:35,630 --> 00:17:37,990
The Stormcrows rode off last night.

202
00:17:41,590 --> 00:17:42,800
500 men.

203
00:17:46,420 --> 00:17:47,790
Sellswords.

204
00:17:49,010 --> 00:17:50,870
Loyal to nothing but gold.

205
00:17:54,870 --> 00:17:56,920
We still have a hard march to Winterfell

206
00:17:56,920 --> 00:17:59,110
and we won't be marching anywhere in this weather.

207
00:17:59,740 --> 00:18:00,360
And?

208
00:18:00,520 --> 00:18:02,260
This isn't our time.

209
00:18:02,710 --> 00:18:05,660
We should head back to Castle Black when the snow clears.

210
00:18:05,660 --> 00:18:08,060
I retreated from King's Landing, Ser Davos.

211
00:18:08,060 --> 00:18:11,660
If I retreat again, I'll become the king who ran.

212
00:18:11,660 --> 00:18:13,590
- Your grace... - Winter is coming.

213
00:18:13,840 --> 00:18:16,740
Those aren't just the Stark words. It's a fact.

214
00:18:16,890 --> 00:18:19,420
If we march back to Castle Black,

215
00:18:19,940 --> 00:18:21,780
we winter at Castle Black.

216
00:18:21,850 --> 00:18:25,850
And who can say how many years this winter will last?

217
00:18:25,860 --> 00:18:27,970
It's better to wait for the right time than risk everything.

218
00:18:27,980 --> 00:18:30,290
This is the right time and I will risk everything.

219
00:18:30,290 --> 00:18:32,940
Because if I don't, we've lost.

220
00:18:33,560 --> 00:18:35,380
We march to victory

221
00:18:35,590 --> 00:18:39,250
or we march to defeat.

222
00:18:39,660 --> 00:18:42,050
But we go forward. Only forward.

223
00:18:52,310 --> 00:18:53,680
Your grace.

224
00:18:58,900 --> 00:19:00,690
I've trusted in your visions

225
00:19:01,340 --> 00:19:04,380
and your prophecies for years.

226
00:19:04,390 --> 00:19:06,210
You saw it yourself, my king,

227
00:19:06,910 --> 00:19:08,670
when you stared into the flames.

228
00:19:08,800 --> 00:19:10,560
A great battle in the snow.

229
00:19:10,560 --> 00:19:12,640
- I don't know what I saw. - You do know.

230
00:19:12,830 --> 00:19:14,170
Trust yourself.

231
00:19:14,250 --> 00:19:16,230
And you? Do you trust yourself?

232
00:19:16,940 --> 00:19:18,400
I trust in the Lord.

233
00:19:20,820 --> 00:19:22,510
Are you sure?

234
00:19:28,850 --> 00:19:32,340
I have seen myself walk along the battlements of Winterfell.

235
00:19:32,790 --> 00:19:37,060
I have seen the flayed man banners lowered to the ground.

236
00:19:45,950 --> 00:19:49,430
But sometimes sacrifices must be made to ensure victory.

237
00:19:51,600 --> 00:19:54,010
I have shown you the power of king's blood.

238
00:19:54,940 --> 00:19:56,900
The usurper Robb Stark.

239
00:19:56,930 --> 00:19:58,860
The usurper Joffrey Baratheon.

240
00:19:58,860 --> 00:20:01,150
We don't have Robert's bastard here.

241
00:20:01,170 --> 00:20:04,190
No, we have someone better.

242
00:20:06,120 --> 00:20:08,560
And your blood runs through her veins.

243
00:20:10,570 --> 00:20:12,270
Have you lost your mind?

244
00:20:12,300 --> 00:20:13,580
Do you doubt me?

245
00:20:14,100 --> 00:20:15,340
Still?

246
00:20:16,590 --> 00:20:18,390
After all that you've seen.

247
00:20:18,590 --> 00:20:19,810
There must be another way.

248
00:20:19,990 --> 00:20:22,520
- Leeches or... - There is only one way.

249
00:20:22,980 --> 00:20:26,240
You must become king before the long night begins.

250
00:20:26,240 --> 00:20:28,730
Only you can lead the living against the dead.

251
00:20:28,760 --> 00:20:31,730
All your life has led us to this moment.

252
00:20:32,150 --> 00:20:34,230
- To this decision. - She's my daughter.

253
00:20:37,030 --> 00:20:38,270
Get out.

254
00:21:00,860 --> 00:21:02,670
There's always some sort to grub on.

255
00:21:02,670 --> 00:21:04,330
A bit of mutton would be nice.

256
00:21:08,060 --> 00:21:09,660
A beauty from beyond the wall.

257
00:21:12,340 --> 00:21:15,180
Where you going, love? Aren't we better-looking than the fat man?

258
00:21:15,180 --> 00:21:17,920
No, the question is is she pretty down south in the real world

259
00:21:17,920 --> 00:21:20,160
or is she pretty 'cause she's the only girl here?

260
00:21:20,170 --> 00:21:22,250
Even in White Harbor, I'd want a kiss.

261
00:21:23,150 --> 00:21:25,070
Come on, love, give us a kiss.

262
00:21:25,070 --> 00:21:26,710
- Leave me alone. - Oh, if you were my girl,

263
00:21:26,710 --> 00:21:27,850
I wouldn't leave you alone.

264
00:21:27,850 --> 00:21:29,860
- One little kiss. - Come on, give him a kiss.

265
00:21:29,860 --> 00:21:31,460
A man gets lonely guarding the wall.

266
00:21:36,590 --> 00:21:37,980
There's no need to be rude.

267
00:21:38,170 --> 00:21:40,080
We just want a little affection.

268
00:21:44,060 --> 00:21:45,340
Get your hands off her.

269
00:21:46,060 --> 00:21:48,940
Brother Derek, Brother Brant,

270
00:21:48,940 --> 00:21:50,900
I believe you both have guard duty tonight.

271
00:21:50,900 --> 00:21:52,060
Sam the slayer.

272
00:21:52,430 --> 00:21:53,980
You gonna slay me with that sword?

273
00:21:53,980 --> 00:21:55,020
Look at his hand shake.

274
00:21:55,400 --> 00:21:57,530
Gilly, go on.

275
00:21:57,820 --> 00:21:59,830
Get back to your room, lock the door.

276
00:22:03,020 --> 00:22:05,930
- I'm warning you. - Come on. Come on.

277
00:22:10,090 --> 00:22:10,950
Sam!

278
00:22:11,960 --> 00:22:14,190
You lying sack of shit.

279
00:22:14,600 --> 00:22:16,130
Killed a white walker, eh?

280
00:22:16,200 --> 00:22:17,980
You fat-ass fuck.

281
00:22:18,980 --> 00:22:19,960
Come on, get up.

282
00:22:20,520 --> 00:22:23,450
- No! - This your hero? This hog?

283
00:22:23,850 --> 00:22:25,250
Leave him alone!

284
00:22:26,320 --> 00:22:28,810
Stubborn little wildling bitch, aren't you?

285
00:22:30,750 --> 00:22:32,240
- Come on! - No!

286
00:22:32,910 --> 00:22:36,190
- Sam! Sam! Sam! - Come on!

287
00:22:44,910 --> 00:22:47,000
- Sam! Sam! - Come on.

288
00:22:47,000 --> 00:22:47,980
Right.

289
00:22:49,280 --> 00:22:50,970
I'll deal with this.

290
00:22:53,610 --> 00:22:55,010
- Turn her over. - All right.

291
00:22:58,190 --> 00:23:00,920
I said get your hands off her.

292
00:23:00,950 --> 00:23:02,450
You're gonna get yourself killed.

293
00:23:02,450 --> 00:23:05,140
Your lover Jon Snow's not here to save you.

294
00:23:05,140 --> 00:23:07,650
I killed a white walker, I killed a Thenn.

295
00:23:08,570 --> 00:23:10,200
I'll take my chances with you.

296
00:23:27,210 --> 00:23:28,140
Sam!

297
00:23:30,680 --> 00:23:32,740
- I'm all right. - You're not.

298
00:23:33,300 --> 00:23:34,780
Just a bit woozy.

299
00:23:59,980 --> 00:24:02,740
The next time you see something like that, you leave it alone.

300
00:24:02,740 --> 00:24:05,300
I will not. They would have--

301
00:24:08,740 --> 00:24:10,240
I don't know what they would have done.

302
00:24:10,780 --> 00:24:13,390
I know they would have killed you if Ghost hadn't come.

303
00:24:13,390 --> 00:24:16,360
No. No, no. They were tiring out.

304
00:24:17,060 --> 00:24:19,270
I had them in the palm of my hand.

305
00:24:20,140 --> 00:24:22,320
Don't be stupid, Sam.

306
00:24:22,720 --> 00:24:24,330
You're not a fighter.

307
00:24:25,440 --> 00:24:27,290
What kind of man would I be if I ran away 

308
00:24:27,290 --> 00:24:29,550
when I saw someone hurting you?

309
00:24:29,580 --> 00:24:31,630
Just promise me

310
00:24:32,210 --> 00:24:35,300
whatever happens, you'll take care of little Sam.

311
00:24:35,310 --> 00:24:36,980
But of course I will.

312
00:24:37,700 --> 00:24:38,650
And...

313
00:24:40,010 --> 00:24:41,790
I'll take care of you, too.

314
00:24:48,500 --> 00:24:49,960
I need more water.

315
00:24:53,840 --> 00:24:54,920
Stay.

316
00:24:56,320 --> 00:24:57,480
Please?

317
00:25:58,010 --> 00:25:59,240
Am I hurting you?

318
00:26:04,010 --> 00:26:05,450
Are you sure?

319
00:26:35,430 --> 00:26:36,730
Oh, my!

320
00:26:53,980 --> 00:26:56,860
A rare find for the fighting pits, my friends.

321
00:26:57,380 --> 00:27:00,770
Not your usual street tough or drunken pirate.

322
00:27:01,350 --> 00:27:04,360
This one's a Westerosi knight

323
00:27:04,360 --> 00:27:08,380
from an ancient house trained in sword and lance.

324
00:27:08,620 --> 00:27:11,120
He fought beside the Stag King Robert

325
00:27:11,120 --> 00:27:13,170
on the far side of the narrow sea.

326
00:27:13,410 --> 00:27:16,370
He was first through the breach during the siege of Spike,

327
00:27:16,580 --> 00:27:19,740
slaughtering 50 men with his flaming sword.

328
00:27:20,280 --> 00:27:24,300
He killed the great Khal Drogo in single combat.

329
00:27:24,570 --> 00:27:26,360
Betrayed by his woman,

330
00:27:26,360 --> 00:27:29,870
he sold himself into slavery to repay his debts.

331
00:27:29,890 --> 00:27:33,280
Bidding begins at 12 gold honors.

332
00:27:34,050 --> 00:27:37,180
13. Do I have 14?

333
00:27:37,950 --> 00:27:41,850
15? 15 gold honors.

334
00:27:41,850 --> 00:27:44,870
Do I hear 16? 16?

335
00:27:44,870 --> 00:27:46,020
20.

336
00:27:46,630 --> 00:27:47,680
Sold.

337
00:27:57,700 --> 00:28:00,500
Wait! You have to buy me as well.

338
00:28:01,320 --> 00:28:02,220
Why?

339
00:28:02,880 --> 00:28:04,000
We're a team.

340
00:28:04,500 --> 00:28:06,000
I'm a great fighter, too.

341
00:28:09,900 --> 00:28:12,150
He's funny. You have to give him that.

342
00:28:22,910 --> 00:28:25,670
Stop! Stop!

343
00:28:39,470 --> 00:28:42,060
You're right, he's funny.

344
00:28:49,250 --> 00:28:51,100
Thank you, my lord. Thank you.

345
00:28:51,100 --> 00:28:52,000
Yes.

346
00:28:52,610 --> 00:28:54,460
My lord, if I may.

347
00:28:54,620 --> 00:28:56,930
I've heard Meereen has become a free city.

348
00:28:56,930 --> 00:28:57,870
You might run into trouble

349
00:28:57,870 --> 00:28:59,890
if you try to fight slaves in the fighting pits.

350
00:28:59,890 --> 00:29:02,300
Now, if you were to fight freed men who'd be paid a wage--

351
00:29:05,560 --> 00:29:07,340
There's your wages, funny man.

352
00:29:07,720 --> 00:29:09,460
Should last the rest of your life.

353
00:29:11,430 --> 00:29:14,340
These are warrior hands, not a serving girl's.

354
00:29:14,700 --> 00:29:16,280
5, going once...

355
00:29:20,580 --> 00:29:23,970
How long before the king of Meereen comes to claim my pillow?

356
00:29:24,040 --> 00:29:25,460
Don't be ridiculous.

357
00:29:25,990 --> 00:29:29,220
My marriage to Hizdahr is political.

358
00:29:29,830 --> 00:29:32,270
I think he's smart enough to understand that.

359
00:29:33,690 --> 00:29:35,770
I think the sons of the Harpy have stopped killing

360
00:29:35,770 --> 00:29:37,860
because their leader was made king.

361
00:29:41,070 --> 00:29:42,740
Are you jealous?

362
00:29:43,730 --> 00:29:45,830
You think I'm petty enough to speak ill of a man

363
00:29:45,830 --> 00:29:47,910
just because he represents competition?

364
00:29:49,120 --> 00:29:50,150
I do.

365
00:29:52,510 --> 00:29:53,540
You're right.

366
00:29:53,900 --> 00:29:56,860
My motivations are entirely impure.

367
00:30:05,390 --> 00:30:06,800
Doesn't make me wrong.

368
00:30:11,700 --> 00:30:15,960
You told me yourself I can't fight enemies within and without.

369
00:30:15,960 --> 00:30:18,220
So when enemies without come knocking,

370
00:30:18,510 --> 00:30:20,700
I need the city of Meereen behind me.

371
00:30:20,700 --> 00:30:22,010
I have no choice.

372
00:30:23,070 --> 00:30:24,570
Everyone has a choice.

373
00:30:24,720 --> 00:30:26,460
Even slaves have a choice...

374
00:30:26,460 --> 00:30:27,980
death or slavery.

375
00:30:28,710 --> 00:30:31,020
So what else can I do, hmm?

376
00:30:32,530 --> 00:30:33,950
Marry me instead.

377
00:30:36,470 --> 00:30:40,320
Even if I wanted to do such an inadvisable thing,

378
00:30:41,770 --> 00:30:42,840
I couldn't.

379
00:30:42,960 --> 00:30:43,970
Why not?

380
00:30:44,230 --> 00:30:46,450
You are queen. You can do what you like.

381
00:30:48,510 --> 00:30:51,880
No, I can't.

382
00:30:52,030 --> 00:30:54,870
Then you are the only person in Meereen who's not free.

383
00:31:06,610 --> 00:31:08,500
And I know I'm here to serve my queen

384
00:31:08,570 --> 00:31:09,950
and not give advice,

385
00:31:10,950 --> 00:31:12,820
but can I make one more suggestion?

386
00:31:16,930 --> 00:31:18,160
Of course.

387
00:31:21,810 --> 00:31:23,620
On the day of the great games,

388
00:31:24,370 --> 00:31:27,000
gather all the great masters and wise masters

389
00:31:27,010 --> 00:31:29,060
and worthy masters you can find

390
00:31:30,520 --> 00:31:32,110
and slaughter them all.

391
00:31:35,550 --> 00:31:39,170
I am a queen, not a butcher.

392
00:31:43,860 --> 00:31:46,660
All rulers are either butchers or meat.

393
00:31:55,760 --> 00:31:59,120
You there. Where would I find the High Septon

394
00:31:59,120 --> 00:32:03,070
or High Sparrow or whatever bloody fool name he's got?

395
00:32:03,190 --> 00:32:06,770
It's not as good a name as Queen of Thorns, I'll admit.

396
00:32:07,850 --> 00:32:10,020
You should have the decency

397
00:32:10,050 --> 00:32:12,340
to stand when you speak to a lady.

398
00:32:12,410 --> 00:32:15,160
You should have the decency to kneel before the gods.

399
00:32:15,170 --> 00:32:17,000
Don't spar with me, little fellow.

400
00:32:20,000 --> 00:32:22,600
For me, it's the knees.

401
00:32:22,980 --> 00:32:25,100
- You? - Hips.

402
00:32:26,850 --> 00:32:30,370
A man of the people. Is that your game?

403
00:32:30,910 --> 00:32:34,650
It's an old game. Dull and unconvincing.

404
00:32:34,720 --> 00:32:36,150
A man of the people

405
00:32:36,660 --> 00:32:39,720
who does Cersei's dirty work for her.

406
00:32:40,600 --> 00:32:42,490
The people always do the dirty work.

407
00:32:42,490 --> 00:32:43,600
Spare me the homilies.

408
00:32:43,680 --> 00:32:46,000
I can smell a fraud from a mile away.

409
00:32:46,000 --> 00:32:47,110
Useful talent.

410
00:32:47,110 --> 00:32:50,180
I'm here for my grandson and granddaughter.

411
00:32:50,180 --> 00:32:52,300
Your grandson and granddaughter

412
00:32:52,310 --> 00:32:55,090
swore sacred vows and lied.

413
00:32:55,830 --> 00:32:58,270
The Father judges us all.

414
00:32:58,520 --> 00:33:00,370
Sons of high lords,

415
00:33:00,880 --> 00:33:02,320
Sons of fishermen.

416
00:33:02,820 --> 00:33:06,090
If you break his laws, you will be punished.

417
00:33:07,170 --> 00:33:08,760
Don't you walk away from me.

418
00:33:08,770 --> 00:33:10,950
You don't give commands here, Lady Olenna.

419
00:33:10,960 --> 00:33:12,350
What is it you want?

420
00:33:13,090 --> 00:33:14,140
Gold?

421
00:33:14,700 --> 00:33:17,560
I'll make you the richest septon who ever lived.

422
00:33:19,030 --> 00:33:20,230
What, then?

423
00:33:21,570 --> 00:33:23,650
I imagine this is strange for you.

424
00:33:24,530 --> 00:33:26,780
Everyone you meet has a hidden motive

425
00:33:26,780 --> 00:33:29,780
and you pride yourself on sniffing it out.

426
00:33:30,790 --> 00:33:32,810
But I'm telling you a simple truth.

427
00:33:33,270 --> 00:33:34,740
I serve the gods.

428
00:33:35,040 --> 00:33:37,230
The gods demand justice.

429
00:33:37,230 --> 00:33:39,600
How do they communicate their demands?

430
00:33:39,930 --> 00:33:41,340
By raven or horse?

431
00:33:41,340 --> 00:33:43,920
By the holy text, "The seven-pointed star."

432
00:33:44,590 --> 00:33:47,100
If you don't have one in your library,

433
00:33:47,100 --> 00:33:48,000
I'll give you my own.

434
00:33:48,010 --> 00:33:50,640
I've read "The seven-pointed star."

435
00:33:50,640 --> 00:33:52,570
Then you'll remember the passages

436
00:33:52,570 --> 00:33:55,240
concerning buggery and perjury.

437
00:33:55,360 --> 00:33:57,410
Your grandchildren will be punished

438
00:33:57,410 --> 00:33:59,740
in the same manner as anyone

439
00:33:59,740 --> 00:34:01,980
who breaks the sacred laws.

440
00:34:01,980 --> 00:34:03,510
Half the men, women, and children

441
00:34:03,510 --> 00:34:06,970
in this foul city break the sacred laws.

442
00:34:07,310 --> 00:34:10,480
You live among murderers, thieves, and rapists,

443
00:34:10,480 --> 00:34:15,780
and yet you punish Loras for shagging some perfumed ponce

444
00:34:15,900 --> 00:34:18,260
and Margaery for defending her brother?

445
00:34:18,260 --> 00:34:22,930
Yes. The gods' laws must be applied to all equally.

446
00:34:23,180 --> 00:34:25,430
If it's equality you want, so be it.

447
00:34:25,430 --> 00:34:29,460
When House Tyrell stops sending our crops to the capital,

448
00:34:29,790 --> 00:34:31,670
everyone here will starve.

449
00:34:32,410 --> 00:34:34,970
And I'll make sure the hungry know who's to blame.

450
00:34:38,010 --> 00:34:40,580
Have you ever sowed the field, Lady Olenna?

451
00:34:42,620 --> 00:34:44,410
Have you ever reaped the grain?

452
00:34:46,120 --> 00:34:47,930
Has anyone in House Tyrell?

453
00:34:49,140 --> 00:34:50,700
A lifetime of wealth and power

454
00:34:50,700 --> 00:34:52,930
has left you blind in one eye.

455
00:34:54,780 --> 00:34:58,760
You are the few, we are the many.

456
00:35:00,490 --> 00:35:03,890
And when the many stop fearing the few...

457
00:35:18,270 --> 00:35:19,400
Lady Olenna.

458
00:35:31,850 --> 00:35:35,340
Starving yourself won't make things any better for her, my love.

459
00:35:38,590 --> 00:35:40,240
She's in a prison cell

460
00:35:40,720 --> 00:35:43,500
and there is nothing I can do.

461
00:35:47,090 --> 00:35:48,530
I am the King!

462
00:35:48,680 --> 00:35:52,130
The Queen is in prison and there is nothing I can do!

463
00:36:06,420 --> 00:36:08,110
No matter who you are,

464
00:36:10,010 --> 00:36:11,860
no matter how strong you are, sooner or later,

465
00:36:11,860 --> 00:36:14,490
you'll face circumstances beyond your control.

466
00:36:15,150 --> 00:36:17,490
Events you couldn't possibly have anticipated

467
00:36:17,490 --> 00:36:19,350
or prevented even if you had.

468
00:36:19,560 --> 00:36:21,760
You cannot blame yourself for fate.

469
00:36:22,650 --> 00:36:23,830
Your father,

470
00:36:25,200 --> 00:36:26,690
Your brother, your grandfather--

471
00:36:26,690 --> 00:36:29,500
I was Queen of the Seven Kingdoms and what could I do?

472
00:36:30,050 --> 00:36:32,000
Hold them as they left this world.

473
00:36:32,720 --> 00:36:34,620
Kissed their heads after they'd gone.

474
00:36:35,180 --> 00:36:36,640
I'll call in the army.

475
00:36:37,020 --> 00:36:39,050
I'll take back the Sept

476
00:36:39,050 --> 00:36:42,660
and kill every last one of them.

477
00:36:44,530 --> 00:36:46,910
I'll start a war if I have to.

478
00:36:46,910 --> 00:36:47,990
You know as well as I do

479
00:36:47,990 --> 00:36:50,430
who the first casualty of that war would be.

480
00:36:55,470 --> 00:36:56,640
I love her.

481
00:37:00,400 --> 00:37:01,690
I love her...

482
00:37:04,810 --> 00:37:06,320
And I can't help her.

483
00:37:22,570 --> 00:37:23,940
We must be strong for those we love.

484
00:37:23,940 --> 00:37:25,910
We cannot give in to despair.

485
00:37:26,540 --> 00:37:28,980
I will speak with the High Sparrow.

486
00:37:29,430 --> 00:37:30,700
There must be something he--

487
00:37:30,700 --> 00:37:32,470
Let me talk to him on your behalf.

488
00:37:33,480 --> 00:37:37,400
The king cannot sully himself negotiating with an unwashed fanatic.

489
00:37:38,570 --> 00:37:40,680
You will try to help her?

490
00:37:40,820 --> 00:37:44,130
I'll do everything I can to win her freedom and her brother's.

491
00:37:44,230 --> 00:37:46,690
Your happiness is all I want in this world.

492
00:37:48,140 --> 00:37:50,950
- I know. - No, you don't.

493
00:37:54,670 --> 00:37:56,350
You can't possibly.

494
00:37:58,270 --> 00:38:00,210
Not until you have children of your own.

495
00:38:01,570 --> 00:38:03,240
I would do anything for you.

496
00:38:05,440 --> 00:38:07,520
Anything to keep you from harm.

497
00:38:09,960 --> 00:38:12,240
I would burn cities to the ground.

498
00:38:14,080 --> 00:38:15,700
You are all that matters.

499
00:38:17,730 --> 00:38:21,410
You and your sister.

500
00:38:21,900 --> 00:38:24,130
From the moment you came into this world.

501
00:38:24,970 --> 00:38:26,190
My boy.

502
00:38:29,230 --> 00:38:30,600
My only boy.

503
00:38:46,500 --> 00:38:47,950
Prince Doran hopes this satisfies

504
00:38:47,950 --> 00:38:50,480
your concerns about the princess's well-being.

505
00:38:57,810 --> 00:38:59,400
You looked different when I left.

506
00:38:59,830 --> 00:39:02,340
You had more hair.

507
00:39:02,340 --> 00:39:03,730
And more hands.

508
00:39:05,410 --> 00:39:08,020
- How's Trystane? - He'll be all right.

509
00:39:08,130 --> 00:39:09,160
I'm sorry for that.

510
00:39:09,160 --> 00:39:10,830
It wasn't supposed to happen that way.

511
00:39:10,960 --> 00:39:12,570
Why is it happening at all?

512
00:39:13,750 --> 00:39:15,500
Your mother's worried about you.

513
00:39:17,470 --> 00:39:18,890
Threats have been made.

514
00:39:18,990 --> 00:39:20,620
Dorne's too dangerous for you.

515
00:39:20,620 --> 00:39:22,780
- I've come to take you home. - This is my home.

516
00:39:22,780 --> 00:39:24,290
This has been my home for years.

517
00:39:24,290 --> 00:39:26,860
I didn't want to come here, but she told me to.

518
00:39:26,860 --> 00:39:27,840
I did what she said.

519
00:39:27,840 --> 00:39:30,660
I did my duty and now she's forcing me to go back?

520
00:39:30,660 --> 00:39:33,780
It's for your own good. These are complicated matters.

521
00:39:33,780 --> 00:39:36,080
No, it's not complicated at all. It's simple.

522
00:39:36,080 --> 00:39:38,560
I love Trystane, I'm going to marry him,

523
00:39:38,560 --> 00:39:40,010
and we're staying right here.

524
00:39:40,010 --> 00:39:42,300
- I don't understand. - Of course you don't.

525
00:39:42,300 --> 00:39:43,590
You don't know me.

526
00:39:52,300 --> 00:39:56,580
*Brothers, oh brothers, my days here are done,*

527
00:39:56,590 --> 00:40:01,100
*the Dornishman's taken my life,*

528
00:40:01,140 --> 00:40:05,930
*But what does it matter, for all men must die,*

529
00:40:05,940 --> 00:40:09,530
*and I've tasted the Dornishman's wife!*

530
00:40:10,850 --> 00:40:16,890
*I've tasted the Dornishman's wife!*

531
00:40:18,750 --> 00:40:20,390
He's got a good voice.

532
00:40:21,350 --> 00:40:23,000
We're lucky he's a singer.

533
00:40:23,080 --> 00:40:25,730
If he were a fighter, we might have been in trouble.

534
00:40:26,470 --> 00:40:28,520
It's against my code to hurt a woman.

535
00:40:28,520 --> 00:40:29,270
It's amazing

536
00:40:29,280 --> 00:40:31,680
how many men we beat seem to have this code.

537
00:40:31,680 --> 00:40:33,430
I wouldn't say you beat me.

538
00:40:34,000 --> 00:40:35,220
How's your arm?

539
00:40:35,220 --> 00:40:36,380
Wonderful.

540
00:40:37,390 --> 00:40:40,200
Wouldn't feel right to leave Dorne without a new scar.

541
00:40:40,760 --> 00:40:42,470
You think you're leaving Dorne?

542
00:40:42,670 --> 00:40:43,980
No great hurry.

543
00:40:44,460 --> 00:40:47,500
Dornish women are the most beautiful women in the world.

544
00:40:47,750 --> 00:40:48,690
Thank you.

545
00:40:48,690 --> 00:40:51,990
I said Dornish women. I didn't say you.

546
00:40:54,340 --> 00:40:57,140
I'm not the most beautiful woman you've ever seen?

547
00:40:58,400 --> 00:41:01,770
I've seen quite a few women in all the seven kingdoms.

548
00:41:01,980 --> 00:41:05,020
Name one more beautiful than I am.

549
00:41:06,760 --> 00:41:10,170
Well, now, in King's Landing,

550
00:41:10,300 --> 00:41:13,450
there was an absolutely gorgeous...

551
00:41:18,080 --> 00:41:19,430
There was a what?

552
00:41:21,890 --> 00:41:24,260
In King's Landing, you were saying?

553
00:41:25,000 --> 00:41:26,160
Was I?

554
00:41:27,450 --> 00:41:29,990
There was a woman more beautiful than I am.

555
00:41:30,180 --> 00:41:31,260
Was there?

556
00:41:31,960 --> 00:41:33,930
My memory's not what it was earlier.

557
00:41:37,710 --> 00:41:39,050
How's your arm now?

558
00:41:39,330 --> 00:41:41,190
You seem concerned with it.

559
00:41:41,190 --> 00:41:42,880
You must really like me.

560
00:41:51,520 --> 00:41:54,310
And how about your head?

561
00:41:58,980 --> 00:42:00,130
My head?

562
00:42:01,380 --> 00:42:02,480
My head?

563
00:42:03,710 --> 00:42:06,170
You don't even want to know what's going on in--

564
00:42:16,770 --> 00:42:18,460
Your nose is bleeding.

565
00:42:21,600 --> 00:42:24,160
It's nothing. It's the dry air.

566
00:42:27,840 --> 00:42:31,720
My dagger was coated with a special ointment from Asshai.

567
00:42:32,200 --> 00:42:34,130
They call it the Long Farewell.

568
00:42:34,690 --> 00:42:36,220
It takes time to work,

569
00:42:36,830 --> 00:42:40,530
but if a single drop makes contact with the skin,

570
00:42:41,020 --> 00:42:42,120
death.

571
00:42:50,320 --> 00:42:52,390
The only antidote.

572
00:42:57,260 --> 00:42:59,760
Who's the most beautiful woman in the world?

573
00:43:01,100 --> 00:43:02,110
You.

574
00:43:03,970 --> 00:43:05,840
Sorry? Who?

575
00:43:08,410 --> 00:43:09,530
You.

576
00:43:11,080 --> 00:43:12,260
Don't drop it.

577
00:43:27,260 --> 00:43:29,330
I think you're very handsome as well.

578
00:44:14,270 --> 00:44:16,930
- I'm sorry about the locale. - No, you're not.

579
00:44:19,600 --> 00:44:21,190
It felt like the safest place.

580
00:44:21,530 --> 00:44:23,780
Not for your clientele, clearly.

581
00:44:24,580 --> 00:44:26,810
It was an establishment like no other.

582
00:44:28,160 --> 00:44:30,430
The sheer range of appetites catered to.

583
00:44:30,430 --> 00:44:34,610
Desires that didn't even exist until we invented them.

584
00:44:35,160 --> 00:44:38,470
You've always been rather impressed with yourself, haven't you?

585
00:44:39,720 --> 00:44:41,480
The past is the past.

586
00:44:42,560 --> 00:44:45,750
The future is all that's worth discussing.

587
00:44:47,470 --> 00:44:49,170
The future of House Tyrell.

588
00:44:49,170 --> 00:44:51,830
Don't pretend to have any concern for my house,

589
00:44:51,830 --> 00:44:53,810
my grandchildren or me.

590
00:44:54,120 --> 00:44:56,180
I should have known you'd return to the capital

591
00:44:56,180 --> 00:44:58,770
as soon as things started to go wrong.

592
00:44:58,770 --> 00:45:01,170
- I promise you-- - I promise you, Lord Baelish,

593
00:45:01,450 --> 00:45:03,330
that our fates are joined.

594
00:45:03,330 --> 00:45:05,030
Together we murdered a king.

595
00:45:05,330 --> 00:45:08,560
If my house should fall, I will have nothing to hide.

596
00:45:09,610 --> 00:45:13,180
And if I should meet with some accident

597
00:45:13,180 --> 00:45:16,090
here at your broken little flesh market,

598
00:45:16,590 --> 00:45:19,340
they'll never even find what's left of you.

599
00:45:20,450 --> 00:45:21,400
So...

600
00:45:22,490 --> 00:45:24,580
do you deny a part in all this?

601
00:45:24,760 --> 00:45:27,390
Cersei summoned me to King's Landing.

602
00:45:28,030 --> 00:45:29,400
I dared not refuse her.

603
00:45:29,400 --> 00:45:31,270
And what did she want?

604
00:45:31,270 --> 00:45:33,900
A piece of information she knew that I had.

605
00:45:34,400 --> 00:45:37,390
Neither silence nor lies were an option.

606
00:45:38,220 --> 00:45:39,890
But I have other information

607
00:45:40,710 --> 00:45:42,300
of which she is unaware.

608
00:45:43,580 --> 00:45:46,480
And as you say, our interests are aligned.

609
00:45:48,550 --> 00:45:49,880
I have a gift for you.

610
00:45:50,510 --> 00:45:52,190
What kind of gift?

611
00:45:52,230 --> 00:45:54,090
The same kind I gave Cersei.

612
00:45:55,660 --> 00:45:57,210
A handsome young man.

613
00:46:11,310 --> 00:46:13,760
Many worthy fighters have died

614
00:46:13,760 --> 00:46:16,250
trying to make it to the great games.

615
00:46:16,490 --> 00:46:17,460
When most of you worthless

616
00:46:17,460 --> 00:46:19,500
scum join them in death this afternoon,

617
00:46:19,500 --> 00:46:22,590
it will represent a significant rise in your station.

618
00:46:22,940 --> 00:46:25,660
But if you do happen to triumph here,

619
00:46:25,760 --> 00:46:28,390
you will fight at the great Pit of Daznak itself

620
00:46:28,390 --> 00:46:29,970
in front of the Queen.

621
00:46:30,090 --> 00:46:34,210
So whatever happens, the gods have smiled upon you today.

622
00:46:34,690 --> 00:46:38,760
This is the day your lives actually start to mean something.

623
00:46:41,120 --> 00:46:43,960
You and you. You.

624
00:46:45,730 --> 00:46:46,600
You two.

625
00:46:48,820 --> 00:46:50,460
You, you, and you.

626
00:46:51,670 --> 00:46:52,560
Up.

627
00:46:53,880 --> 00:46:56,520
- Valar morghulis. - Valar dohaeris.

628
00:46:56,640 --> 00:46:58,320
Prepare yourselves.

629
00:47:10,840 --> 00:47:13,260
Sitting through the great games will be bad enough.

630
00:47:13,260 --> 00:47:16,250
For generations in the days leading up to the great games,

631
00:47:16,250 --> 00:47:18,020
it has been customary for our ruler

632
00:47:18,020 --> 00:47:19,760
to make the rounds of the lower pits

633
00:47:19,770 --> 00:47:22,730
to pay the fighters there the honor of her presence.

634
00:47:27,370 --> 00:47:28,640
Move yourselves.

635
00:47:35,450 --> 00:47:36,660
Your grace.

636
00:47:37,170 --> 00:47:38,560
Your future grace.

637
00:47:38,910 --> 00:47:40,280
You honor us all.

638
00:47:43,400 --> 00:47:44,730
Stand there.

639
00:47:45,670 --> 00:47:47,920
Stand straight. That's the fucking Queen.

640
00:47:49,710 --> 00:47:51,730
We fight and die for your glory,

641
00:47:51,810 --> 00:47:53,190
glorious Queen.

642
00:47:56,310 --> 00:47:58,500
We fight and die for your glory,

643
00:47:58,500 --> 00:48:00,420
glorious Queen.

644
00:48:02,360 --> 00:48:05,040
Fight!

645
00:49:03,070 --> 00:49:04,230
I think I've seen enough.

646
00:49:04,230 --> 00:49:07,130
Your grace, it is a tradition

647
00:49:07,240 --> 00:49:10,080
for the Queen to stay until the victor has emerged.

648
00:49:10,080 --> 00:49:12,560
I've sacrificed more than enough for your traditions.

649
00:49:17,680 --> 00:49:18,590
What are you doing?

650
00:49:28,020 --> 00:49:30,440
Wait your turn, you piece of fucking filth.

651
00:50:59,720 --> 00:51:01,150
Get him out of my sight.

652
00:51:01,540 --> 00:51:03,160
Khaleesi, please.

653
00:51:03,510 --> 00:51:05,330
I just need a moment of your time.

654
00:51:06,300 --> 00:51:07,680
I brought you a gift.

655
00:51:08,610 --> 00:51:09,560
It's true.

656
00:51:11,810 --> 00:51:12,800
He has.

657
00:51:14,570 --> 00:51:15,440
Who are you?

658
00:51:17,380 --> 00:51:18,520
I am the gift.

659
00:51:21,460 --> 00:51:23,290
It's a pleasure to meet you, your grace.

660
00:51:25,160 --> 00:51:27,010
My name isTyrion Lannister.

661
00:52:00,630 --> 00:52:02,190
This is horrible.

662
00:52:02,340 --> 00:52:03,720
Unacceptable.

663
00:52:05,930 --> 00:52:08,110
Are they feeding you enough at least?

664
00:52:09,690 --> 00:52:12,560
I brought you this. Venison.

665
00:52:13,470 --> 00:52:14,730
It's quite good.

666
00:52:17,970 --> 00:52:20,810
I had it myself for supper only last night.

667
00:52:24,970 --> 00:52:26,150
We did everything we could

668
00:52:26,150 --> 00:52:28,070
from the moment they took your brother.

669
00:52:28,260 --> 00:52:30,030
Tommen even went to the Sept himself

670
00:52:30,030 --> 00:52:31,820
to confront the High Sparrow.

671
00:52:32,640 --> 00:52:35,330
But I fear the Faith has left reason behind.

672
00:52:35,550 --> 00:52:37,840
I know you did this.

673
00:52:38,870 --> 00:52:42,140
We are making every effort on your behalf.

674
00:52:42,590 --> 00:52:44,940
I swear to you by all the seven gods.

675
00:52:44,940 --> 00:52:47,220
Lies come easily to you.

676
00:52:47,230 --> 00:52:48,850
Everyone knows that.

677
00:52:49,060 --> 00:52:50,710
But innocence,

678
00:52:51,670 --> 00:52:53,950
decency, concern,

679
00:52:54,700 --> 00:52:56,900
you're not very good at those, I'm afraid.

680
00:52:58,460 --> 00:53:00,720
Perhaps that's why your son was so eager

681
00:53:00,730 --> 00:53:02,960
to cast you aside for me.

682
00:53:04,880 --> 00:53:06,300
You're upset.

683
00:53:07,120 --> 00:53:08,800
You're not thinking clearly.

684
00:53:09,390 --> 00:53:11,650
I'll visit again when you've had a chance to calm down.

685
00:53:11,650 --> 00:53:13,700
I don't want to see you again.

686
00:53:13,760 --> 00:53:16,160
I do hope you change your mind about that.

687
00:53:16,650 --> 00:53:18,660
I've been told men often go mad

688
00:53:18,660 --> 00:53:20,960
in the black cells beneath the Red Keep.

689
00:53:21,310 --> 00:53:23,110
Though I suppose your isolation will end

690
00:53:23,110 --> 00:53:24,910
when your trial begins.

691
00:53:26,720 --> 00:53:28,110
Leave.

692
00:53:28,580 --> 00:53:29,430
Yes.

693
00:53:30,570 --> 00:53:31,980
I'm afraid I must.

694
00:53:31,980 --> 00:53:34,100
My son needs me now more than ever.

695
00:53:34,700 --> 00:53:36,660
Get out, you hateful bitch!

696
00:53:50,860 --> 00:53:52,270
Sleep well, sister.

697
00:54:20,760 --> 00:54:21,870
Thank you, Boake.

698
00:54:29,190 --> 00:54:30,920
- You saw her? - Yes.

699
00:54:31,180 --> 00:54:33,450
- And? - Her accommodations seem sufficient.

700
00:54:33,450 --> 00:54:34,770
What happens to her now?

701
00:54:36,160 --> 00:54:38,190
Well, she and her brother are both being held

702
00:54:38,190 --> 00:54:39,850
under fair suspicion.

703
00:54:40,270 --> 00:54:42,780
A trial will be held for each of them

704
00:54:42,780 --> 00:54:45,620
to determine if they're guilty of any acts

705
00:54:45,620 --> 00:54:49,460
that might constitute a violation of the tenets of the faith.

706
00:54:49,750 --> 00:54:51,170
Who will stand judge?

707
00:54:51,170 --> 00:54:55,860
Seven septons as it was in all trials before the Targaryens.

708
00:54:56,930 --> 00:54:58,220
Will you be one of them?

709
00:54:58,700 --> 00:54:59,560
I will.

710
00:55:02,090 --> 00:55:03,850
If one or both of them

711
00:55:03,850 --> 00:55:06,240
were to confess before the trial...

712
00:55:06,260 --> 00:55:08,350
Then they will be shown the Mother's mercy.

713
00:55:09,650 --> 00:55:11,770
And what does the Mother's mercy entail?

714
00:55:12,550 --> 00:55:14,560
It depends upon the situation.

715
00:55:15,030 --> 00:55:17,810
The acts themselves, the degree of contrition.

716
00:55:17,810 --> 00:55:19,870
Thank you, High Septon,

717
00:55:20,720 --> 00:55:23,580
for bringing them whatever justice they deserve

718
00:55:24,530 --> 00:55:26,020
in the eyes of the Seven.

719
00:55:30,610 --> 00:55:31,820
Did you know this chapel

720
00:55:31,820 --> 00:55:34,750
is one of the oldest structures in King's Landing?

721
00:55:36,350 --> 00:55:38,370
I think I may have heard at one point.

722
00:55:38,710 --> 00:55:41,170
Baelor built his Sept around it.

723
00:55:42,870 --> 00:55:45,450
But men worshipped here long before him.

724
00:55:46,450 --> 00:55:48,310
Who carved this altar?

725
00:55:49,150 --> 00:55:51,340
- Do you know? - I'm afraid I don't.

726
00:55:52,620 --> 00:55:53,770
No one does.

727
00:55:54,660 --> 00:55:58,230
There's no name on it or anywhere else in the chapel.

728
00:56:00,450 --> 00:56:02,610
No, the people who built this place

729
00:56:02,830 --> 00:56:06,570
didn't inflict their vanity on those who came after them

730
00:56:06,970 --> 00:56:10,840
the way Baelor did with that great gilded monstrosity up there.

731
00:56:12,530 --> 00:56:14,310
Their faith was clean.

732
00:56:15,860 --> 00:56:18,940
Strip away the gold and the ornaments,

733
00:56:19,390 --> 00:56:21,800
knock down the statues and the pillars,

734
00:56:22,640 --> 00:56:24,400
and this is what remains.

735
00:56:27,580 --> 00:56:30,220
Something simple...

736
00:56:33,310 --> 00:56:36,960
and solid and true.

737
00:56:41,250 --> 00:56:44,400
The Tyrells' finery will be stripped away.

738
00:56:45,590 --> 00:56:47,430
Their lies knocked down.

739
00:56:47,430 --> 00:56:50,300
Their true hearts laid bare for all to see.

740
00:56:51,990 --> 00:56:54,100
And so it will be for all of us.

741
00:56:54,720 --> 00:56:57,150
High and low alike.

742
00:57:01,540 --> 00:57:03,050
What will we find

743
00:57:03,910 --> 00:57:06,340
when we strip away your finery?

744
00:57:09,940 --> 00:57:12,810
A young man came to us not long ago.

745
00:57:13,860 --> 00:57:16,030
Broken in body and spirit.

746
00:57:18,320 --> 00:57:20,740
He had so much to strip away.

747
00:57:22,500 --> 00:57:24,580
So much weighing him down.

748
00:57:26,220 --> 00:57:29,440
But piece by piece, he unburdened himself.

749
00:57:30,840 --> 00:57:32,360
Let go of vanity,

750
00:57:32,930 --> 00:57:35,240
pride, sin.

751
00:57:37,950 --> 00:57:40,200
Now his soul is so light,

752
00:57:40,630 --> 00:57:43,840
he will float through the Seven Heavens like a bird.

753
00:57:50,770 --> 00:57:52,960
And he has much to say about you.

754
00:58:17,350 --> 00:58:18,330
Move.

755
00:58:21,320 --> 00:58:23,820
Let me go immediately.

756
00:58:24,350 --> 00:58:26,720
You will order her to let me go.

757
00:58:26,840 --> 00:58:29,190
I am the queen! I am the queen!

758
00:58:29,190 --> 00:58:30,940
Have you lost your mind?

759
00:58:31,650 --> 00:58:32,930
Let me go!

760
00:58:34,750 --> 00:58:36,470
Get your filthy hands off me!

761
00:58:36,470 --> 00:58:38,190
Have you lost your mind?

762
00:58:39,020 --> 00:58:41,810
I am the queen! Let me go!

763
00:58:48,170 --> 00:58:49,080
Look at me.

764
00:58:52,250 --> 00:58:53,680
Look at my face.

765
00:58:56,620 --> 00:58:59,460
It's the last thing you'll see before you die.

