( Theme music playing )
♪ Game of Thrones 1x10 ♪
Fire and Blood
Original Air Date on June 19, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
( Muffled cheering
and screams )
( Louder screaming )
Look at me.
Look at me!
Do you remember
me now, boy, eh?
Remember me?
There's a bright boy.
You'll be coming
with me, boy,
and you'll be keeping
your mouth shut.
- Keep your mouth shut, boy.
- I'm not a boy!
You're not a smart boy,
is that what you're trying to say?
Do you want
to live, boy?!
( Knife snicks )
North, boy,
we're going north.
( Cawing )
It had three eyes.
It told me to come
with him, so I did.
We went down into the crypts
and my father was there.
Osha: Your father's not
down there, little lord.
Not for many years yet.
You're afraid--
just like Hodor.
I'm not afraid of some hole
in the ground.
You've lived beyond the Wall.
What are you scared of?
I'm a crippled boy
and I'm willing to go.
That's my grandfather
Lord Rickard.
He was burned alive
by the Mad King Aerys.
That's Lyanna,
my father's sister.
King Robert was
supposed to marry her,
but Rhaegar Targaryen
kidnapped her.
Robert started a war
to win her back.
He killed Rhaegar,
but she died anyway.
That's where
I saw father.
You see?
He's not here.
( Growling )
- ( Snarling )
- ( Screams )
-( Boy) Here, Shaggydog.
-( Bran) Rickon!
( Osha panting )
That beast
is supposed to be
chained in the kennels!
- He doesn't like chains.
- What are you doing down here?
- Come back up with us.
- No, I came to see father.
How many times have I told you?
He's in King's Landing
with Sansa and Arya.
He was down here.
I saw him.
Saw him when?
Last night,
when I was sleeping.
Here, Shaggydog.
You both miss him.
It's only natural
he should be in your thoughts
and dreams,
but that doesn't mean that--
Bran...
- My Lady.
My Lady.
( Panting )
( Wheezing )
( Soft grunting,
thudding )
( Louder grunting )
Robb.
- Robb!
- ( Sobs )
You've ruined your sword.
Shh shh.
- Shh.
- I'll kill them all--
( sobs )
--Every one of them.
I will kill them all.
- My boy.
- ( Sobbing )
They have your sisters.
We have to get
the girls back.
And then we will
kill them all.
Marillion: ♪ the boar's great tusks,
they boded ill ♪
♪ for good
King Robert's health ♪
♪ and the beast was
every bit as fat ♪
♪ as Robert was himself ♪
♪ but our brave King cried,
"Do your worst!
♪ I'll have
your ugly head! ♪
♪ you're nowhere near
as murd'rous as ♪
♪ the lion in my bed" ♪
♪ King Robert
lost his battle and ♪
♪ he failed
his final test ♪
♪ the lion ripped
his balls off ♪
♪ and ♪
♪ the boar
did all the rest. ♪
Very amusing.
Isn't it a funny song?
Thank you
for your rendition.
I imagine it was even better
received at that tavern.
I'm so sorry,
Your Grace.
I'll never sing it again,
I swear.
Tell me,
which do you favor:
Your fingers
or your tongue?
Your Grace?
Fingers
or your tongue?
If you got to keep one,
which would it be?
I-- I--
or I could just
cut your throat.
Every man needs hands,
Your Grace.
Good.
- Tongue it is.
- Your Grace, please.
I won't sing--
Your Grace.
Ser Ilyn,
who better than you
- to carry out the sentence?
- I beg you!
Please no.
No!
Your Grace, please.
I beg you, I will never sing again!
- I'm done for the day.
- No-oooo!
I'll leave the rest
of the matters to you, mother.
( Screaming continues )
Your Grace, please!
You look quite nice.
Thank you, My Lord.
"Your Grace."
I'm King now.
Stop-ppp!
No!
Walk with me.
I want to show you something.
- ( Blade zings )
- ( Gurgles )
Do as you're bid, child.
...And as soon as you've had
your blood, I'll put a son in you.
Mother says that
shouldn't be long.
( Flies buzzing )
No, please no!
This one's your father.
This one here.
Look at it and see
what happens to traitors.
- You promised to be merciful.
- I was.
I gave him
a clean death.
Look at him.
Please let me go home.
I won't do any treason, I swear.
Mother says I'm still to marry you.
So you'll stay here
and obey.
Look at him!
Joffrey: Well?
How long
do I have to look?
As long as it pleases me.
Do you want
to see the rest?
If it please Your Grace.
That's your Septa there.
I'll tell you what:
I'm going to give you
a present.
After I raise my armies
and kill your traitor brother,
I'm going to give you
his head as well.
Or maybe he'll
give me yours.
My mother tells me a King
should never strike his lady.
Ser Meryn.
Here, girl.
Will you obey now?
Or do you need
another lesson?
I'll look for you
in court.
Save yourself
some pain, girl.
Give him what he wants.
You'll be
needing that again.
The proper course
is clear:
Pledge fealty to King Renly
and move south
to join our forces
with his.
Robb:
Renly is not the King.
You cannot mean
to hold to Joffrey, My Lord.
He put your father
to death.
That doesn't
make Renly King.
He's Robert's
youngest brother.
If Bran can't be Lord
of Winterfell before me,
Renly can't be King
before Stannis.
Do you mean to declare us
for Stannis?
- Renly is not right!
- (Greatjon) My Lords.
(Man) If we put ourselves
behind Stannis--
My Lords!
Here is what I say
to these two Kings--
( spits )
( Cheers, laughter )
Renly Baratheon
is nothing to me,
nor Stannis neither.
Why should they rule
over me and mine
from some flowery seat
in the South?
What do they know of the Wall
or the Wolfswood?
Even their Gods
are wrong!
( All laugh )
Why shouldn't we rule
ourselves again?
It was the Dragons
we bowed to
and now the Dragons
are dead!
There sits the only King
I mean to bend
my knee to--
the King
in the North!
I'll have peace
on those terms.
They can keep
their Red Castle
and their Iron Chair too.
The King
in the North!
Am I your brother,
now and always?
Now and always.
My sword is yours,
in victory and defeat
from this day
until my last day.
The King
in the North!
All: The King in the North!
The King in the North!
The King
in the North!
The King in the North!
The King
in the North!
The King in the North!
The King
in the North!
The King in the North!
- Lady Stark.
- I want to see him.
Now!
( Prisoners coughing )
Leave us.
You look lovely
tonight, Lady Stark.
Widowhood becomes you.
Your bed must be lonely.
Is that why you came?
I'm not at my best,
but I think I could
be of service.
You slip out of that gown
and we'll see if I'm up to it.
( groans )
Oh, I do like
a violent woman.
I will kill you
tonight, Ser,
pack your head in a box
and send it to your sister.
Let me show you how--
hit me again,
over the ear.
And again and again.
You're stronger than you look--
it shouldn't take long.
That is what you want
the world to believe,
isn't it?
That you don't fear death.
But I don't, My Lady.
The dark is coming for all of us.
Why cry about it?
Because you are going
to the deepest
of the Seven Hells,
if the Gods are just.
What Gods are those?
The trees your husband
prayed to?
Where were the trees when his
head was getting chopped off?
If your Gods are real
and if they are just,
why is the world
so full of injustice?
Because of men like you.
There are no men like me.
Only me.
My son Bran.
How did he come to fall
from that tower?
I pushed him
out the window.
Why?
I hoped the fall
would kill him.
Why?
( Inhales )
You should get some sleep.
It's going to be
a long war.
I can't believe
we're actually at war.
Was it this exciting last time,
when you were young?
What does it say?
Have we captured
Robb Stark yet?
- What's our next move?
- Stop talking.
Get back into bed.
They have my son.
The Stark boy appears
to be less green than we'd hoped.
I've heard his wolf killed a doze
men and as many horses.
Is it true about
Stannis and Renly?
Both Baratheon brothers
have taken up against us.
Jaime captured,
his armies scattered...
It's a catastrophe.
Perhaps we should
sue for peace.
( Goblet shatters )
There's your peace.
Joffrey saw to that when h
decided to remove Ned Stark's head.
You'll have an easier time
drinking from that cup
than you will bringing Robb Stark
to the table now.
He's winning...
in case you
hadn't noticed.
I'm told we still
have his sisters.
The first order of business
is ransoming Ser Jaime.
No truces.
We can't afford to look weak.
We should march
on them at once.
First we must return
to Casterly Rock to raise--
They have my son!
Get out, all of you.
Not you.
You were right
about Eddard Stark.
If he were alive,
we could have used him
to broker a peace
with Winterfell and Riverrun,
which would have
given us more time
to deal with Robert's brothers.
But now...
Madness--
madness and stupidity.
I always thought
you were a stunted fool.
Perhaps I was wrong.
Half wrong.
I'm new to strategy, but--
unless we want to be
surrounded by three armies,
it appears we can't
stay here.
No one will stay here.
Ser Gregor will head out
with 500 riders
and set the Riverland on fire
from God's Eye to the Red Fork.
The rest of us will
regroup at Harrenhal.
And you will go
to King's Landing.
And do what?
Rule!
You will serve as Hand
of the King in my stead.
You will bring that boy King to heel
and his mother too, if needs be.
And if you get so much as a whiff
of treason from any of the rest:
- Baelish, Varys, Pycelle--
- Heads, spikes, walls.
Why not my Uncle?
Why not anyone?
Why me?
You're my son.
Oh, one more thing:
You will not take
the whore to court.
Do you understand?
( Animals calling )
Ser Jorah?
Gently gently.
My son...
Where is he?
I want him.
The boy did not live.
- Tell me.
- What is there to tell?
How did my son die?!
He never lived,
My Princess.
The women say...
What do the women say?
- They say the child was--
- (Mirri) Monstrous,
twisted.
I pulled him out
myself.
He was scaled
like a lizard,
blind, with leather wings
like the wings of a bat.
When I touched him
the skin fell from his bones.
Inside he was
full of graveworms.
I warned you that only death
can pay for life.
You knew the price.
Where is Khal Drogo?
Show him to me.
Show me what I bought
with my son's life.
As you command, lady.
Come.
I will take you
to him.
- Time enough for that later--
- I want to see him now.
The Khalasar is gone.
A Khal who cannot ride
is no Khal.
The Dothraki
follow only the strong.
I'm sorry, My Princess.
Drogo!
Why is he out here alone?
He seems to like
the warmth, Princess.
Mirri:
He lives.
You asked for life,
you paid for life.
This is not life.
When will he be as he was?
When the sun rises in the west,
sets in the east
when the seas go dry.
When the mountains blow
in the wind like leaves.
Leave us.
I don't want you alone
with this sorceress.
I have nothing more
to fear from this woman.
Go.
You knew what I was buying
and you knew the price.
It was wrong of them
to burn my temple.
- It angered the Great Shepherd.
- This is not God's work.
- My child was innocent.
- Innocent?
He would have been the stallion
who mounts the world.
Now he will burn no cities.
Now his Khalasar will trample
no nations into dust.
I spoke for you.
I saved you.
( Chuckles )
Saved me?
Three of those riders
had already
raped me before
you saved me, girl.
I saw my God's house burn,
there where I had healed men
and women beyond counting.
In the streets
I saw piles of heads--
the head of the Baker
who makes my bread,
the head of a young boy
that I had cured of fever
just three moons past.
So tell me again
exactly what it was
that you saved.
Your life.
Hmph.
Why don't you take
a look at your Khal...
Then you will see
exactly what life is worth
when all the rest has gone.
You can't!
Get out of my way, Sam.
They'll put out the word.
They'll send out ravens.
People will come after you.
Do you know what happens
to deserters?
Better than you do.
What are you going to do?
I'm gonna find my brother
and put a sword through
King Joffrey's throat.
You can't leave us now.
We need you here.
- Move.
- I won't let you go.
- No.
- Hyah!
- ( Neighs )
Hand of the King?
So it would seem.
And your father said you couldn't take
anyone with you to King's Landing.
No, he said I couldn't take you
with me to King's Landing.
He was very specific
on that point.
He knew my name?
What?
He said, "Don't bring Shae
with you to King's Landing"?
I believe he used
the word "whore."
Are you ashamed of me?
Are you afraid that I'm dancing
around the court with my tits out?
- ( Chuckles )
- I'm funny now?
I'm Shae the funny whore.
My father's probably the most
powerful man in the country.
Certainly the richest.
He has all Seven Kingdoms
in his pockets.
Everyone everywhere
always has to do exactly
what my father says.
He's always been a cunt.
I believe the ladies
of the court
could learn a great deal
from a girl like you.
Why don't you
come with me,
be the Hand's lady?
Because the King needs
a Hand and the Hand--
I know what
a Hand needs.
- ( Ghost barks )
- ( Shouting )
- Ghost?
- Hyah!
- Hyah.
Hyah.
( Shrieks )
- ( Neighs )
- Samwell!
- Is he dead?
- No, he's not dead.
Samwell:
Did we get him?
Grenn: Come on, help me
get him up.
Lucky you've got
plenty of padding.
We're taking you back
to where you belong.
- I belong with my brother.
- But we're your brothers now.
They'll kill you if they find out
you've gone.
They'll kill you if they know
you came after me.
- Go back.
- Sam told us everything.
- We're sorry about your father.
- But it doesn't matter.
You took the oath.
You can't leave.
- I have to.
- You can't.
- You said the words.
- I don't care about--
"Hear my words and bear
witness to my vow..."
To hell with all of you.
"Night gathers and now
my Watch begins.
It shall not end
until my death.
I shall live and die
at my post."
"I am the sword
in the darkness..."
All:
"...The Watcher on the Walls,
the shield that guards
the realms of men.
I pledge my life and honor
to the Night's Watch,
for this night
and all nights to come."
( Water spatters )
When the sun
rises in the west
and sets in the east...
( Sobs )
Then you shall return
to me, my sun and stars.
( Sobbing )
Kings?
( Chuckles )
Oh, I can tell you all
there is to know about Kings.
The thing you need to
understand about Kings is...
For the past 67 years,
I've known--
truly known more Kings
than any man alive.
They're complicated men,
but I know how to serve them.
( Chuckles ) Yes.
And keep on serving them.
( Coughs )
Aerys Targaryen...
of all the thousand thousand
maladies the Gods visit on us,
madness is the worst.
He was a good man,
such a charmer.
To watch him melt away
before my eyes,
consumed by dreams
of fire and blood...
Robert Baratheon
was an entirely different animal--
powerful man,
a great warrior--
but alas,
winning a Kingdom
and ruling a Kingdom
are rather different things.
They say that
if a man goes through life
with his battle visor down,
he can often be blind
to the enemies at his side.
( Chuckles )
( Coughs )
Now I serve his son
King Joffrey,
may the Gods
bless his reign.
He is a capable young man--
strong military mind.
Stern...
But sternness in defense
of the realm is no vice.
It's far too soon to know what
manner of King he will be,
but I sense
true greatness on the horizon
for our new King.
True greatness.
So what's the thing?
What thing?
About Kings.
You said, "the thing you need
to understand about Kings..."
What? Things?
What?
When you started, you--
never mind.
( Mutters )
Let me see you
out, my dear.
- It's all right. No need.
- Yes yes.
Till the next time.
( Sighs )
Right.
( Groans )
When you imagine yourself up
there, how do you look?
Does the crown fit?
Do all the lords and ladies
simper and bow, the ones who
sneered at you for years?
It's hard for them to simper
and bow without heads.
A man with great ambition
and no morals--
I wouldn't
bet against you.
And what would you do,
my friend,
if you found yourself
sitting up there?
I must be one of the few men
in this city
who doesn't
want to be King.
You must be one
of the few men in the city
who isn't a man.
Oh, you can do
better than that.
When they castrated you, did they
take the pillar with the stones?
- I've always wondered.
- Have you?
Do you spend a lot of time wondering
what's between my legs?
I picture a gash
like a woman's.
Is that about right?
I am flattered, of course,
to be pictured at all.
Must be strange for you,
even after all these years--
a man from another land,
despised by most,
feared by all--
am I?
That is good to know.
Do you lie awake at night
fearing my gash?
But you carry on,
whispering in one King's ear
and then the next.
I admire you.
And I admire you,
Lord Baelish.
A grasper from a minor house
with a major talent
for befriending
powerful men--
and women.
A useful talent,
I'm sure you'd agree.
So here we stand...
In mutual admiration
and respect.
Playing our roles.
Serving a new King.
Long may he reign.
- My King.
My Lords.
Shall we begin?
Yoren:
You're Arry now, hear me?
Arry the orphan boy.
No one asks an orphan
too many questions
'cause nobody gives
three shits.
What's your name?
- Arry.
- Ah.
We have a long way
to travel and in bad company.
I have 20 this time,
men and boys all
bound for the Wall.
Your Lord father gave me
the pick of the dungeons
and I didn't find
no little lordlings down there.
This lot, half of them would
turn you over to the King
quick as spit for a pardon.
And the other half
would do the same,
except they'd
rape you first.
So keep to yourself--
and when you piss,
do it in the woods alone.
You stay
with this lot, boy.
And stay--
or I'll lock you in the back of
the wagon with these three.
Watch yourself,
midget.
He's got a sword,
this one.
What's a gutter rat
like you doing with a sword?
- Maybe he's a little squire.
- He ain't no squire. Look at him.
- ( Grunts )
- He looks like a girl.
I bet he stole
that sword.
Let's have a look.
I could use me
a sword like that.
- Take it off him.
- Give it here, midget.
Look at him!
You'd better give
Hot Pie the sword.
I've seen him
kick a boy to death.
I knocked him down
and I kicked him in the balls
and I kept kicking him
until he was dead.
I kicked him
all to pieces.
- You better give me that sword!
- You want it?
I'll give it to you.
I already killed
one fat boy.
I bet you never
killed anyone.
I bet you're a liar.
But I'm not.
I'm good at killing
fat boys.
- I like killing fat boys.
- ( Gasps )
Oh, you like picking
on the little ones, do you?
You know, I've been hammering
an anvil these past 10 years.
When I hit
that steel, it sings.
Are you gonna sing
when I hit you?
This is
castle-forged steel.
Where'd you steal it?
- It was a gift.
- It don't matter now.
Where we're going,
they don't care what you've done.
They've got rapers,
pickpockets, highwaymen--
murderers.
- Which are you?
- Armorer's apprentice.
But my master
got sick of me,
so here I am.
Yoren: Come on, you sorry
sons of whores!
It's a thousand leagues
from here to the Wall
and winter is coming!
Ham.
How many days in a row
must a man be
expected to start
his day with ham?
Bring me some beer
at least.
You look exhausted.
Was your moonlight ride
that tiring?
Don't look so terrified.
If we beheaded everyone
that ran away for the night,
only ghosts
would guard the Wall.
At least you weren't
whoring in Mole's Town.
Honor made you leave,
honor brought you back.
My friends
brought me back.
I didn't say
it was your honor.
They killed my father.
And you're going to bring him
back to life, are you?
No? Good.
We've had enough
of that sort of thing.
Beyond the Wall,
the rangers are
reporting whole villages
abandoned.
At night they see fires
blazing in the mountains
from dusk until dawn.
A captured wildling swears their tribes
are uniting in some secret stronghold,
to what ends
the Gods only know.
Outside Eastwatch
Cotter Pyke's men discovered four
blue-eyed corpses.
Unlike us, they were wise enough
to burn them.
Do you think
your brother's war
is more important
than ours?
- No.
- When dead men and worse
come hunting for us in the night,
do you think it matters
who sits
on the Iron Throne?
- No.
- Good.
Because I want you
and your wolf with us
when we ride out
beyond the Wall tomorrow.
Beyond the Wall?
I'll not sit meekly by
and wait for the snows.
I mean to find out
what's happening.
The Night's Watch will
ride in force
against the wildlings,
the White Walkers
and whatever else
is out there.
( Men shouting )
Mormont:
And we will find Benjen Stark,
alive or dead.
I will command them
myself.
So I'll only ask you once,
Lord Snow...
Man:
Move out!
...Are you a brother
of the Night's Watch
or a bastard boy
who wants to play at war?
Drogo will have no use for
dragon eggs in the Night Lands.
Sell them. You can return
to the Free Cities
and live as a wealthy woman
for all your days.
They were not
given to me to sell.
Khaleesi, My Queen,
I vow to serve you,
obey you,
to die for you
if need be,
but let him go,
Khaleesi.
I know what you intend.
Do not.
I must.
You don't understand--
don't ask me to stand aside
as you climb on that pyre.
I won't watch you burn.
Is that what you fear?
You will be my Khalasar.
I see the faces of slaves.
I free you.
Take off your collars. Go if yo
wish, no one will stop you.
But if you stay,
it will be as
brothers and sisters,
as husbands and wives.
( Soft laughter )
Ser Jorah, bind this woman
to the pyre.
You swore to obey me.
( Grunting )
I am Daenerys Stormborn
of House Targaryen
of the blood of Old Valyria.
I am the Dragon's daughter.
And I swear to you
that those who would harm you
will die screaming.
You will not
hear me scream.
I will.
But it is not
your screams I want.
Only your life.
( Singing )
( Wailing )
( Mirri screaming )
( Screaming continues )
( Chirruping )
( Soft snarls )
Blood of my blood.
( Hisses )
( Shrieking )
( Shrieking continues )
( Theme music playing )
== sync, corrected by elderman ==